<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 23:52:32 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 23:52:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for iOS/iPadOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned Macs into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows compatibility reports for Windows updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the app and driver compatibility reports for Windows devices before you deploy Intune policies for feature updates or update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-compatibility-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-supervised-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Update Supersedence for Enterprise App Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to update an Enterprise App Catalog app using supersedence with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-eam-supersedence</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an Enterprise App Catalog App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add an Enterprise App Catalog app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-enterprise-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to set up and use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent for Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/vulnerability-remediation-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use EPM support approvals for file elevation requests with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage support approvals for elevation requests when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-support-approved</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Apps to Groups in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign an Intune app to groups of users or devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Include and Exclude App Assignments in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to include and exclude app assignments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-inc-exl-assignments</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Group to Manage Users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to create a group based on existing users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-group</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use third-party certification authorities (CA) with SCEP in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, you can add a vendor or third-party certificate authority (CA) to issue certificates to mobile devices using the SCEP protocol. In this overview, a Microsoft Entra application gives Microsoft Intune permissions to validate certificates. Then, use the application ID, authentication key, and tenant ID of the Microsoft Entra application in the setup of your SCEP server to issue certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-authority-add-scep-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune to remediate vulnerabilities found by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune Security Tasks to manage threats and vulnerabilities identified by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/atp-manage-vulnerabilities</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 09:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect Intune account to managed Google Play account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect your Intune account to your Managed Google Play account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/connect-intune-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows Backup for Organizations in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows backup and restore in Intune for employees or students.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-backup-restore</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported filter device and app properties &amp; operators in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>When using filters, get more information on the device properties, supported operators, and supported Windows OS SKUs, including examples. Use these features to create rule expressions in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-device-properties</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about the Microsoft Tunnel VPN solution for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway, a VPN server for Intune that runs on Linux. With Microsoft Tunnel, cloud-based devices you manage with Intune can reach your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Intune data with natural language and take action - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, use Explorer to query your data in natural language and run built-in queries that match your request. Copilot summarizes the results, and provides recommendations and actions based on the query results. You can also create policies that target users and groups in the query results. Use this feature to explore your Intune data, troubleshoot issues, and create custom reports.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-explorer</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control AI features on Android Enterprise devices</title>
      <description>Using Microsoft Intune, you can manage and restrict AI usage on Android devices enrolled in Intune. This guide provides lists the steps in Intune to block AI apps, websites, screen-driven experiences, on-device AI services, and OEM-specific AI features. You can manage Microsoft Copilot, Google Gemini, Samsung Galaxy AI, claude.ai, ChatGPT, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/ai/manage-ai-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Protection Policy Settings for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy (APP) settings for MAM on Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common tasks and features in the settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure common features. You can create a Universal Print policy, configure Microsoft Edge and Google Chrome web browsers, and use built in settings instead of plist files for macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-common-features</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create filters in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about policy assignment filters, and see the steps to create, update, or delete a filter in Microsoft Intune. Create an assignment filter for managed devices or managed apps scenarios.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign Managed Google Play Apps to Android Enterprise Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how to synchronize and assign apps to Android Enterprise devices from the Managed Google Play store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-managed-home-screen-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android configuration list for Intune settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune settings catalog to add, configure, or restrict features on Android devices. This article lists and describes the settings you can configure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple User Enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple User Enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-user-enrollment-supported-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Managed Google Play apps on Intune-managed devices - Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot common issues with Managed Google Play for Android Enterprise devices enrolled in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/app-management/troubleshoot-google-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 02:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS device enrollment guide for  Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll macOS devices using device enrollment, automated device enrollment (DEP), and Apple Configurator enrollment options in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device enrollment guide for  Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll iOS and iPadOS devices using user and device enrollment, automated device enrollment (DEP), and Apple Configurator in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-passcode</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor your Endpoint Privilege Management policies for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View reports for managed and unmanaged file elevations when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple Volume-Purchased Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to improve your security posture with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-configure-security</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased device security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure devices with Microsoft Intune to support your Zero Trust journey.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-secure-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased tenant security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure your tenant with Microsoft Intune to support your Zero Trust journey.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-secure-tenant</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased data security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure data on devices with Microsoft Intune to support your Zero Trust journey.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-secure-data</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Intune sends to Google - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>List of data that Intune sends to Google when Android enterprise device management is enabled with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/data-intune-sends-to-google</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect device hardware info with the properties catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the properties catalog in Microsoft Intune view and collect enhanced device hardware info on Windows devices you manage with Intune. You can collect info like BIOS version, TPM status, disk info, memory details, and network adapter configurations. Use this information to get deeper visibility into your device inventory and troubleshoot issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Hide Devices With Cleanup Rules - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune's device cleanup rules offer a simple, automated way to ensure that only actively managed devices remain visible in the admin center. Learn more about device cleanup rules and how to configure them.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-cleanup-rules</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use derived credentials for mobile devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a third-party partners derived credential as an authentication method for Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/derived-credentials</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Wipe - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wipe, or factory reset, devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Disable Activation Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune to disable Activation Lock on Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-activation-lock-disable</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Find lost devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Locate lost or stolen devices by using the locate device feature in Microsoft Intune. Get details on security and privacy information when using the locate device action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-locate</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Collect Diagnostics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Retire - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to retire device using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-retire</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Reset Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to reset a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-passcode-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Sync - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the device sync remote action in Intune to apply policy, app, and configuration updates to managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Send Custom Notifications - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Delete - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to delete devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Lost Mode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enable Lost Mode in Microsoft Intune to remotely lock a lost or stolen iOS or iPadOS device and display a custom message and phone number on the lock screen.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-lost-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Update Cellular Data Plan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to update the cellular data plan for iOS/iPadOS devices that support eSIM with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/update-cellular-data-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Run Remediation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand remediations with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-run-remediation</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Logout current user - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the logout the current user from a Shared iPad with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-logout-user</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove User - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a user from a Shared iPad with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-user</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Full Scan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand Microsoft Defender full scan with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-full-scan</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Shutdown - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to shutdown Apple devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-shutdown</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: New Remote Assistance Session - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the the new remote assistance session action in Intune to offer support to your users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remote-assist</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Play Lost Mode Sound - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Play lost device sound remote action in Microsoft Intune to trigger an audible alert on a lost, stolen, or misplaced device—helping users locate it quickly and securely.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-play-lost-mode-sound</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Quick Scan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand Microsoft Defender quick scan with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-quick-scan</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Remote Action: Deprovision - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to deprovision a chromeOS device with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-deprovision</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: BitLocker Key Rotation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the BitLocker recovery key with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-bitlocker-keys</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Actions – Wipe, Lock, Locate, and More - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how to use Microsoft Intune to remotely manage, wipe, lock, restart, and secure Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, Windows, and ChromeOS devices. Learn about available remote actions, prerequisites, and bulk actions for IT admins.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Apps and Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how apps and configurations can be removed temporarily, then restored automatically or manually using the Remove apps and configuration device action with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/remove-apps-config</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Remote Action: Rotate FileVault Recovery Key - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the FileVault recovery key with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Rotate local admin password - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the local admin password on Windows and macOS devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-local-admin-password</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Pause Config Refresh - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to temporarily pause policy enforcement on Windows 11 devices using Intune's Pause Config Refresh remote action to support troubleshooting and manual changes.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/pause-config-refresh</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remote Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the remote lock action in Microsoft Intune to lock a managed device that has a passcode or PIN.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remote-lock</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Rename Device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Rename device remote action in Microsoft Intune to update the device name shown in the admin center. Useful for standardizing naming conventions, managing shared devices, and improving inventory clarity.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rename</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Autopilot Reset - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Autopilot reset with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-autopilot-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Fresh Start - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Fresh Start to remove or uninstall apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-fresh-start</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Restart - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to restart managed devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-restart</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, or create settings on iOS/iPadOS devices to restrict features in Microsoft Intune. Create password requirements, control the locked screen, use built-in apps, add restricted or approved apps, handle bluetooth devices, connect to the cloud for backup and storage, enable kiosk mode, add domains, and control how users interact with the Safari web browser.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune enrollment for Android Enterprise dedicated devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure enrollment in Microsoft Intune for Android Enterprise dedicated devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-kiosk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Microsoft Intune licenses - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Assign licenses to users so they can enroll in Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/licenses-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add users to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add and managing Microsoft Entra user accounts from within Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/users-add</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to Assist Users Authenticated by your Organization - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Cloud PKI for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>An overview of the Microsoft Cloud PKI service, available with Microsoft Intune Suite or as an Intune add-on.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Query in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device query in Microsoft Intune to get on-demand device state, run Kusto Query Language (KQL) queries, and troubleshoot devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/device-query</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover what Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics is, how it extends endpoint analytics with advanced device insights, proactive troubleshooting, and enhanced reporting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/advanced-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>ServiceNow integration enables help desk staff, who are licensed to use Remote Help, to use ServiceNow to view incidents and details of the tech issue that an employee is facing from the Troubleshooting pane. This article also describes how to configure ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/service-now-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan for Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the requirements and capabilities of Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Elevation Settings for Endpoint Privilege Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View guidance on how to manage the Endpoint Privilege Management client, including reporting level and default elevation response.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-elevation-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Cloud PKI root and issuing CA for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure a root and issuing CA for the Microsoft Cloud PKI service.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-configure-ca</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment models for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the deployment options for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-deployment</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android FOTA Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates on Android devices. A FOTA update can include software and security patches, feature updates, and other changes to the device's firmware.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/fota-updates-android</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring your own certificate authority with Cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a Microsoft Cloud PKI BYOCA issuing CA in Intune and anchor it to an on-premises or private CA.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-configure-byoca</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for deploying Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune cloud PKI fundamentals - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes fundamentals for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-fundamentals</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrator to standard user - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for using Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrators to standard users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-transition-administrator-to-standard-user</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how anomaly detection in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics proactively monitors device health, detects issues, and provides actionable insights for IT admins.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/anomaly-detection</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>