<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:41:49 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:41:49 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Create assignment filters in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create assignment filters in Microsoft Intune to target policies based on device properties like OS version or manufacturer. Learn to create, update, and delete filters for managed devices and apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up account driven Apple User Enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up account driven Apple User Enrollment for personal devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-account-driven-user-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Apps to Groups in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign an Intune app to groups of users or devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared iPad devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Shared iPad devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-shared-ipad</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to manage software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Wi-Fi profile for devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the steps to create a Wi-Fi device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Create profiles for Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, Android kiosk, iOS, iPadOS, macOS, Windows 10/11, and Windows Holographic for Business. Use these profiles to create a WiFi connection to use certificates, choose an EAP type, select an authentication method, enable a proxy, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single sign-on (SSO) for iOS/iPadOS and macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of Microsoft Enterprise SSO plug-in in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers. The Enterprise SSO plug-in is available on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-ios-ipados-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Web Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding web apps (client-server applications) to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/web-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict devices features using policy in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a device configuration profile to restrict features on Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, AOSP, macOS, iOS, iPadOS, and Windows 10/11 client devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple device enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple device enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-device-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add VPN settings to devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>On Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, macOS, and Windows devices, use built-in settings to create virtual private network (VPN) connections in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared iOS and iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Shared iOS and iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-shared-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up per-app VPN for iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the prerequisites, create a group for the virtual private network (VPN) users, add a SCEP certificate profile, configure a per-app VPN profile, and assign some apps to the VPN profile in Microsoft Intune on iOS/iPadOS devices. Also lists the steps to verify the VPN connection on the device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-setting-configure-per-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiosk settings for Windows and Holographic devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your Windows 10/11 and Windows Holographic for Business devices as single-app and multi-app kiosks, customize the start menu, add apps, show the task bar, and configure a web browser in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kiosk-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up user enrollment with Company Portal for iOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up the profile based Apple User Enrollment option for personal devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-user-enrollment-with-company-portal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use custom device settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a profile to use custom settings for Windows 10/11 client, Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, macOS, and iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create iOS/iPadOS or macOS device profile with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create an iOS, iPadOS, or macOS device profile. Configure settings for AirPrint, layout of the home screen, app notifications, shared device, single sign-on, and web content filter settings in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-features-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use derived credentials for mobile devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a third-party partners derived credential as an authentication method for Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/derived-credentials</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security, email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4 to deploy device configuration profiles as part of the minimum set of policies for your devices using Microsoft Intune. The starting point is to enable the firewall, install AV, scan for malware, install software updates, create a strong PIN policy, and create email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-configuration-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with iOS/iPadOS frontline worker devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage frontline worker devices using iOS and iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune. Select the best enrollment option, configure the home screen, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/frontline-worker/frontline-worker-overview-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to Apple devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Export iOS, iPadOS, and macOS settings from Apple Configurator or Apple Profile Manager tools, and then import these settings into Microsoft Intune. These settings can create, use, and control custom settings and features on iOS, iPadOS, and macOS devices. This custom profile can then be assigned or distributed to iOS, iPadOS, and macOS devices in your organization to create a baseline or standard.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-apple</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Install and configure Microsoft Tunnel Gateway on a Linux server to support Intune managed cloud-based devices in connecting to your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure WiFi settings for Apple devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a Wi-Fi configuration profile on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices using Wi-Fi configuration settings in Microsoft Intune. Configure the connection details, authentication methods, SSIDs, security types, and proxy settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-settings-apple</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings insight - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Settings insight provides peer benchmarking information during security baseline configuration, showing when organizations similar to yours use Microsoft's recommended default values.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/settings-insight</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-supervised-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple User Enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple User Enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-user-enrollment-supported-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure VPN settings for Apple devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a VPN configuration profile on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices using virtual private network (VPN) configuration settings in Microsoft Intune. Configure the connection details, authentication methods, split tunneling, custom VPN settings with the identifier, key and value pairs, per-app VPN settings that include Safari URLs, and on-demand VPNs with SSIDs or DNS search domains, proxy settings to include a configuration script, IP or FQDN address, and TCP port.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-apple</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign device profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to assign device configuration profiles and policies to users and devices. Learn how to exclude groups from a profile assignment in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about managing devices, apps, and security with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Update Policies for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure software update policies for Apple devices using Apple's Declarative Device Management (DDM) model. Improve security, reduce user disruption, and ensure compliance with reliable, automated updates across your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get support in the Microsoft Intune admin center - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get online and telephone support for Microsoft Intune and other device management cloud services from within the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/get-support</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add, Configure, and Protect Apps with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-protect-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help Desk Troubleshooting Dashboard - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Help desk staff use the troubleshooting pane to solve users' technical problems.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/help-desk-operators</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Windows Feature Update Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Windows feature update polies and how to manage them in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/feature-update-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect device hardware info with the properties catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the properties catalog in Microsoft Intune view and collect enhanced device hardware info on Windows devices you manage with Intune. You can collect info like BIOS version, TPM status, disk info, memory details, and network adapter configurations. Use this information to get deeper visibility into your device inventory and troubleshoot issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare a Win32 App to Be Uploaded to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to prepare a Win32 app to be uploaded to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-prepare</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign Win32 Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add, assign, and manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-add</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win32 App Management in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune. This article provides an overview of the Intune Win32 app delivery and management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune built-in roles reference - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Permissions reference for built-in roles for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control-reference</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a custom role in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a custom role in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign a role to an Intune administrator - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign a built-in or custom role to a user in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/assign-role</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable use of Windows diagnostic data by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows diagnostic data in processor configuration for your tenant to enable its use by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/data-enable-windows-data</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Windows Update Ring Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Windows Update ring policies for Windows devices, how to create and manage them, and improve update deployment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/update-rings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Windows Feature Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune policies to manage Windows feature updates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/feature-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Compatibility Reports for Windows Updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the app and driver compatibility reports for Windows devices before you deploy Intune policies for feature updates or update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/compatibility-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android FOTA Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates on Android devices. A FOTA update can include software and security patches, feature updates, and other changes to the device's firmware.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/fota-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Rollout Options for Feature Update Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure rollout options in feature update policies to control when Windows feature updates become available to devices and deploy updates gradually.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/rollout-options</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune capabilities that can help you protect your devices and data against unauthorized access and other threats.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-protect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for Android software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for Android devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on corporate owned Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/software-updates-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin guide and checklist for macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updates for macOS devices using Microsoft Intune. Use this article to help manage software updates on your organization-owned devices, including how to create policies, manage updates, and review update status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-guide-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for software updates on BYOD in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for BYOD and personally owned devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on personal devices on Android and iOS/iPadOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/byod-software-updates-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Windows quality updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Windows quality updates in Microsoft Intune using quality update policies, expedited updates, and hotpatch to keep devices secure and compliant.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/quality-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To support hybrid and remote workers, convert or migrate your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints. This planning guide focuses on deploying apps and updates with Intune, moving from Group Policy Objects, and using Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-endpoints-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent to Manage Vulnerabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify, prioritize, and remediate security vulnerabilities across your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/vulnerability-remediation-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows cloud configuration step by step guide - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use this Windows 10/11 cloud configuration step-by-step setup guide to create your own cloud configuration deployment. You create the Microsoft Entra group and policies using Microsoft Intune, including the enrollment profile, compliance policy, and security baseline. You also deploy apps and resources that users need to do their jobs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/cloud-configuration-setup-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Rings Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference article that lists all the settings for Windows Update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/update-ring-policy-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View Software Update Reports for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Track Apple device update status in real time with Intune's declarative software update reporting. Learn how Microsoft Intune surfaces update changes directly from managed Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Update Management Overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Windows updates with Intune. Control update settings, define rollout strategies, and ensure consistent device security across your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports for Windows Feature Update Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the reports available for Windows feature update policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/feature-updates-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expedite Policies for Windows Quality Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use expedite policies in Microsoft Intune to quickly deploy a specific Windows security update, bypass deferrals, and monitor installation status across devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/expedite-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Windows Driver Update Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create, approve, deploy, and pause Windows driver updates using Intune policies to keep Windows devices current and stable.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/driver-update-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Windows Driver Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Windows driver updates using Intune driver update policies to keep Windows devices current and stable.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/driver-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Update Errors and Descriptions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference article with a list of the Software Update agent error code in Microsoft Intune, including the symbolic name and error description.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/software-update-agent-error-codes</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Holographic devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and complete different tasks on devices running Windows Holographic for Business and HoloLens. You can configure the Company Portal app, create a compliance policy, customize OMA-URI settings, deploy apps, categorize devices in groups, create profiles, restrict devices, enable software updates, set terms and conditions, configure VPN and Wi-Fi settings, and use Hello for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-holographic-for-business</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Hotpatch With Windows Quality Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how hotpatch works with Windows quality update policies in Microsoft Intune to install eligible security updates without requiring an immediate device restart.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/hotpatch</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports for Windows Quality Update Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the reports available for Windows quality update policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/quality-updates-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports for Windows Driver Update Policies reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune reports to monitor Windows driver updates for devices assigned to Windows Driver update policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/driver-updates-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade Devices to Windows 11 Using Feature Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to upgrade Windows 10 devices to Windows 11 using feature updates in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/feature-updates-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions About Windows Driver Update Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides answers to some frequently asked questions about Windows Driver Update Policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/driver-updates-faq</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports for Windows Update Ring Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the reports available for Windows update ring policies in Intune. Discover how to access and interpret these reports to monitor update deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/update-rings-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Service Description - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a cloud-based service that helps you manage Windows, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/microsoft-intune-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zebra LifeGuard Over-the-Air Integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates for supported Zebra devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/zebra-lifeguard-ota-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom settings - Windows Holographic for Business devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a custom profile to use the OMA-URI settings for devices running Windows Holographic for Business in Microsoft Intune, including Microsoft HoloLens. You can set AllowFastReconnect, AllowVPN, AllowUpdateService, UpdateServiceURL, RequireUpdatesApproval, ApprovedUpdates, and ApplicationLaunchRestrictions policy configuration service provider (CSP) settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-windows-holographic</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operating systems and browsers supported by Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Lists supported device platforms and browsers for Intune device management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/supported-devices-browsers</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration guide to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deployment guide to set up, onboard, or move to Intune. These steps include moving from partner MDM providers, using co-management, moving from on-premises group policy, and moving from Office 365 device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-intune-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See an overview of the steps to start using Intune. Plan your move and deployment of Intune, determine your licensing needs and any platform requirements, use compliance and Conditional Access, deploy apps, create device configuration profiles, and enroll your devices to be managed. Get more information on mobile application management for BYOD or personal devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/get-started-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is device management? - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about what device management means and how it can help organizations, including Microsoft 365 small &amp; medium business, and enterprise. See a list of features and benefits, including mobile device management (MDM) and mobile application management (MAM), and learn about Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-device-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View device details with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View your device details, including operating systems, storage space, manufacturer, and model. Get a list of installed apps, check compliance policies, and set up TeamViewer with Microsoft Intune in Azure. Similar to viewing inventory of the devices you manage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-inventory</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Windows virtual machines with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the general guidelines for using Windows 10/11 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-10-virtual-machines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add users to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add and managing Microsoft Entra user accounts from within Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/users-add</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Linux device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Linux device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune servicing information and details - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the frequency of the Microsoft Intune service updates, the release cadence, and how to check your tenant release version.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-service-servicing-information</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>