<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:28:50 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:28:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 22:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Collect Diagnostics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Intune security baselines for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that have preset and recommended configurations to the Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Find lost devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Locate lost or stolen devices by using the locate device feature in Microsoft Intune. Get details on security and privacy information when using the locate device action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-locate</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt macOS FileVault disk encryption with Intune policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to configure FileVault on macOS devices, and use the admin center to manage their recovery keys.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Disable Activation Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune to disable Activation Lock on Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-activation-lock-disable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Defender for Endpoint in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/advanced-threat-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Reset Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to reset a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-passcode-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Sync - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the device sync remote action in Intune to apply policy, app, and configuration updates to managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Send Custom Notifications - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenarios for using Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Conditional Access is commonly used with Intune compliance policy for devices and apps</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-intune-common-ways-use</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View report details for encryption status of devices managed with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to view reports for device encryption status across macOS FileVault and Windows BitLocker encrypted devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encryption-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune capabilities that can help you protect your devices and data against unauthorized access and other threats.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-protect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Lost Mode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enable Lost Mode in Microsoft Intune to remotely lock a lost or stolen iOS or iPadOS device and display a custom message and phone number on the lock screen.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-lost-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Update Cellular Data Plan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to update the cellular data plan for iOS/iPadOS devices that support eSIM with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/update-cellular-data-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor security baselines deployed by Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor device and per-setting results of security baselines you deploy with Microsoft Intune, and identify conflicts for devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove User - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a user from a Shared iPad with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Logout current user - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the logout the current user from a Shared iPad with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-logout-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Shutdown - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to shutdown Apple devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-shutdown</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Wipe - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wipe, or factory reset, devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt Windows devices with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to manage encryption of Windows devices with either BitLocker or Personal Data Encryption.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard and Configure Devices with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint via Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune, including connecting the products, onboarding devices, and assigning policies for compliance and risk level assessment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/advanced-threat-protection-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Quick Scan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand Microsoft Defender quick scan with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-quick-scan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: BitLocker Key Rotation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the BitLocker recovery key with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-bitlocker-keys</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Actions – Wipe, Lock, Locate, and More - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how to use Microsoft Intune to remotely manage, wipe, lock, restart, and secure Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, Windows, and ChromeOS devices. Learn about available remote actions, prerequisites, and bulk actions for IT admins.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Run Remediation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand remediations with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-run-remediation</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Apps and Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how apps and configurations can be removed temporarily, then restored automatically or manually using the Remove apps and configuration device action with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/remove-apps-config</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint detection and response policy. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security endpoint detection and response policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-edr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage devices with endpoint security in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security node to view devices and manage them in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-manage-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrator to standard user - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for using Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrators to standard users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-transition-administrator-to-standard-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Intune policies to configure and manage Windows LAPS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create policies to manage the Windows Local Administrator Policy Solution (LAPS) on Windows devices that enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-laps-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Remote Action: Rotate FileVault Recovery Key - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the FileVault recovery key with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-passcode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Delete - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to delete devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: New Remote Assistance Session - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the the new remote assistance session action in Intune to offer support to your users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remote-assist</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Retire - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to retire device using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-retire</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Rotate local admin password - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the local admin password on Windows and macOS devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-local-admin-password</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Pause Config Refresh - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to temporarily pause policy enforcement on Windows 11 devices using Intune's Pause Config Refresh remote action to support troubleshooting and manual changes.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/pause-config-refresh</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Play Lost Mode Sound - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Play lost device sound remote action in Microsoft Intune to trigger an audible alert on a lost, stolen, or misplaced device—helping users locate it quickly and securely.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-play-lost-mode-sound</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage account protection settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune endpoint security account protection policies to protect the identity and accounts of users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security baseline policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that establish a default and recommended security postures on Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remote Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the remote lock action in Microsoft Intune to lock a managed device that has a passcode or PIN.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remote-lock</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Rename Device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Rename device remote action in Microsoft Intune to update the device name shown in the admin center. Useful for standardizing naming conventions, managing shared devices, and improving inventory clarity.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rename</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to configure the Intune Company Portal apps, Company Portal website, and Intune app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can configure the Intune Company Portal apps, Company Portal website, and Intune app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Full Scan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand Microsoft Defender full scan with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-full-scan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Remote Action: Deprovision - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to deprovision a chromeOS device with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-deprovision</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To enhance the security of your organization, set your users to run with standard permissions while Endpoint Privilege Management ensures those users can seamlessly run specified files with elevated rights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use reusable groups of settings policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage groups of settings for Intune profiles as a single object and then add that settings group object to multiple profile instances. Later changes you make to the settings groups  automatically apply to each profile that includes the reusable settings group.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/reusable-settings-groups</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Windows LAPS with Microsoft Intune policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune application protection policy to manage the local administrator accounts on Windows devices. Through the Windows LAPS CSP, back up accounts and passwords to Microsoft Entra ID, define password requirements, and protect account passwords through scheduled password rotations and manual rotations at need.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-laps-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Autopilot Reset - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Autopilot reset with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-autopilot-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Fresh Start - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Fresh Start to remove or uninstall apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-fresh-start</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Restart - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to restart managed devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-restart</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage attack surface reduction settings with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security attack surface reduction policy settings in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-asr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune endpoint security disk encryption policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy Microsoft Intune endpoint security policy disk encryption policies for BitLocker and FileVault.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-disk-encryption-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security policies and profiles to focus on security configuration of devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan and Prepare for Endpoint Privilege Management Deployment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan your Endpoint Privilege Management deploying by understanding requirements, fundamentals, and security recommendations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about Microsoft Intune's unified endpoint management and security solutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policies overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect Intune account to managed Google Play account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect your Intune account to your Managed Google Play account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/connect-intune-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS direct enrollment - Apple Configurator-Setup Assistant - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Apple Configurator to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices with Setup Assistant.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-configurator-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure compliance policies with actions for noncompliance in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your compliance policies with one or more actions for noncompliance to protect devices and your organization from unprotected devices. Actions can remotely lock devices, send email or notifications to device users, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/actions-for-noncompliance</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android (AOSP) device management in Intune for corporate-owned userless devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for corporate-owned userless devices built on the Android Open Source Project (AOSP) platform.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-aosp-corporate-owned-userless-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage and secure devices overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get an overview of the concepts and features you should know when managing devices that access organization resources in Microsoft Intune. You can manage new and existing devices, including BYOD personal devices, check health compliance and view reports, configure device features, and secure devices using mobile threat solutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/manage-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device query in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to gain on-demand information about the state of your devices using device query.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/device-query</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android (AOSP) device management in Intune for corporate-owned user-associated devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for corporate-owned user-associated devices built on the Android Open Source Project (AOSP) platform.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-aosp-corporate-owned-user-associated-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll personal devices in Intune with Android Enterprise work profile management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for personal devices and bring-your-own-device scenarios using Android Enterprise work profile management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-work-profile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Windows virtual machines with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the general guidelines for using Windows 10/11 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-10-virtual-machines</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use direct enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy and enroll macOS devices in Microsoft Intune using direct enrollment with Apple Configurator.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-direct-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work from anywhere report in Endpoint analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Work from anywhere report in Endpoint analytics provides insights to help your end users be productive from anywhere.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/work-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Multi Admin Approval in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Multi Admin Approval to protect your tenant against the use of compromised administrative accounts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/multi-admin-approval</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remove SCEP or PKCS certificates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the actions that can remove, revoke, or leave untouched the certificates on a device that were provisioned by Intune certificate profiles. Actions include tasks to wipe or retire a managed device, to unenroll a device, manage the certificate profile assignment, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/remove-certificates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Windows BIOS features using DFCI MDM policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Device Firmware Configuration Interface (DFCI) profile to manage UEFI settings in Microsoft Intune. To use DFCI profiles, create Microsoft Entra security groups, the Windows Autopilot deployment profile, and the Enrollment State Page profile.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-firmware-configuration-interface-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for software updates on BYOD in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for BYOD and personally owned devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on personal devices on Android and iOS/iPadOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-personal-byod</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Apple device management in Intune for corporate-owned userless devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for corporate-owned userless iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-corporate-owned-userless-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move from Android device administrator to mobile application management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to set up mobile application management, an alternative option to Android device administrator that focuses on app protection and doesn't require device enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/move-to-android-mobile-application-management</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Holographic devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and complete different tasks on devices running Windows Holographic for Business and HoloLens. You can configure the Company Portal app, create a compliance policy, customize OMA-URI settings, deploy apps, categorize devices in groups, create profiles, restrict devices, enable software updates, set terms and conditions, configure VPN and Wi-Fi settings, and use Hello for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-holographic-for-business</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable eSIM data connections in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or use eSIM to get internet and data access using different data plans. In Intune, add or import activation codes, and then assign these activation codes using a configuration profile. You can also monitor the eSIM profiles and check the status of the eSIM-enabled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/esim-device-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically remove devices with cleanup rules - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune's device cleanup rules offer a simple, automated way to ensure that only actively managed devices remain visible in the admin center. Learn more about device cleanup rules and how to configure them.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-cleanup-rules</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View device details with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View your device details, including operating systems, storage space, manufacturer, and model. Get a list of installed apps, check compliance policies, and set up TeamViewer with Microsoft Intune in Azure. Similar to viewing inventory of the devices you manage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-inventory</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to improve your security posture with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-configure-security</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints</title>
      <description>To support hybrid and remote workers, convert or migrate your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints. This planning guide focuses on deploying apps and updates with Intune, moving from Group Policy Objects, and using Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-endpoints-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop-multi-session</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the Microsoft Intune MDM lifecycle - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Intune helps you manage devices through their lifecycle - from enrollment, through configuration, to eventual retirement.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-lifecycle</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions about MAM and app protection - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides answers to some frequently asked questions on Intune mobile application management (MAM) and Intune app protection.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mam-faq</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device query for multiple devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how device query for multiple devices allows you to gain comprehensive insights about all your devices using Kusto Query Language (KQL).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/device-query-multiple-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>