<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:19:54 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:19:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Administrative templates in Microsoft Intune to create groups of settings for Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a device configuration profile. You can control Office programs, Microsoft Edge, access OneDrive, use remote desktop, enable Auto-Play, set power management settings, use HTTP printing, control user sign-in, and change the event log size.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict USB devices using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to restrict USB devices, including thumb drives, flash drives, USB cameras, and more. Use other settings to allow specific USB devices on Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-restrict-usb</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Universal Print policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to create a Universal Print policy for Windows 10/11 client devices. The policy automatically installs printers on your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-printer-provisioning</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Defender for Endpoint in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/advanced-threat-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common tasks and features in the settings catalog</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure common features. You can create a Universal Print policy, configure Microsoft Edge and Google Chrome web browsers, and use built in settings instead of plist files for macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-common-features</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Microsoft 365 apps with the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to update Microsoft 365 apps to the latest version, and choose how frequently Office checks for updates. See the device registry keys that are updated when an Intune policy to Office update is applied.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-update-office</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Microsoft Edge policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create settings using the settings catalog to configure Microsoft Edge on Windows and macOS devices. Using Microsoft Intune, you can configure group policy settings, and deploy these settings to Microsoft Edge users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-configure-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run remote actions on devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to run remote actions on Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Windows devices. You can reset the password, lock the device, wipe or reset the OS, scan for viruses, and more. Use this feature to remotely manage devices and have help desk run common tasks.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data storage and processing in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how personal data is stored and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-store-process</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remotely administer devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the required roles to use TeamViewer, how to install the TeamViewer connector, and step-by-step guidance to remotely administer devices using Microsoft Intune in the Azure portal</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/teamviewer-support</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune manages users and devices, simplifies app management and automated policy deployment, and integrates with mobile threat defense. It connects to Managed Google Play, Apple tokens and certificates, and Teamviewer for remote assistance. Can use MDM or MAM to protect data, configure devices, and simplify access to company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third-party device compliance partners support in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a third-party device compliance partner as a source of compliance data for devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-compliance-partners</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune contributes to a strong Zero Trust strategy and architecture.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/zero-trust-with-microsoft-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-managed-home-screen-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device restriction settings for Android in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>On Android Enterprise or Android for Work devices owned by your organization, you can restrict settings on the device using Microsoft Intune. Allow copy and paste, notifications, app permissions, data sharing, password length, sign in failures, use fingerprint to unlock, reuse passwords, and enable bluetooth sharing of work contacts. Configure devices as a dedicated device kiosk to run one app, or multiple apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android with Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sync devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Synchronize devices that are registered or managed with Microsoft Intune to get the latest policies and actions. Includes the steps to sync by using the Azure portal, and lists the error codes that can be retried.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure ChromeOS connector for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect the Google Admin Console to Microsoft Intune so that you can view and take action on enrolled ChromeOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/chrome-enterprise-connector-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View and correct personal data collected by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to view and correct personal data that's been collected by Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-view-correct</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View device details with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View your device details, including operating systems, storage space, manufacturer, and model. Get a list of installed apps, check compliance policies, and set up TeamViewer with Microsoft Intune in Azure. Similar to viewing inventory of the devices you manage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-inventory</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage devices with endpoint security in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security node to view devices and manage them in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-manage-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find the primary user of a Microsoft Intune device.</title>
      <description>Find the primary user (or User Device Affinity) of an Intune device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/find-primary-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View ChromeOS device information</title>
      <description>View ChromeOS devices and details synced with the Chrome Enterprise connector in the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/chrome-enterprise-device-details</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rename a device with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Rename a device by using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rename</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 02:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO and deploy the configuration to your macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using Microsoft Entra ID with the Secure Enclave, smart card, or password authentication methods. You create a settings catalog policy to configure the settings. This article is a step-by-step guide to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platform SSO scenarios for macOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure common Platform SSO scenarios for macOS devices. You can enable Kerberos SSO to on-premises Active Directory and cloud-based Microsoft Entra ID, use Touch ID biometric policy with Secure Enclave authentication, and enable SSO on non-Microsoft apps. You can also configure end user experience settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-scenarios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiosk settings for Windows 10/11 in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your Windows 10/11 client devices as single-app and multi-app kiosks, customize the start menu, add apps, show the task bar, and configure a web browser in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kiosk-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device restriction settings for Windows 10/11 in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings and their descriptions for creating device restrictions on Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a configuration profile to control screenshots, password requirements, kiosk settings, apps in the store, Microsoft Edge browser, Microsoft Defender, access to the cloud, start menu, and more in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walkthrough-Create a settings catalog policy</title>
      <description>This tutorial or walkthrough steps through creating and comparing an on-premises Administrative Templates (ADMX) Group Policy and Microsoft Intune cloud-based settings catalog policy. It shows similar settings in on-premises and the Intune settings catalog to create and manage policies for Office, Windows, and Microsoft Edge on Windows 10/11 client devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/tutorial-settings-catalog-group-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure and secure devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure policies with Microsoft Intune in preparation for device deployment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/configure-device-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 02:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure feature updates policy for Windows 10 Windows 11 devices in Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows feature updates. Configure and deploy policy to maintain the Windows feature version of Windows 10/11 devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-10-feature-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows Backup for Organizations in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows backup and restore in Intune for employees or students.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-backup-restore</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View declarative device management-based software update reports for Apple devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to software updates reports for managed Apple devices based on Apples declarative device management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-reports-apple-declarative-based</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune enrollment for Android Enterprise dedicated devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure enrollment in Microsoft Intune for Android Enterprise dedicated devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-kiosk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll personal devices in Intune with Android Enterprise work profile management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for personal devices and bring-your-own-device scenarios using Android Enterprise work profile management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-work-profile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android Enterprise work profile for corporate owned devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Android Enterprise work profile for corporate-owned devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-corporate-owned-work-profile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment for Android Enterprise fully managed devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up enrollment in Intune for devices using the Android Enterprise fully managed device management solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to assist users authenticated by your organization.</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance recommendations when using filters</title>
      <description>When using filters in Microsoft Intune, use Intune virtual groups that don't require Microsoft Entra ID syncing. To improve performance, reuse groups, make incremental group changes, and use filters to include and exclude.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-performance-recommendations</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags for distributed IT - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags to filter configuration profiles to specific roles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/scope-tags</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared iOS and iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Shared iOS and iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-shared-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment time grouping - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview and setup of the enrollment time grouping feature in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-time-grouping</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add users to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add and managing Microsoft Entra user accounts from within Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/users-add</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set the mobile device management authority - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to set the mobile device management authority in Microsoft Intune and some key considerations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/mdm-authority-set</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1 for deploying or setting up Intune. The starting point is to review supported configurations, sign up for the trial, configure the custom domain name, add users and groups to Intune, assign licenses to users, manage roles, grant admin permissions, and set the MDM authority.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add groups to organize users and devices for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Microsoft Entra groups to organize users and devices for use with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/groups-add</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell scripts for Remediations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>PowerShell script reference for Remediations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/powershell-scripts-remediation</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Windows 10 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the general guidelines for using Windows 10 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-10-virtual-machines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlicensed admins in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to give unlicensed admins permissions to access Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/unlicensed-admins</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a user in Intune</title>
      <description>Create a user in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure a custom domain name - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a custom domain name for your Microsoft Intune subscription</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/custom-domain-name-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to detect and fix support issues</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Delivery Optimization settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure device configuration policy to manage Delivery Optimization settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/delivery-optimization-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operating systems and browsers supported by Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Lists supported device platforms and browsers for Intune device management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/supported-devices-browsers</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Microsoft Intune licenses</title>
      <description>Assign licenses to users so they can enroll in Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/licenses-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Open Source Project Supported Devices</title>
      <description>Lists Android open source project devices (AOSP) supported devices</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/android-os-project-supported-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the Microsoft Intune MDM lifecycle</title>
      <description>Learn how Intune helps you manage devices through their lifecycle - from enrollment, through configuration, to eventual retirement.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-lifecycle</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune classic groups in the Azure portal - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn what's new with groups in the Microsoft Intune Azure portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/groups-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop-multi-session</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the Microsoft Intune tenant status page - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune tenant status page displays details about your tenant and the status of connectors you've configured, and messages intended for tenants and about the Intune service health.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/tenant-status</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Licenses available for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune is available with these licenses</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/licenses</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up or sign in to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to sign up for a Microsoft Intune subscription or sign in to start with your subscription.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/account-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Cloud PKI for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>An overview of the Microsoft Cloud PKI service, available with Microsoft Intune Suite or as an Intune add-on.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to install and configure the unified Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune, which supports SCEP, PKCS, imported PKCS, and certificate revocation.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-install</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune - Azure</title>
      <description>Learn about the unified Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune, which supports SCEP, PKCS, imported PKCS, and certificate revocation.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Types of certificate that are supported by Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Microsoft Intune's support for Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP), Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create trusted certificate profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and deploy trusted certificate profiles to deploy a trusted root certificate to managed devices in Intune. Trusted certificate profiles support use of Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) and Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-trusted-root</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites for the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the software and network prerequisites for use of the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Cloud PKI root and issuing CA for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure a root and issuing CA for the Microsoft Cloud PKI service.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-configure-ca</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment models for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the deployment options for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-deployment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring your own certificate authority with Cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a Microsoft Cloud PKI BYOCA issuing CA in Intune and anchor it to an on-premises or private CA.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-configure-byoca</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune cloud PKI fundamentals - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes fundamentals for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-fundamentals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Issue DigiCert PKCS certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Install and configure the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune to issue PKCS certificates from DigiCert PKI Platform to Intune-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-digicert-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor issued PKI certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor reports for certificates issued via Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delete issued PKI certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Delete certificates issued via Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote actions for ChromeOS devices</title>
      <description>Remotely run Microsoft Intune device actions on ChromeOS devices in the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/chrome-enterprise-remote-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use imported PFX certificates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use imported Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificates with Microsoft Intune. Import certificates, configure certificate templates, and create an Imported PKCS Certificate profile.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-imported-pfx-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit logs for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get audit logs for Microsoft cloud public key infrastructure (PKI) activity in the admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-audit-logs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use a PKCS certificate profile to provision devices with certificates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificates with Microsoft Intune, work with root certificates and certificate templates, and use device configuration profiles for a PKCS Certificate.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-pfx-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign and encrypt email using S/MIME - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use email digital certificates in Microsoft Intune to sign and encrypt emails on devices. These certificates are called S/MIME and are configured using device configuration profiles. Signing and encryption certificates use PKCS, or private certificates, and use a connector to import certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-s-mime-encryption-sign</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure infrastructure to support SCEP certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To use Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) with Microsoft Intune, configure your on-premises AD domain, create a certification authority, and set up the NDES server to support use of the Certificate Connector.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-scep-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use third-party certification authorities (CA) with SCEP in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, you can add a vendor or third-party certificate authority (CA) to issue certificates to mobile devices using the SCEP protocol. In this overview, a Microsoft Entra application gives Microsoft Intune permissions to validate certificates. Then, use the application ID, authentication key, and tenant ID of the Microsoft Entra application in the setup of your SCEP server to issue certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-authority-add-scep-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-supervised-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use SCEP certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and assign Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-profile-scep</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Windows devices using Automatic enrollment, Windows Autopilot, group policy, and co-management enrollment options in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>