<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:19:38 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:19:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign device profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to assign device configuration profiles and policies to users and devices. Learn how to exclude groups from a profile assignment in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Administrative templates in Microsoft Intune to create groups of settings for Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a device configuration profile. You can control Office programs, Microsoft Edge, access OneDrive, use remote desktop, enable Auto-Play, set power management settings, use HTTP printing, control user sign-in, and change the event log size.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or configure a device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Select the platform type, configure the settings, and add a scope tag. Learn more about applicability rules, and the policy refresh cycle times.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-create</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See device configuration policies with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See and manage the device configuration policy details in Microsoft Intune. Look at a graphical chart of the number of devices assigned to a policy, and see which devices have policies assigned or deployed. Can also troubleshoot policies that have conflict settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can use Security Copilot to get information about your Intune data, including devices, apps, policies, and groups managed in Intune. You can also compare policies, get device specific details, and get target info for policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for US government deployments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the list of US government endpoint URLs that Intune needs and requires. Allow the ports, IP addresses, and endpoint URLs in your proxy server configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-us-government-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Copilot in Intune features overview</title>
      <description>Microsoft Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Intune data with natural language and take action</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, use Explorer to query your data in natural language and run built-in queries that match your request. Copilot summarizes the results, and provides recommendations and actions based on the query results. You can also create policies that target users and groups in the query results. Use this feature to explore your Intune data, troubleshoot issues, and create custom reports.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-explorer</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions with policies and profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Common questions, answers, and scenarios with device policies and profiles in Microsoft Intune. Learn more about profile changes not applying to users or devices, how long it takes for new policies to deploy, which settings apply when there are conflicts, what happens when you delete or remove a profile, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot-agents-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to set up and use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent for Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/vulnerability-remediation-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Microsoft Surface Management Portal</title>
      <description>You can use Security Copilot to help you manage and monitor Surface devices at scale.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot-surface-portal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copilot in Intune shows device information and errors</title>
      <description>Microsoft Copilot in Intune can help you get information about your devices, compare devices, and get error information. Use this information to help you manage and troubleshoot device issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copilot in Intune FAQ</title>
      <description>Get answers to common questions when using Copilot in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-faq</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to detect and fix support issues</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 17:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Android, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows devices in Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1 for deploying or setting up Intune. The starting point is to review supported configurations, sign up for the trial, configure the custom domain name, add users and groups to Intune, assign licenses to users, manage roles, grant admin permissions, and set the MDM authority.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to install and configure the unified Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune, which supports SCEP, PKCS, imported PKCS, and certificate revocation.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-install</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites for the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the software and network prerequisites for use of the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automatic enrollment in Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment of Windows 10/11 devices that join or register with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/quickstart-setup-auto-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign an app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to add and assign an app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-add-assign-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send notifications to noncompliant devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this topic, you use Microsoft Intune to send email notifications to noncompliant devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/quickstart-send-notification</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluate and try - Enroll a device</title>
      <description>In this evaluation task, enroll a device running Windows 10/11 into Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/quickstart-enroll-windows-device</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a user in Intune</title>
      <description>Create a user in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and assign an app protection policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you use Microsoft Intune to create and assign and app protection policy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-create-assign-app-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create an email device profile for iOS/iPadOS devices</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune to create an email device profile so iOS/iPadOS devices can securely connect to company organization email.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/quickstart-email-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and assign a custom role in Intune</title>
      <description>Create and assign a custom role for a remote device manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Configure Slack to use Intune for EMM and app configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this tutorial you will configure Slack to use Intune for EMM and app configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/tutorial-configure-slack-enterprise-grid</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a group to manage users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to create a group based on existing users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-group</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password compliance policy for Android Enterprise devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this topic, you will use Microsoft Intune to set the length of the password required for Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/quickstart-set-password-length-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure infrastructure to support SCEP certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To use Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) with Microsoft Intune, configure your on-premises AD domain, create a certification authority, and set up the NDES server to support use of the Certificate Connector.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-scep-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually configure Jamf Pro integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manually configure Jamf Pro integration with Intune when you can't use the Jamf Cloud Connector.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-integrate-jamf</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up BlackBerry Protect with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the CylancePROTECT (BlackBerry) MTD solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/blackberry-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>ServiceNow integration enables help desk staff, who are licensed to use Remote Help, to use ServiceNow to view incidents and details of the tech issue that an employee is facing from the Troubleshooting pane. This article also describes how to configure ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/service-now-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlicensed admins in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to give unlicensed admins permissions to access Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/unlicensed-admins</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use multiple administrative approvals in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure multi-admin approval to protect your tenant against the use of compromised administrative accounts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/multi-admin-approval</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags for distributed IT - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags to filter configuration profiles to specific roles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/scope-tags</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a custom role in Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a custom role in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the Microsoft Intune tenant status page - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune tenant status page displays details about your tenant and the status of connectors you've configured, and messages intended for tenants and about the Intune service health.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/tenant-status</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings insight</title>
      <description>The Settings insight feature adds insights giving you confidence in configurations that are successfully adopted by similar organizations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/settings-insight</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed IT with multiple admins</title>
      <description>Learn about scaling guidelines for Microsoft Intune when you have a large number of local admins who need to manage their own users/devices and policies within the same tenant. Use Microsoft Intune's Role Based Access Control to manage access.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-scale-guidelines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up or sign in to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to sign up for a Microsoft Intune subscription or sign in to start with your subscription.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/account-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-managed-home-screen-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Linux device management</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Linux device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune - Azure</title>
      <description>Learn about the unified Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune, which supports SCEP, PKCS, imported PKCS, and certificate revocation.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage transferring data between iOS apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how to use mobile app management policies in Microsoft Intune to manage data transfers between apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/data-transfer-between-apps-manage-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Microsoft Entra ID to access Intune APIs in Microsoft Graph - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes steps needed for apps to use Microsoft Entra ID to access the Intune APIs in Microsoft Graph.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/intune-graph-apis</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings for Microsoft Defender Antivirus for Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the settings in the Microsoft Defender Antivirus profile for Windows devices. You can configure these settings as part of Endpoint security Antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage volume-purchased iOS/iPadOS eBooks - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync books you purchased in volume from the iOS store with Intune. You can then manage and track usage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-ebooks-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the prerequisites for installation and use of the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. These include Linux servers, network, and firewall configurations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrap iOS apps with the Intune App Wrapping Tool</title>
      <description>Learn how to wrap your iOS apps without changing the code of the app itself. Prepare the apps so you can apply mobile app management policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-wrapper-prepare-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple volume-purchased apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using a Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policies overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect Intune account to managed Google Play account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect your Intune account to your Managed Google Play account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/connect-intune-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App configuration policies for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use app configuration policies on an iOS/iPadOS or Android device in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-protect-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data protection for Windows MAM</title>
      <description>Enable protected MAM access to org data using Windows MAM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/protect-mam-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android with Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android to ensure collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-office</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Intune SDK integration into your iOS app</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Intune SDK integration into your iOS app</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase3</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Application Management (MAM) and Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the available features when deciding to use Mobile Application Management (MAM) and/or Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles for personal or BYOD Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/android-deployment-scenarios-app-protection-work-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Plan the integration</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Plan the integration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-advanced-threat-protection-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review app protection policy logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Get started with MAM</title>
      <description>Get started with Intune before incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase3</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - MAM integration essentials</title>
      <description>Understand MAM integration essentials to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase4</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data storage and processing in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how personal data is stored and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-store-process</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - MSAL prerequisite and setup</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. MSAL prerequisite and setup</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - App participation features</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. App participation features</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase4</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - MSAL Prerequisite</title>
      <description>Understand the MSAL prerequisite to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - App participation features</title>
      <description>Understand App participation features when incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase7</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business</title>
      <description>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-2-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android lets you incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-appendix</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - App Protection CA support (optional)</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. App Protection CA support (optional)</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase6</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Multi-Identity</title>
      <description>Understand Multi-Identity when incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase5</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Multi-Identity</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Multi-Identity</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase5</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense for App Protection Policy</title>
      <description>Step 3. Integrate Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-3-scc</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 6. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business data security</title>
      <description>Step 6. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business corporate data security in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-6-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policy settings for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy (APP) settings for MAM on Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to wipe only corporate data from apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to selectively wipe only corporate data from Intune-managed apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-selective-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Teams for iOS and Android with Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Teams for iOS and Android to ensure team collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-teams</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android with Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data collection in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about personal data collected in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-collect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Appendix</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Appendix</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-appendix</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage device operating system versions with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the methods for managing device operating system versions supported by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/manage-os-versions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure app protection policies for Windows 10/11 - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to configure app protection policies for Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-configure-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>