<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:42:26 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:42:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft 365 Apps to Windows Devices Using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to install Microsoft 365 apps on Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-office365</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Apps to Groups in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign an Intune app to groups of users or devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Configuration Policies for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use app configuration policies on an iOS/iPadOS or Android device in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Win32 Apps in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the most common methods to troubleshoot Win32 app issues with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add a Windows Line-of-Business App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add a Windows line-of-business (LOB) app using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows App Deployment by Using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Windows 10/11 app deployment scenarios available with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-windows-10-app-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Shell Scripts on macOS Devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create, assign, monitor, and troubleshoot shell scripts for macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/macos-shell-scripts</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add App Configuration Policies for Managed Android Enterprise Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use app configuration policies in Microsoft Intune to supply settings when users run a Managed Google Play app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-use-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an Unmanaged macOS PKG App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add an unmanaged macOS PKG app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/macos-unmanaged-pkg</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Include and Exclude App Assignments in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to include and exclude app assignments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-inc-exl-assignments</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add iOS Store Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding iOS store apps to Microsoft Intune. You can assign apps using this method if the apps are free of charge in the App Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policies for Microsoft 365 Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the policies available for Microsoft 365 apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-office-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android to ensure collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-office</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration Policies for Intune App SDK Managed Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure policies for Intune App SDK managed apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-managed-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Android Store Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add Android store apps from the Google Play store to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Microsoft Intune Management Agent for macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Microsoft Intune management agent for macOS.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-macos-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Application Management (MAM) and Android Enterprise Personally-Owned Work Profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the available features when deciding to use Mobile Application Management (MAM) and/or Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles for personal or BYOD Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/android-deployment-scenarios-app-protection-work-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Google Chrome for Android Devices Using Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune configuration policies with Google Chrome for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-configure-chrome-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand App Protection Policy Delivery and Timing - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the different deployment windows for app protection policies to understand when changes should appear on your end user devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-delivery</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS Devices Using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-advanced-threat-protection-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Built-In Apps to Mobile Devices Using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Intune to make it easier to install built-in apps mobile devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-built-in</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure a VPN or Per-App VPN for Android Enterprise Devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use an app configuration policy to add or create a VPN or per-app VPN profile for Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-vpn-ae</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Store Apps to Intune (Legacy) - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Store (legacy) apps to Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Monitor App Protection Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to monitor app protection policies in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Quiet Time Policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create quiet time policies for iOS/iPadOS and Android apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-quiet-time-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apps for GCC High and DoD Environments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about apps involving GCC High and DoD environments using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy-gcc-dod</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Protection Policies for Extensions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes the app protection policy (APP) for extensions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-extensions</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Microsoft 365 Apps to macOS Devices Using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to install Microsoft 365 apps on macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-office365-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Win32 Apps on S Mode Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enable Win32 apps on S mode devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-s-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Update Supersedence for Enterprise App Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to update an Enterprise App Catalog app using supersedence with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-eam-supersedence</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare a Win32 App to Be Uploaded to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to prepare a Win32 app to be uploaded to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-prepare</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Protection Policy Settings for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy (APP) settings for MAM on Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor App Information and Assignments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>After you've assigned an app to users or devices, use this information to help you monitor the app's status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Wipe Only Corporate Data From Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to selectively wipe only corporate data from Intune-managed apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-selective-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Teams for iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Teams for iOS and Android to ensure team collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-teams</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Store Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Store apps to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Intune in Environments Without Google Mobile Services - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune in environments without Google Mobile Services.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-without-gms</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an Enterprise App Catalog App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add an Enterprise App Catalog app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-enterprise-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Android Enterprise System Apps in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Android Enterprise system apps in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-ae-system</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win32 App Management in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune. This article provides an overview of the Intune Win32 app delivery and management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS App Provisioning Profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune gives you the tools to proactively assign a new provisioning profile to devices that have apps that are nearing expiry.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-provisioning-profile-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Windows Update Packages in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to deploy a Windows update package (.msu file) in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-deploy-update-package</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign Win32 Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add, assign, and manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-add</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add apps to Microsoft Intune so you can assign apps to users and devices. Intune supports a wide range of app types.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add App Configuration Policies for Managed iOS/iPadOS Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use app configuration policies to provide configuration data to an iOS/iPadOS app when it's run.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-use-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add a macOS DMG App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a macOS DMG app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-macos-dmg</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Add macOS Line-of-Business Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add macOS line-of-business (LOB) apps to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Protection Framework Using App Protection Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how app protection policies ensure an organization's data remains safe or contained in a managed app, regardless of whether the device is enrolled.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign Managed Google Play Apps to Android Enterprise Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how to synchronize and assign apps to Android Enterprise devices from the Managed Google Play store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add the Company Portal for macOS App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add the macOS Company Portal app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-company-portal-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Launcher for Android Enterprise With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune configuration policies with Microsoft Launcher.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/configure-microsoft-launcher</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is App Management in Microsoft Intune? - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about client app management capabilities by platform for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and Deploy App Protection Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to create and assign Microsoft Intune app protection policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Edge to macOS Devices Using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Edge to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-edge-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Outlook for iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Outlook for iOS and Android to ensure team collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-outlook</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-managed-home-screen-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Configure the Intune Company Portal Apps, Company Portal Website, and Intune App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can configure the Intune Company Portal apps, Company Portal website, and Intune app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Corporate Data Using Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure your corporate data in Microsoft Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the App Lifecycle for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the managed apps lifecycle in Microsoft Intune. The app lifecycle involves adding, deploying, configuring, protecting, and retiring apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-lifecycle</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an Android Line-of-Business App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add a Android line-of-business (LOB) app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an iOS/iPadOS Line-of-Business App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add an iOS/iPadOS line-of-business (LOB) app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Transfer Policy Exceptions for Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create exceptions to the Intune App Protection Policy (APP) data transfer policy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-exception</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wipe Data Using App Protection Policy Conditional Launch Actions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to selectively wipe data using app protection policy conditional launch actions in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-access-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 02:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Reset Protection Emails Not Enforced in Intune for Android - Intune</title>
      <description>Describes an issue in which an Android Enterprise device can be activated by using a Google account that isn't included in the "Factory reset protection emails" setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-configuration/factory-reset-protection-emails-not-enforced</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data protection for Windows MAM - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable protected MAM access to org data using Windows MAM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/protect-mam-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign an app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to add and assign an app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-add-assign-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review app protection policy logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse Collections - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune Data Warehouse collections provide details related to the Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/intune-data-warehouse-collections</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph APIs to configure devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the Graph API entities with the matching Windows CSP and offset URI on Windows 10 devices and newer used when configuring devices in Microsoft Intune. See the matching API and CSP for shared PCs, endpoint protection, Microsoft Defender for Endpoint, identity protection, Windows 10 Teams, kiosk, and Windows Update client policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/graph-apis-used-by-intune-device-configuration-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported Microsoft Intune apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides lists of support partner and Microsoft apps that are commonly used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-supported-intune-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovered apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand details about the detected apps that Intune found on a device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-discovered-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Edge for Windows to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Edge for Windows to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-windows-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add PowerShell scripts to Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and run PowerShell scripts, assign the script policy to Microsoft Entra groups, and use reports to monitor the scripts. See the steps to delete scripts you add on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune. Read common issues and resolutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/powershell-scripts</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Intune policies to manage Windows LAPS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create policies to manage the Windows Local Administrator Policy Solution (LAPS) on Windows devices that enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-laps-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to improve your security posture with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-configure-security</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Plan the integration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan the integration to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase1</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows Backup for Organizations in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows backup and restore in Intune for employees or students.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-backup-restore</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage account protection settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune endpoint security account protection policies to protect the identity and accounts of users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Windows LAPS with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Microsoft Intune and application protection policy to manage the local administrator accounts on Windows devices. Through the Windows LAPS CSP, back up accounts and passwords to Microsoft Entra ID, define password requirements, and protect account passwords through scheduled password rotations and manual rotations at need.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-laps-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 22:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Collect Diagnostics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Intune security baselines for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that have preset and recommended configurations to the Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Find lost devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Locate lost or stolen devices by using the locate device feature in Microsoft Intune. Get details on security and privacy information when using the locate device action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-locate</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt macOS FileVault disk encryption with Intune policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to configure FileVault on macOS devices, and use the admin center to manage their recovery keys.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Disable Activation Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune to disable Activation Lock on Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-activation-lock-disable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Defender for Endpoint in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/advanced-threat-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Reset Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to reset a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-passcode-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Sync - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the device sync remote action in Intune to apply policy, app, and configuration updates to managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Send Custom Notifications - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings for Microsoft Defender Antivirus for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the settings in the Microsoft Defender Antivirus profile for Windows devices. You can configure these settings as part of Endpoint security Antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenarios for using Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Conditional Access is commonly used with Intune compliance policy for devices and apps</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-intune-common-ways-use</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View report details for encryption status of devices managed with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to view reports for device encryption status across macOS FileVault and Windows BitLocker encrypted devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encryption-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>