<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:02:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Review App Protection Policy Logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor results of your device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the device compliance dashboard to understand overall device compliance the per policy and per setting device compliance results.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Windows, Windows Holographic, and Surface Hub devices in Microsoft Intune. Check for compliance on the minimum and maximum operating system, set password restrictions and length, check for partner anti-virus (AV) solutions, enable encryption on data storage, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Intune security baselines for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that have preset and recommended configurations to the Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure device configuration profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or configure a device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Select the platform type, configure the settings, and add a scope tag. Learn more about applicability rules, and the policy refresh cycle times.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-create</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure compliance policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Description for configuring compliance policies</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-compliance-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune to remediate vulnerabilities found by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune Security Tasks to manage threats and vulnerabilities identified by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/atp-manage-vulnerabilities</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune capabilities that can help you protect your devices and data against unauthorized access and other threats.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-protect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies with tenant attached Configuration Manager devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use tenant attach to add Configuration Manager devices to Microsoft Intune and then deploy Intune policies to those devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/tenant-attach-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Enterprise security configurations for personally-owned work profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review example configurations of basic, enhanced, and high security for devices with Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/android-personally-owned-security-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device compliance security configurations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review example device compliance configurations of basic, enhanced, and high security for iOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/ios-ipados-device-compliance-security-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Defender for Endpoint Web protection on Android devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender for Endpoint web protection settings on Android devices managed by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-configure-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint detection and response policy. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security endpoint detection and response policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-edr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Enterprise security configurations for corporate-owned fully managed profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review example configurations of basic, enhanced, and high security for devices with Android Enterprise corporate-owned fully managed profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/android-fully-managed-security-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings you can manage with Intune Endpoint Protection profiles for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the available settings in Intune endpoint protection profiles for managed Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-protection-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Defender for Endpoint in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Install and configure Microsoft Tunnel Gateway on a Linux server to support Intune managed cloud-based devices in connecting to your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compliance in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about compliance, dependencies, and features in Microsoft Intune supporting data protection and regulatory requirements.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/compliance-in-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot-agents-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Scenario - Cloud-Managed Modern Desktop - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the guided scenario to set up and configure a basic Modern Desktop from the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-cloud-managed-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) with your Mobile Threat Defense partner to protect access to company resources based on device risk.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mobile-threat-defense</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune manages users and devices, simplifies app management and automated policy deployment, and integrates with mobile threat defense. It connects to Managed Google Play, Apple tokens and certificates, and Teamviewer for remote assistance. Can use MDM or MAM to protect data, configure devices, and simplify access to company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Intune, including device compliance and onboarding status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage endpoint security in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security node to manage device security and remediate issues for devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard and Configure Devices with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint via Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune, including connecting the products, onboarding devices, and assigning policies for compliance and risk level assessment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-integrate</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to Android DA devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a custom profile for Android device administrator (DA) devices in Microsoft Intune. Create a WiFi profile with a preshared key, create a per-app VPN profile, or allow/block apps for Samsung Knox Standard devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain join profile settings for Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a domain join device configuration profile for Microsoft Entra hybrid joined devices. Use this profile to deploy on-premises Active Directory domain information to devices provisioned with Windows Autopilot and Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/domain-join-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune product and capabilities documentation</title>
      <description>Learn more about how Microsoft Intune products and capabilities can help you secure, deploy, and manage users, apps, and endpoint devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, administrative templates (ADMX), and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect Intune account to managed Google Play account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect your Intune account to your Managed Google Play account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/connect-intune-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect device hardware info with the properties catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the properties catalog in Microsoft Intune view and collect enhanced device hardware info on Windows devices you manage with Intune. You can collect info like BIOS version, TPM status, disk info, memory details, and network adapter configurations. Use this information to get deeper visibility into your device inventory and troubleshoot issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Collect Diagnostics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Find lost devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Locate lost or stolen devices by using the locate device feature in Microsoft Intune. Get details on security and privacy information when using the locate device action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-locate</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Disable Activation Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune to disable Activation Lock on Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-activation-lock-disable</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Query in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device query in Microsoft Intune to get on-demand device state, run Kusto Query Language (KQL) queries, and troubleshoot devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/device-query</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Reset Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to reset a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-passcode-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Sync - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the device sync remote action in Intune to apply policy, app, and configuration updates to managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Send Custom Notifications - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work From Anywhere Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how the Work from Anywhere report in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides insights into remote productivity, device readiness, and user experience.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/work-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security, email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4 to deploy device configuration profiles as part of the minimum set of policies for your devices using Microsoft Intune. The starting point is to enable the firewall, install AV, scan for malware, install software updates, create a strong PIN policy, and create email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-configuration-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Lost Mode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enable Lost Mode in Microsoft Intune to remotely lock a lost or stolen iOS or iPadOS device and display a custom message and phone number on the lock screen.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-lost-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scores, Baselines, and Insights in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand endpoint analytics scores, baselines, and insights in Microsoft Intune to measure and improve device performance metrics.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/scores</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for Android software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for Android devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on corporate owned Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Platform Schema - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the Intune data platform schema for device query and inventory, including supported properties and data types in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/data-platform-schema</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for software updates on BYOD in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for BYOD and personally owned devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on personal devices on Android and iOS/iPadOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-personal-byod</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how anomaly detection in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics proactively monitors device health, detects issues, and provides actionable insights for IT admins.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/anomaly-detection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple configuration list for Intune settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune settings catalog to add, configure, or restrict features on Apple devices. This article lists and describes the settings you can configure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/apple-settings-catalog-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics, including device enrollment issues, startup performance, and data collection problems.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Reliability in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Explore application reliability in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics to analyze app crashes, improve user productivity, and enhance device performance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/app-reliability</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Update Cellular Data Plan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to update the cellular data plan for iOS/iPadOS devices that support eSIM with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/update-cellular-data-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor your Endpoint Privilege Management policies for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View reports for managed and unmanaged file elevations when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint Analytics in Microsoft Adoption Score - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Adoption Score integrates endpoint analytics to provide insights on device performance, startup performance, application reliability, and work-from-anywhere readiness for your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/adoption-score</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint Analytics: Optimize Device Performance and User Experience - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides actionable insights to optimize device performance, improve user experience, and enable proactive IT troubleshooting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove User - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a user from a Shared iPad with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-user</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Logout current user - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the logout the current user from a Shared iPad with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-logout-user</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Shutdown - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to shutdown Apple devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-shutdown</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step-by-step guide to configure endpoint analytics in Microsoft Intune, enroll devices, and manage data collection policies for device insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint Analytics Data Collection - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand endpoint analytics data collection in Microsoft Intune, including data flow, privacy, and how to stop gathering device data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/data-collection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common tasks and features in the settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure common features. You can create a Universal Print policy, configure Microsoft Edge and Google Chrome web browsers, and use built in settings instead of plist files for macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-common-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Wipe - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wipe, or factory reset, devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: BitLocker Key Rotation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the BitLocker recovery key with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-bitlocker-keys</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Run Remediation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand remediations with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-run-remediation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Apps and Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how apps and configurations can be removed temporarily, then restored automatically or manually using the Remove apps and configuration device action with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/remove-apps-config</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get support in the Microsoft Intune admin center</title>
      <description>Get online and telephone support for Microsoft Intune and other device management cloud services from within the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/get-support</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Remote Action: Rotate FileVault Recovery Key - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the FileVault recovery key with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Analytics Troubleshooting and Frequently Asked Questions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find troubleshooting steps and FAQs for Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics, including endpoint analytics issues, data refresh, and dashboard customization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/advanced-analytics-troubleshooting-faqs</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover what Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics is, how it extends endpoint analytics with advanced device insights, proactive troubleshooting, and enhanced reporting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/advanced-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Scopes in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device scopes in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics with scope tags for custom device reporting and targeted insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/device-scopes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View Software Update Reports for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Track Apple device update status in real time with Intune's declarative software update reporting. Learn how Microsoft Intune surfaces update changes directly from managed Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/updates/apple-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-passcode</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Performance Report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Explore the resource performance report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics for CPU and RAM insights, device performance analysis, and proactive endpoint analytics.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/resource-performance-report</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment time grouping - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview and setup of the enrollment time grouping feature in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-time-grouping</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/updates/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Delete - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to delete devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Retire - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to retire device using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-retire</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Rotate local admin password - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the local admin password on Windows and macOS devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-local-admin-password</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics, enable advanced analytics features, and integrate endpoint analytics for proactive device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/advanced-analytics-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Performance in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how startup performance in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics helps analyze boot times, identify issues, and optimize device performance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/startup-performance</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating elevation rules with Endpoint Privilege Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View guidance on how to create strong file elevation rules with Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-elevation-rules</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/updates/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Play Lost Mode Sound - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Play lost device sound remote action in Microsoft Intune to trigger an audible alert on a lost, stolen, or misplaced device—helping users locate it quickly and securely.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-play-lost-mode-sound</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Pause Config Refresh - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to temporarily pause policy enforcement on Windows 11 devices using Intune's Pause Config Refresh remote action to support troubleshooting and manual changes.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/pause-config-refresh</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported Microsoft Intune Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides lists of support partner and Microsoft apps that are commonly used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-supported-intune-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Query for Multiple Devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use device query for multiple devices in Microsoft Intune to run Kusto Query Language (KQL) queries, analyze device inventory, and gain cross-platform insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/device-query-multiple-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Device Timeline in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover the enhanced device timeline in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics for detailed device event history and advanced troubleshooting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/enhanced-device-timeline</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Support for Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get support for Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics, including technical troubleshooting, online help, and product feedback options.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/get-support</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restart Frequency in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Analyze restart frequency in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics to identify device reboot patterns, troubleshoot issues, and improve reliability.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/restart-frequency</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Windows Health Monitoring profile in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a Windows Health Monitoring profile to collect endpoint analytics and software update events on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune. Use this data to recommend software, review startup performance, and fix support issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/windows-health-monitoring</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remote Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the remote lock action in Microsoft Intune to lock a managed device that has a passcode or PIN.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remote-lock</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>