<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:02:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Get an Apple MDM Push certificate for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get an Apple MDM Push certificate to manage iOS/iPadOS devices with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-mdm-push-certificate-get</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll devices using a device enrollment manager account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the device enrollment manager account to enroll devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-manager-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add corporate identifiers to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add corporate identifiers (enrollment method, IMEI, and serial numbers) to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/corporate-identifiers-add</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of enrollment restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the enrollment restrictions available in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-restrictions-set</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect Intune account to managed Google Play account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect your Intune account to your Managed Google Play account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/connect-intune-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk enrollment for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a bulk enrollment package for Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-bulk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune enrollment for Android Enterprise dedicated devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure enrollment in Microsoft Intune for Android Enterprise dedicated devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-kiosk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS direct enrollment - Apple Configurator-Setup Assistant - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Apple Configurator to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices with Setup Assistant.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-configurator-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Use Apple Business Manager to enroll iOS/iPadOS devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this tutorial, you'll set up Apple corporate device enrollment features with Intune to enroll iOS/iPadOS devices purchased through Apple Business Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/tutorial-use-device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center copy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices copy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Categorize devices into groups in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Categorize Intune-managed devices into groups for easier management in the admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-group-mapping</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Intune and Microsoft Entra device limit restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the differences between Intune device limit restrictions and Microsoft Entra device limit restrictions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-limit-intune-azure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up web based device enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up web-based device enrollment to manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/web-based-device-enrollment-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Intune devices with Android device administrator - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Android device administrator with Intune to manage devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-enroll-device-administrator</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android (AOSP) device management in Intune for corporate-owned userless devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for corporate-owned userless devices built on the Android Open Source Project (AOSP) platform.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-aosp-corporate-owned-userless-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable autodiscovery of Intune enrollment server - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Simplify enrollment for users by enabling automatic discovery of the Intune enrollment server.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-create-cname</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android (AOSP) device management in Intune for corporate-owned user-associated devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for corporate-owned user-associated devices built on the Android Open Source Project (AOSP) platform.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-aosp-corporate-owned-user-associated-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll personal devices in Intune with Android Enterprise work profile management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for personal devices and bring-your-own-device scenarios using Android Enterprise work profile management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-work-profile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android Enterprise work profile for corporate owned devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Android Enterprise work profile for corporate-owned devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-corporate-owned-work-profile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automatic enrollment in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment of Windows 10/11 devices that join or register with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/quickstart-setup-auto-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple device enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple device enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-device-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authentication methods for Apple automated device enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the Intune-supported authentication methods you can use with automated device enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/automated-device-enrollment-authentication</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Require multifactor authentication for Intune device enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to require multifactor authentication in Microsoft Entra ID for Intune device enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/multi-factor-authentication</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device platform restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Restrict personally owned devices, and specific device platforms and OS versions from enrolling in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/create-device-platform-restrictions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically enroll devices with Samsung Knox Mobile Enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android devices in Microsoft Intune with the Knox Mobile Enrollment tool.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-samsung-knox-mobile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect to the Data Warehouse with Power BI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can download a file for use with Microsoft Power BI that allows you to load interactive, dynamically generated reports for your Microsoft Intune tenant.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-proc-get-a-link-powerbi</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up user enrollment with Company Portal for iOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up the profile based Apple User Enrollment option for personal devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-user-enrollment-with-company-portal</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with the Microsoft Intune App SDK - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Quickly enable your mobile app for mobile application management (MAM) with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Intune Data Warehouse - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Intune Data Warehouse to build reports that provide insight into your enterprise mobile environment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-nav-create-intune-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use direct enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy and enroll macOS devices in Microsoft Intune using direct enrollment with Apple Configurator.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-direct-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Microsoft Entra ID to access Intune APIs in Microsoft Graph - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes steps needed for apps to use Microsoft Entra ID to access the Intune APIs in Microsoft Graph.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/intune-graph-apis</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment notifications in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up enrollment notifications in Intune for employees or students.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluate and try - Enroll a device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this evaluation task, enroll a device running Windows 10/11 into Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/quickstart-enroll-windows-device</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can use Security Copilot to get information about your Intune data, including devices, apps, policies, and groups managed in Intune. You can also compare policies, get device specific details, and get target info for policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrap Android apps with the Intune App Wrapping Tool - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wrap your Android apps without changing the code of the app itself. Prepare the apps so you can apply mobile app management policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-wrapper-prepare-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure ChromeOS connector for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect the Google Admin Console to Microsoft Intune so that you can view and take action on enrolled ChromeOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/chrome-enterprise-connector-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back up and restore iOS/iPadOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about backup and restore scenarios for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/backup-restore-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device limit restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Restrict the number of devices allowed to enroll in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/create-device-limit-restrictions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Intune SDK integration into your iOS app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Intune SDK integration into your iOS app</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase3</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Plan the integration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Plan the integration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set terms and conditions in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set terms and conditions that users see in the Company Portal for Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/terms-and-conditions-create</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device staging overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>An overview of device staging, Android Enterprise token types, and token management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-staging-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare apps for mobile application management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The information in this topic helps you decide when you should use the App wrapping tool and the App SDK to enable your custom line-of-business apps to use the mobile app management policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/apps-prepare-mobile-application-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View enrollment reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor and troubleshoot issues with enrollment restrictions and enrollment status page assignments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/view-enrollment-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of Intune App SDK - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune App SDK is available for both the iOS and Android platforms, and enables mobile app management features with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Apple device management in Intune for corporate-owned userless devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for corporate-owned userless iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-corporate-owned-userless-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move Android devices from device administrator to personally owned work profile management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Move Android devices from device administrator to personally owned work profile management in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-move-device-admin-work-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Get started with MAM - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get started with Intune before incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase3</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get data from the Data Warehouse API with a REST client - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to retrieve data from the Microsoft Intune Data Warehouse using a RESTful API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-proc-data-rest</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse Collections - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune Data Warehouse collections provide details related to the Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/intune-data-warehouse-collections</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - MAM integration essentials - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand MAM integration essentials to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase4</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Warehouse data model - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune Data Warehouse samples data daily to provide a historical view of your continually changing mobile environment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-data-model</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - MSAL prerequisite and setup - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. MSAL prerequisite and setup</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse API endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This reference topic describes the Microsoft Intune Data Warehouse API URL structure. Filter examples are provided.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-api-url</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - App participation features - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. App participation features</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase4</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incomplete user enrollments report overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Access your organization's incomplete user enrollments report generated by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-report-company-portal-abandon</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse API - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can use the Intune Data Warehouse API to build reports that provide insight into your enterprise mobile environment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-nav-intune-data-warehouse</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - MSAL Prerequisite - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the MSAL prerequisite to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move from Android device administrator to mobile application management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to set up mobile application management, an alternative option to Android device administrator that focuses on app protection and doesn't require device enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/move-to-android-mobile-application-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple School Manager Program enrollment for iOS/iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to set up Microsoft Intune with Apple School Manager for corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-school-manager-set-up-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - App participation features - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand App participation features when incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase7</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Line-of-business app versioning in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Introduces how app versions are used in Intune when an app is added or updated.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/apps-lob-app-versioning</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android lets you incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-appendix</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple School Manager - get Apple token and assign devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get the Apple token needed to set up Apple School Manager and Microsoft Intune for corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-school-manager-step-1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - App Protection CA support (optional) - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. App Protection CA support (optional)</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase6</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple School Manager - create enrollment profile - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create the enrollment profile in Intune for Apple School Manager enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-school-manager-step-2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Multi-Identity - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Multi-Identity when incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase5</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference for Application entities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference topic for the Application category of entity collections in the Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-application</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Multi-Identity - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Multi-Identity</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase5</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph APIs to configure devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the Graph API entities with the matching Windows CSP and offset URI on Windows 10 devices and newer used when configuring devices in Microsoft Intune. See the matching API and CSP for shared PCs, endpoint protection, Microsoft Defender for Endpoint, identity protection, Windows 10 Teams, kiosk, and Windows Update client policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/graph-apis-used-by-intune-device-configuration-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference for Policy entities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference topic for the Policy category of entity collections in the Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile App Management (MAM) - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference topic for the Mobile App Management category of entity collections in the Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-mobile-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move your Intune Data Warehouse account data - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how to back up your Intune Data Warehouse data when moving your account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/data-warehouse-account-move</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Intune features overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Security Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues and query devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse application-only authentication - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes Data Warehouse application-only authentication for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/data-warehouse-app-only-auth</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create an Intune report from the OData feed with Power BI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a treemap visualization using Power BI Desktop with an interactive filter from the Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-proc-create-with-odata</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Intune data with natural language and take action - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, use Explorer to query your data in natural language and run built-in queries that match your request. Copilot summarizes the results, and provides recommendations and actions based on the query results. You can also create policies that target users and groups in the query results. Use this feature to explore your Intune data, troubleshoot issues, and create custom reports.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-explorer</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntuneManagementExtension Entity - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference topic for the IntuneManagementExtension Entity category of entity collections in the Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-intunemanagementextension</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment for Android Enterprise fully managed devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up enrollment in Intune for devices using the Android Enterprise fully managed device management solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment for shared device mode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to set up Apple automated device enrollment for iOS/iPadOS devices in shared device mode, a feature of Microsoft Entra.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/automated-device-enrollment-shared-device-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Warehouse User Entity Timeline - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how the Microsoft Intune Data Warehouse represents Users in a timeline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-user-timeline</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Appendix - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Appendix</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-appendix</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple School Manager - sync and distribute devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Sync and distribute Apple School Manager devices enrolled in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-school-manager-step-3</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared iPad devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Shared iPad devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-shared-ipad</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Date - Intune Data Warehouse - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference topic for the Date category of entity collections in the Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-date</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared iOS and iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Shared iOS and iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-shared-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment time grouping - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview and setup of the enrollment time grouping feature in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-time-grouping</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Plan the integration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan the integration to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Device Association - Intune Data Warehouse - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The UserDeviceAssociation entity contains user device associations in your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-user-device</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for iOS/iPadOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User - Intune Data Warehouse - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference topic for the User category of entity collections in the Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up account driven Apple User Enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up account driven Apple User Enrollment for personal devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-account-driven-user-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrap iOS apps with the Intune App Wrapping Tool - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wrap your iOS apps without changing the code of the app itself. Prepare the apps so you can apply mobile app management policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-wrapper-prepare-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Web-view features - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Web-view features</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase7</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse Change log - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic provides a list of changes for the Microsoft Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-changelog</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot-agents-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>