<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 11:16:10 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 11:16:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Audit, export or delete personal data collected by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to audit, export, or delete personal data that is collected by Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-audit-export-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to improve your security posture with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-configure-security</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Android, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows devices in Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO and deploy the configuration to your macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using Microsoft Entra ID with the Secure Enclave, smart card, or password authentication methods. You create a settings catalog policy to configure the settings. This article is a step-by-step guide to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policies overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get an Apple MDM Push certificate for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get an Apple MDM Push certificate to manage iOS/iPadOS devices with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-mdm-push-certificate-get</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll devices using a device enrollment manager account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the device enrollment manager account to enroll devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-manager-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to assist users authenticated by your organization. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure feature updates policy for Windows devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows feature updates. Configure and deploy policy to maintain the Windows feature version of Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-10-feature-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set the mobile device management authority - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to set the mobile device management authority in Microsoft Intune and some key considerations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/mdm-authority-set</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple volume-purchased apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, administrative templates (ADMX), and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of enrollment restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the enrollment restrictions available in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-restrictions-set</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign device profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to assign device configuration profiles and policies to users and devices. Learn how to exclude groups from a profile assignment in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration guide to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deployment guide to set up, onboard, or move to Intune. These steps include moving from partner MDM providers, using co-management, moving from on-premises group policy, and moving from Office 365 device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-intune-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect Intune account to managed Google Play account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect your Intune account to your Managed Google Play account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/connect-intune-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk enrollment for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a bulk enrollment package for Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-bulk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog to configure administrative templates (ADMX) in Microsoft Intune on Windows 10/11 client devices. You can configure some Control Panel features, Start menu and task bar notifications, event log service, prevent IIS installation, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Cloud PKI for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>An overview of the Microsoft Cloud PKI service, available with Microsoft Intune Suite or as an Intune add-on.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to install and configure the unified Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune, which supports SCEP, PKCS, imported PKCS, and certificate revocation.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-install</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune enrollment for Android Enterprise dedicated devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure enrollment in Microsoft Intune for Android Enterprise dedicated devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-kiosk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS direct enrollment - Apple Configurator-Setup Assistant - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Apple Configurator to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices with Setup Assistant.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-configurator-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Properties catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Properties catalog policy to manage Device Inventory settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Use Apple Business Manager to enroll iOS/iPadOS devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this tutorial, you'll set up Apple corporate device enrollment features with Intune to enroll iOS/iPadOS devices purchased through Apple Business Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/tutorial-use-device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure a tenant-wide Windows Hello for Business policy with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Apply policy for Windows Hello for Business on devices at the time they enroll with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-hello</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune - Azure - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the unified Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune, which supports SCEP, PKCS, imported PKCS, and certificate revocation.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Windows 10, Windows 11, Windows Holographic, and Surface Hub devices in Microsoft Intune. Check for compliance on the minimum and maximum operating system, set password restrictions and length, check for partner anti-virus (AV) solutions, enable encryption on data storage, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure compliance policies with actions for noncompliance in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your compliance policies with one or more actions for noncompliance to protect devices and your organization from unprotected devices. Actions can remotely lock devices, send email or notifications to device users, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/actions-for-noncompliance</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Types of certificate that are supported by Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Microsoft Intune's support for Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP), Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS device enrollment guide for  Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll macOS devices using device enrollment, automated device enrollment (DEP), and Apple Configurator enrollment options in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Intune security baselines for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that have preset and recommended configurations to the Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create trusted certificate profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and deploy trusted certificate profiles to deploy a trusted root certificate to managed devices in Intune. Trusted certificate profiles support use of Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) and Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-trusted-root</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center copy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices copy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to import and analyze group policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Import and analyze your group policy objects using the Group Policy analytics tool. See the policies that are supported and aren't supported in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/group-policy-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Categorize devices into groups in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Categorize Intune-managed devices into groups for easier management in the admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-group-mapping</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Intune and Microsoft Entra device limit restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the differences between Intune device limit restrictions and Microsoft Entra device limit restrictions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-limit-intune-azure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up web based device enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up web-based device enrollment to manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/web-based-device-enrollment-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Universal Print policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to create a Universal Print policy for Windows 10/11 client devices. The policy automatically installs printers on your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-printer-provisioning</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites for the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the software and network prerequisites for use of the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Windows Driver updates policy for Windows devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using Microsoft Intune policy to manage Windows driver updates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-driver-updates-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Intune devices with Android device administrator - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Android device administrator with Intune to manage devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-enroll-device-administrator</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android (AOSP) device management in Intune for corporate-owned userless devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for corporate-owned userless devices built on the Android Open Source Project (AOSP) platform.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-aosp-corporate-owned-userless-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported filter device and app properties &amp; operators in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>When using filters, get more information on the device properties, supported operators, and supported Windows OS SKUs, including examples. Use these features to create rule expressions in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-device-properties</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable autodiscovery of Intune enrollment server - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Simplify enrollment for users by enabling automatic discovery of the Intune enrollment server.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-create-cname</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt macOS FileVault disk encryption with Intune policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to configure FileVault on macOS devices, and use the admin center to manage their recovery keys.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure macOS Enterprise SSO app extension with MDMs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Microsoft Enterprise single sign-on (SSO) app extension plug-in. Add or create an macOS device profile using the SSO app extension in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-macos-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict devices features using policy in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a device configuration profile to restrict features on Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, AOSP, macOS, iOS, iPadOS, and Windows 10/11 client devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Wi-Fi profile for devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the steps to create a Wi-Fi device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Create profiles for Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, Android kiosk, iOS, iPadOS, macOS, Windows 10/11, and Windows Holographic for Business. Use these profiles to create a WiFi connection to use certificates, choose an EAP type, select an authentication method, enable a proxy, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage and secure devices overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get an overview of the concepts and features you should know when managing devices that access organization resources in Microsoft Intune. You can manage new and existing devices, including BYOD personal devices, check health compliance and view reports, configure device features, and secure devices using mobile threat solutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/manage-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the settings catalog to configure DDM software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Apple's declarative device management (DDM) settings to install a specific update by an enforced deadline. This feature uses the settings catalog to configure managed software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS and managed macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/managed-software-updates-ios-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared or multi-user Windows device settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add and use Windows 10/11 and Windows Holographic for Business devices that are shared, or used by multiple users in Microsoft Intune. See a list of all the settings and what they do on the devices, including Microsoft HoloLens. Control guest accounts, manage accounts and delete inactive accounts, allow or prevent saving to local storage, set power and sleep options, choose when updates are installed, and use devices in education environments in a device configuration profile.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/shared-user-device-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add groups to organize users and devices for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Microsoft Entra groups to organize users and devices for use with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/groups-add</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Defender for Endpoint in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/advanced-threat-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell scripts for Remediations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>PowerShell script reference for Remediations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/powershell-scripts-remediation</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android (AOSP) device management in Intune for corporate-owned user-associated devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for corporate-owned user-associated devices built on the Android Open Source Project (AOSP) platform.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-aosp-corporate-owned-user-associated-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll personal devices in Intune with Android Enterprise work profile management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for personal devices and bring-your-own-device scenarios using Android Enterprise work profile management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-work-profile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Windows BIOS using configuration MDM policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the BIOS configuration profile that can manage traditional BIOS settings in Microsoft Intune. You use an OEM tool to create a configuration file with the settings. You deploy an OEM Win32 app to the devices to read the configuration file and BIOS passwords. Then, you create a BIOS configuration policy in Intune to add the configuration file and assign the policy to your devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/bios-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android Enterprise work profile for corporate owned devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Android Enterprise work profile for corporate-owned devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-corporate-owned-work-profile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automatic enrollment in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment of Windows 10/11 devices that join or register with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/quickstart-setup-auto-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about the Microsoft Tunnel VPN solution for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway, a VPN server for Intune that runs on Linux. With Microsoft Tunnel, cloud-based devices you manage with Intune can reach your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add VPN settings to devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>On Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, macOS, and Windows devices, use built-in settings to create virtual private network (VPN) connections in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join your cloud-native endpoints to Microsoft Entra</title>
      <description>When moving to or using cloud-native endpoints, use Microsoft Entra joined endpoints. When your endpoints are joined to Microsoft Entra, you can use Windows Autopilot to provision or get devices ready for organization use. Learn more about the benefits to IT admins and end-users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/azure-ad-joined-hybrid-azure-ad-joined</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple device enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple device enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-device-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third-party device compliance partners support in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a third-party device compliance partner as a source of compliance data for devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-compliance-partners</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up device-based Conditional Access policies with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure a device-based Conditional Access policy that uses device status from a Microsoft Intune device compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/create-conditional-access-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authentication methods for Apple automated device enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the Intune-supported authentication methods you can use with automated device enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/automated-device-enrollment-authentication</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Require multifactor authentication for Intune device enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to require multifactor authentication in Microsoft Entra ID for Intune device enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/multi-factor-authentication</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-level architecture for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This reference architecture shows options for integrating Microsoft Intune in your Azure environment with Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/high-level-architecture</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for iOS/iPadOS that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically enroll devices with Samsung Knox Mobile Enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android devices in Microsoft Intune with the Knox Mobile Enrollment tool.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-samsung-knox-mobile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage and secure apps overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get an overview of the concepts and features you should know when managing apps that access organization resources in Microsoft Intune. You can deploy apps used by your organization, including Microsoft Edge and Microsoft 365. You can also configure apps, protect apps on organizations owned and BYOD personal devices, and update apps that you deploy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/manage-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up user enrollment with Company Portal for iOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up the profile based Apple User Enrollment option for personal devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-user-enrollment-with-company-portal</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings for Microsoft Defender Antivirus for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the settings in the Microsoft Defender Antivirus profile for Windows devices. You can configure these settings as part of Endpoint security Antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Route logs to Azure Monitor using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Diagnostics Settings to send audit logs and operational logs in Microsoft Intune to Azure Storage account, Event Hubs, or Log Analytics. Choose how long you want to keep the data, and see some estimated costs for different size tenants.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/review-logs-using-azure-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenarios for using Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Conditional Access is commonly used with Intune compliance policy for devices and apps</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-intune-common-ways-use</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate your imported group policy to a policy in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>After you import your Windows group policy objects in Microsoft Intune, use the migrate feature to transfer your GPOs to a Settings Catalog policy. This policy uses your imported GPOs, and can be assigned to users and devices managed by your organizations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/group-policy-analytics-migrate</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create discovery scripts for custom compliance policy in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create scripts for Linux or Windows devices to discover the settings you define as custom compliance settings for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-custom-script</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiosk settings for Windows and Holographic devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your Windows 10/11 and Windows Holographic for Business devices as single-app and multi-app kiosks, customize the start menu, add apps, show the task bar, and configure a web browser in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kiosk-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View report details for encryption status of devices managed with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to view reports for device encryption status across macOS FileVault and Windows BitLocker encrypted devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encryption-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use app-based Conditional Access policies with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using app-based Conditional Access policies with Microsoft Intune for both enrolled and unenrolled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/app-based-conditional-access-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Windows Driver updates policy in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage policies that install Windows driver updates on your Intune managed Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-driver-updates-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Windows virtual machines with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the general guidelines for using Windows 10/11 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-10-virtual-machines</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up per-app VPN for iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the prerequisites, create a group for the virtual private network (VPN) users, add a SCEP certificate profile, configure a per-app VPN profile, and assign some apps to the VPN profile in Microsoft Intune on iOS/iPadOS devices. Also lists the steps to verify the VPN connection on the device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-setting-configure-per-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>