<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 06:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 06:02:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Android App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy endpoint detection and response policy with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune endpoint security policies to configure and deploy Microsoft Defender for Endpoint EDR capabilities to Windows, macOS, and Linux devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-edr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage antivirus settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies and use reports for devices you manage with endpoint security antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-antivirus-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about Microsoft Intune's unified endpoint management and security solutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune product and capabilities documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about how Microsoft Intune products and capabilities can help you secure, deploy, and manage users, apps, and endpoint devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure feature updates policy for Windows devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows feature updates. Configure and deploy policy to maintain the Windows feature version of Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-10-feature-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect device hardware info with the properties catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the properties catalog in Microsoft Intune view and collect enhanced device hardware info on Windows devices you manage with Intune. You can collect info like BIOS version, TPM status, disk info, memory details, and network adapter configurations. Use this information to get deeper visibility into your device inventory and troubleshoot issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune Management Extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Intune data with natural language and take action - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, use Explorer to query your data in natural language and run built-in queries that match your request. Copilot summarizes the results, and provides recommendations and actions based on the query results. You can also create policies that target users and groups in the query results. Use this feature to explore your Intune data, troubleshoot issues, and create custom reports.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-explorer</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot Agents in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how Microsoft Security Copilot enhances Microsoft Intune through AI-powered security agents. Learn about available agents and explore their capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Device Offboarding Agent - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Device Offboarding Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify and offboard devices that are no longer in use.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/device-offboarding-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Platform Schema - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the Microsoft Intune data platform schema for device queries and inventory. Discover supported properties and data types to efficiently manage and report on your devices with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/data-platform-schema</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Performance Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how startup performance in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics helps analyze boot times, identify issues, and optimize device performance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/startup-performance</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Query for Multiple Devices in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use device query for multiple devices in Microsoft Intune to run Kusto Query Language (KQL) queries, analyze device inventory, and gain cross-platform insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/device-query-multiple-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Intune features overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Security Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues and query devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scores, Baselines, and Insights in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand endpoint analytics scores, baselines, and insights in Microsoft Intune to measure and improve device performance metrics.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/scores</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Reliability Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Explore application reliability in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics to analyze app crashes, improve user productivity, and enhance device performance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/app-reliability</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Analytics overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover what Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics is, how it extends endpoint analytics with advanced device insights, proactive troubleshooting, and enhanced reporting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Query in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device query in Microsoft Intune to get on-demand device state, run Kusto Query Language (KQL) queries, and troubleshoot devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/device-query</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data collection in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about personal data collected in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-collect</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step-by-step guide to configure endpoint analytics in Microsoft Intune, enroll devices, and manage data collection policies for device insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/configure</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint Analytics in Microsoft Adoption Score - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Adoption Score integrates endpoint analytics to provide insights on device performance, startup performance, application reliability, and work-from-anywhere readiness for your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/adoption-score</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Support for Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get support for Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics, including technical troubleshooting, online help, and product feedback options.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/get-support</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics, including device enrollment issues, startup performance, and data collection problems.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Intune service and set up the environment for education.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/set-up-microsoft-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battery Health Report in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how the battery health report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics provides insights into device battery performance, degradation, and proactive replacement strategies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/battery-health</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint analytics overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides actionable insights to optimize device performance, improve user experience, and enable proactive IT troubleshooting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune Suite add-on capabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune Suite unifies a series of mission-critical advanced endpoint management and security capabilities. The capabilities of the suite are integrated with Microsoft 365 and Microsoft Security across endpoint platforms for both cloud and on-premises co-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-add-ons</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint Analytics Data Collection - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand endpoint analytics data collection in Microsoft Intune, including data flow, privacy, and how to stop gathering device data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/data-collection</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomalies Report in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how anomalies report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics helps IT admins monitor device health, detect issues, and get actionable insights to improve endpoint reliability.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/anomalies</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Performance Report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Explore the resource performance report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics for CPU and RAM insights, device performance analysis, and proactive endpoint analytics.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/resource-performance</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work From Anywhere Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how the Work from Anywhere report in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides insights into remote productivity, device readiness, and user experience.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/work-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Windows Health Monitoring profile in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a Windows Health Monitoring profile to collect endpoint analytics and software update events on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune. Use this data to recommend software, review startup performance, and fix support issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/windows-health-monitoring</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune manages users and devices, simplifies app management and automated policy deployment, and integrates with mobile threat defense. It connects to Managed Google Play, Apple tokens and certificates, and Teamviewer for remote assistance. Can use MDM or MAM to protect data, configure devices, and simplify access to company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed IT with multiple admins - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about scaling guidelines for Microsoft Intune when you have a large number of local admins who need to manage their own users/devices and policies within the same tenant. Use Microsoft Intune's Role Based Access Control to manage access.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-scale-guidelines</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Scopes in endpoint analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device scopes in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics with scope tags for custom device reporting and targeted insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/device-scopes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions About Advanced Analytics in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides answers to some frequently asked questions about Advanced Analytics.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/faq</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Timeline Report in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover the device timeline in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics for detailed device event history and advanced troubleshooting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/device-timeline</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage account protection settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune endpoint security account protection policies to protect the identity and accounts of users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To enhance the security of your organization, set your users to run with standard permissions while Endpoint Privilege Management ensures those users can seamlessly run specified files with elevated rights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot managed device to Network Device Enrollment Service (NDES) communication in Microsoft Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot managed device to NDES server communication when using Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) certificate profiles to deploy certificates with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/certificates/troubleshoot-scep-certificate-device-to-ndes</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for US government deployments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the list of US government endpoint URLs that Intune needs and requires. Allow the ports, IP addresses, and endpoint URLs in your proxy server configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-us-government-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for iOS/iPadOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple device enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple device enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-device-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iVerify Enterprise Mobile Threat Defense with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up iVerify Enterprise Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/iverify-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up iVerify Enterprise Mobile Threat Defense with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up iVerify Enterprise Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/iverify-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned Macs into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use third-party certification authorities (CA) with SCEP in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, you can add a vendor or third-party certificate authority (CA) to issue certificates to mobile devices using the SCEP protocol. In this overview, a Microsoft Entra application gives Microsoft Intune permissions to validate certificates. Then, use the application ID, authentication key, and tenant ID of the Microsoft Entra application in the setup of your SCEP server to issue certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-authority-add-scep-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known Issues for Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure policies that define how Endpoint Privilege Management functions in your tenant, and behaviors when elevating files to run in administrative context.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-known-issues</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows enrollment attestation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out how the Device attestation status report can help you and learn to use the Attest device action to ensure your devices are secure and reliable.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-attestation</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt macOS devices with FileVault using Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to configure and manage FileVault disk encryption on macOS devices, including Setup Assistant enforcement and comprehensive recovery key management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View report details for encryption status of devices managed with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to view reports for device encryption status across macOS FileVault and Windows BitLocker encrypted devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encryption-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies with tenant attached Configuration Manager devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use tenant attach to add Configuration Manager devices to Microsoft Intune and then deploy Intune policies to those devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/tenant-attach-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 2. Create App Protection Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business across Windows, Android, and iOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-2-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage firewall settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security firewall policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-firewall-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard and Configure Devices with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint via Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune, including connecting the products, onboarding devices, and assigning policies for compliance and risk level assessment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-integrate</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage attack surface reduction settings with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security attack surface reduction policy settings in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-asr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune endpoint security disk encryption policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy Microsoft Intune endpoint security policy disk encryption policies for BitLocker and FileVault.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-disk-encryption-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security policies and profiles to focus on security configuration of devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 4. Create App Configuration Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4. Create app configuration policies for Microsoft Edge for Business across Windows, Android, and iOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-4-acp-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-1-mamca</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense for App Protection Policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense signals with Microsoft Edge for Business app protection policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-3-scc</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 5. Create Settings Catalog policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 5. Create Settings Catalog policies for Microsoft Edge for Business on Windows and macOS.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-5-settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 6. Deploy Microsoft Edge security baseline - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 6. Deploy the Microsoft Edge security baseline for rapid Windows security configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-6-security-baseline</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 7. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business End User Experience for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 7. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business end user experience Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-7-end-user-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 8. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business Data Security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 8. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business corporate data security in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-8-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Corporate Data in Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure your corporate data in Microsoft Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business across all platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of enrollment restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the enrollment restrictions available in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-restrictions-set</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot auto-enrolling existing Configuration Manager devices in Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Helps you understand and troubleshoot issues when you set up co-management by taking Path 1 - Auto-enroll existing Configuration Manager-managed devices into Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/comanage-configmgr/troubleshoot-co-management-auto-enrolling</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 02:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk enrollment for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a bulk enrollment package for Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-bulk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually Add the Windows 10 Company Portal App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how your workforce can manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app to their PC from the Microsoft Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Apps to Groups in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign an Intune app to groups of users or devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare Apps for Mobile Application Management With Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The information in this article helps you decide when you should use the App wrapping tool and the App SDK to enable your custom line-of-business apps to use the mobile app management policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/apps-prepare-mobile-application-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovered Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand details about the detected apps that Intune found on a device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-discovered-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Transfer Policy Exceptions for Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create exceptions to the Intune App Protection Policy (APP) data transfer policy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-exception</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 12:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS direct enrollment - Apple Configurator-Setup Assistant - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Apple Configurator to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices with Setup Assistant.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-configurator-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use direct enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy and enroll macOS devices in Microsoft Intune using direct enrollment with Apple Configurator.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-direct-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to Detect and Fix Support Issues - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt Windows devices with BitLocker using Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to manage BitLocker encryption on Windows devices, including silent encryption and Personal Data Encryption.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage devices with endpoint security in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security node to view devices and manage them in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-manage-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings you can manage with Intune Endpoint Protection profiles for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the available settings in Intune endpoint protection profiles for managed Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-protection-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent to Manage Vulnerabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify, prioritize, and remediate security vulnerabilities across your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/vulnerability-remediation-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Apps and Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how apps and configurations can be removed temporarily, then restored automatically or manually using the Remove apps and configuration device action with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/remove-apps-config</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center copy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices copy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO and deploy the configuration to your macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using Microsoft Entra ID with the Secure Enclave, smart card, or password authentication methods. You create a settings catalog policy to configure the settings. This article is a step-by-step guide to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Update Policies for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure software update policies for Apple devices using Apple's Declarative Device Management (DDM) model. Improve security, reduce user disruption, and ensure compliance with reliable, automated updates across your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/updates/apple</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with the Device Offboarding Agent - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Device Offboarding Agent in Microsoft Intune, its prerequisites, how it works, and how to configure it.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/device-offboarding-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Collect Diagnostics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan for Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the requirements and capabilities of Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>