<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:06:06 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:06:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune product and capabilities documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about how Microsoft Intune products and capabilities can help you secure, deploy, and manage users, apps, and endpoint devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, administrative templates (ADMX), and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Delivery Optimization settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure device configuration policy to manage Delivery Optimization settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/delivery-optimization-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple configuration list for Intune settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune settings catalog to add, configure, or restrict features on Apple devices. This article lists and describes the settings you can configure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/apple-settings-catalog-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Delivery Optimization settings for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Delivery Optimization settings for Windows devices that you can deploy using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/delivery-optimization-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set permissions to Managed Home Screen using Android Enterprise OEMConfig - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add the Samsung Knox Service Plugin, Zebra OEMConfig Powered by MX, and Legacy Zebra OEMConfig apps to Intune, and use the app schemas to configure permissions for the Managed Home Screen (MHS) app on Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/oemconfig-managed-home-screen-permissions-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune capabilities that can help you protect your devices and data against unauthorized access and other threats.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-protect</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Windows Update rings policy in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows update rings. You can configure, deploy, and pause update installation with Windows Update client policies using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/update-rings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security, email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4 to deploy device configuration profiles as part of the minimum set of policies for your devices using Microsoft Intune. The starting point is to enable the firewall, install AV, scan for malware, install software updates, create a strong PIN policy, and create email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-configuration-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Update for Business reports for Windows Updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Windows Update for Business reports to view data for Windows Updates you deploy with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Update settings you can manage with Intune Update Ring policies for Windows devices. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings for Windows Update that you can manage through Intune policy for Update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/settings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune to expedite Windows quality updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to expedite the installation of Windows updates on managed devices as soon as possible.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/expedite-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to manage software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Windows Driver updates policy for Windows devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using Microsoft Intune policy to manage Windows driver updates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/driver-updates-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows cloud configuration step by step guide - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use this Windows 10/11 cloud configuration step-by-step setup guide to create your own cloud configuration deployment. You create the Microsoft Entra group and policies using Microsoft Intune, including the enrollment profile, compliance policy, and security baseline. You also deploy apps and resources that users need to do their jobs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/cloud-configuration-setup-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent to Manage Vulnerabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify, prioritize, and remediate security vulnerabilities across your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/vulnerability-remediation-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows compatibility reports for Windows updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the app and driver compatibility reports for Windows devices before you deploy Intune policies for feature updates or update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/compatibility-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zebra LifeGuard Over-the-Air Integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates for supported Zebra devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/zebra-lifeguard-ota-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android FOTA Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates on Android devices. A FOTA update can include software and security patches, feature updates, and other changes to the device's firmware.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/fota-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin guide and checklist for macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updates for macOS devices using Microsoft Intune. Use this article to help manage software updates on your organization-owned devices, including how to create policies, manage updates, and review update status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-guide-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows quality update policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Hotpatch updates to receive security updates without restarting your device</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/quality-updates-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Holographic devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and complete different tasks on devices running Windows Holographic for Business and HoloLens. You can configure the Company Portal app, create a compliance policy, customize OMA-URI settings, deploy apps, categorize devices in groups, create profiles, restrict devices, enable software updates, set terms and conditions, configure VPN and Wi-Fi settings, and use Hello for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-holographic-for-business</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure schedules to gradually roll out Windows Updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure schedules that manage how and when Windows updates roll out to your managed devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/rollout-options</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows cloud configuration in a guided scenario - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a guided scenario to configure Windows 10/11 client devices in a cloud configuration in Microsoft Intune. Cloud config focuses on a simplified device experience for internet browsing and using Microsoft 365 apps, including Microsoft Teams.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/cloud-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for software updates on BYOD in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for BYOD and personally owned devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on personal devices on Android and iOS/iPadOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/byod-software-updates-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View Software Update Reports for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Track Apple device update status in real time with Intune's declarative software update reporting. Learn how Microsoft Intune surfaces update changes directly from managed Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software update errors and descriptions in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the Software Update agent error code in Microsoft Intune, including the error code, symbolic name, and error description.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/software-update-agent-error-codes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common tasks and features in the settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure common features. You can create a Universal Print policy, configure Microsoft Edge and Google Chrome web browsers, and use built in settings instead of plist files for macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-common-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable use of Windows diagnostic data by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows diagnostic data in processor configuration for your tenant to enable its use by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/data-enable-windows-data</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To support hybrid and remote workers, convert or migrate your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints. This planning guide focuses on deploying apps and updates with Intune, moving from Group Policy Objects, and using Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-endpoints-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Windows Driver updates policy in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage policies that install Windows driver updates on your Intune managed Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/driver-updates-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Follow the steps to deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for Android software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for Android devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on corporate owned Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/software-updates-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure feature updates policy for Windows devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows feature updates. Configure and deploy policy to maintain the Windows feature version of Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/feature-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune Suite add-on capabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune Suite unifies a series of mission-critical advanced endpoint management and security capabilities. The capabilities of the suite are integrated with Microsoft 365 and Microsoft Security across endpoint platforms for both cloud and on-premises co-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-add-ons</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Update Policies for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure software update policies for Apple devices using Apple's Declarative Device Management (DDM) model. Improve security, reduce user disruption, and ensure compliance with reliable, automated updates across your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work From Anywhere Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how the Work from Anywhere report in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides insights into remote productivity, device readiness, and user experience.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/work-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom settings - Windows Holographic for Business devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a custom profile to use the OMA-URI settings for devices running Windows Holographic for Business in Microsoft Intune, including Microsoft HoloLens. You can set AllowFastReconnect, AllowVPN, AllowUpdateService, UpdateServiceURL, RequireUpdatesApproval, ApprovedUpdates, and ApplicationLaunchRestrictions policy configuration service provider (CSP) settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-windows-holographic</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed IT with multiple admins - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about scaling guidelines for Microsoft Intune when you have a large number of local admins who need to manage their own users/devices and policies within the same tenant. Use Microsoft Intune's Role Based Access Control to manage access.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-scale-guidelines</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Windows Update client policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage Windows software updates by using Intune policy for Update rings for Windows and Windows feature updates for Windows Update client policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for US government deployments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the list of US government endpoint URLs that Intune needs and requires. Allow the ports, IP addresses, and endpoint URLs in your proxy server configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-us-government-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy endpoint detection and response policy with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune endpoint security policies to configure and deploy Microsoft Defender for Endpoint EDR capabilities to Windows, macOS, and Linux devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-edr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage antivirus settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies and use reports for devices you manage with endpoint security antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-antivirus-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about Microsoft Intune's unified endpoint management and security solutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect device hardware info with the properties catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the properties catalog in Microsoft Intune view and collect enhanced device hardware info on Windows devices you manage with Intune. You can collect info like BIOS version, TPM status, disk info, memory details, and network adapter configurations. Use this information to get deeper visibility into your device inventory and troubleshoot issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune Management Extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Intune data with natural language and take action - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, use Explorer to query your data in natural language and run built-in queries that match your request. Copilot summarizes the results, and provides recommendations and actions based on the query results. You can also create policies that target users and groups in the query results. Use this feature to explore your Intune data, troubleshoot issues, and create custom reports.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-explorer</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot Agents in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how Microsoft Security Copilot enhances Microsoft Intune through AI-powered security agents. Learn about available agents and explore their capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step-by-step guide to configure endpoint analytics in Microsoft Intune, enroll devices, and manage data collection policies for device insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/configure</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Performance Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how startup performance in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics helps analyze boot times, identify issues, and optimize device performance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/startup-performance</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Device Offboarding Agent - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Device Offboarding Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify and offboard devices that are no longer in use.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/device-offboarding-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Platform Schema - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the Microsoft Intune data platform schema for device queries and inventory. Discover supported properties and data types to efficiently manage and report on your devices with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/data-platform-schema</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomalies Report in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how anomalies report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics helps IT admins monitor device health, detect issues, and get actionable insights to improve endpoint reliability.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/anomalies</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Timeline Report in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover the device timeline in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics for detailed device event history and advanced troubleshooting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/device-timeline</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions About Advanced Analytics in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides answers to some frequently asked questions about Advanced Analytics.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/faq</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint Analytics in Microsoft Adoption Score - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Adoption Score integrates endpoint analytics to provide insights on device performance, startup performance, application reliability, and work-from-anywhere readiness for your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/adoption-score</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Intune features overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Security Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues and query devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Query for Multiple Devices in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use device query for multiple devices in Microsoft Intune to run Kusto Query Language (KQL) queries, analyze device inventory, and gain cross-platform insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/device-query-multiple-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scores, Baselines, and Insights in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand endpoint analytics scores, baselines, and insights in Microsoft Intune to measure and improve device performance metrics.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/scores</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Reliability Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Explore application reliability in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics to analyze app crashes, improve user productivity, and enhance device performance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/app-reliability</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data collection in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about personal data collected in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-collect</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Analytics overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover what Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics is, how it extends endpoint analytics with advanced device insights, proactive troubleshooting, and enhanced reporting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Query in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device query in Microsoft Intune to get on-demand device state, run Kusto Query Language (KQL) queries, and troubleshoot devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/device-query</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Intune service and set up the environment for education.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/set-up-microsoft-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Support for Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get support for Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics, including technical troubleshooting, online help, and product feedback options.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/get-support</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics, including device enrollment issues, startup performance, and data collection problems.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint analytics overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides actionable insights to optimize device performance, improve user experience, and enable proactive IT troubleshooting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battery Health Report in Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how the battery health report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics provides insights into device battery performance, degradation, and proactive replacement strategies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/battery-health</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint Analytics Data Collection - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand endpoint analytics data collection in Microsoft Intune, including data flow, privacy, and how to stop gathering device data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/data-collection</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Windows Health Monitoring profile in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a Windows Health Monitoring profile to collect endpoint analytics and software update events on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune. Use this data to recommend software, review startup performance, and fix support issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/windows-health-monitoring</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Performance Report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Explore the resource performance report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics for CPU and RAM insights, device performance analysis, and proactive endpoint analytics.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/resource-performance</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune manages users and devices, simplifies app management and automated policy deployment, and integrates with mobile threat defense. It connects to Managed Google Play, Apple tokens and certificates, and Teamviewer for remote assistance. Can use MDM or MAM to protect data, configure devices, and simplify access to company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Scopes in endpoint analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device scopes in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics with scope tags for custom device reporting and targeted insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/device-scopes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage account protection settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune endpoint security account protection policies to protect the identity and accounts of users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To enhance the security of your organization, set your users to run with standard permissions while Endpoint Privilege Management ensures those users can seamlessly run specified files with elevated rights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot managed device to Network Device Enrollment Service (NDES) communication in Microsoft Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot managed device to NDES server communication when using Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) certificate profiles to deploy certificates with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/certificates/troubleshoot-scep-certificate-device-to-ndes</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for iOS/iPadOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple device enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple device enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-device-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iVerify Enterprise Mobile Threat Defense with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up iVerify Enterprise Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/iverify-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up iVerify Enterprise Mobile Threat Defense with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up iVerify Enterprise Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/iverify-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned Macs into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use third-party certification authorities (CA) with SCEP in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, you can add a vendor or third-party certificate authority (CA) to issue certificates to mobile devices using the SCEP protocol. In this overview, a Microsoft Entra application gives Microsoft Intune permissions to validate certificates. Then, use the application ID, authentication key, and tenant ID of the Microsoft Entra application in the setup of your SCEP server to issue certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-authority-add-scep-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>