<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 11:09:16 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 11:09:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to Assist Users Authenticated by your Organization - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to improve your security posture with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-configure-security</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased device security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure devices with Microsoft Intune to support your Zero Trust journey.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-secure-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased tenant security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure your tenant with Microsoft Intune to support your Zero Trust journey.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-secure-tenant</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased data security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure data on devices with Microsoft Intune to support your Zero Trust journey.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-secure-data</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Cloud PKI for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>An overview of the Microsoft Cloud PKI service, available with Microsoft Intune Suite or as an Intune add-on.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Query in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device query in Microsoft Intune to get on-demand device state, run Kusto Query Language (KQL) queries, and troubleshoot devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/device-query</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>ServiceNow integration enables help desk staff, who are licensed to use Remote Help, to use ServiceNow to view incidents and details of the tech issue that an employee is facing from the Troubleshooting pane. This article also describes how to configure ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/service-now-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Cloud PKI root and issuing CA for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure a root and issuing CA for the Microsoft Cloud PKI service.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-configure-ca</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment models for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the deployment options for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-deployment</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android FOTA Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates on Android devices. A FOTA update can include software and security patches, feature updates, and other changes to the device's firmware.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/fota-updates-android</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring your own certificate authority with Cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a Microsoft Cloud PKI BYOCA issuing CA in Intune and anchor it to an on-premises or private CA.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-configure-byoca</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune cloud PKI fundamentals - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes fundamentals for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-fundamentals</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how anomaly detection in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics proactively monitors device health, detects issues, and provides actionable insights for IT admins.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/anomaly-detection</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Tunnel VPN with Android devices that don't enroll with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add support for Mobile Application Management (MAM) for Android to the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. Tunnel support for MAM expands access to your organizational resources for devices that can't or haven't enrolled with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-mam-android</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor issued PKI certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor reports for certificates issued via Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor your Endpoint Privilege Management policies for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View reports for managed and unmanaged file elevations when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delete issued PKI certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Delete certificates issued via Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Elevation Settings for Endpoint Privilege Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View guidance on how to manage the Endpoint Privilege Management client, including reporting level and default elevation response.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-elevation-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review the type of data that Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management collects - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View details about the type of data Endpoint Privilege Management can collect and store when used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-data-collection</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit logs for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get audit logs for Microsoft cloud public key infrastructure (PKI) activity in the admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-audit-logs</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Tunnel VPN with iOS/iPad devices that don't enroll with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add support for Mobile Application Management (MAM) for iOS to the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. Tunnel support for MAM expands access to your organizational resources for devices that can't or haven't enrolled with Microsoft Intune. Admins should use this article to create policies that support per-app VPN in line of business (LOB) apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-mam-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Intune sends to Zebra - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>List of data that Intune sends to Zebra.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/data-intune-sends-to-zebra</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known Issues for Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure policies that define how Endpoint Privilege Management functions in your tenant, and behaviors when elevating files to run in administrative context.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-known-issues</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrator to standard user - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for using Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrators to standard users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-transition-administrator-to-standard-user</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for deploying Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions for Endpoint Privilege Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A list of frequently asked questions for customers deploying Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-frequently-asked-questions</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zebra LifeGuard Over-the-Air Integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates for supported Zebra devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zebra-lifeguard-ota-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Analytics Troubleshooting and Frequently Asked Questions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find troubleshooting steps and FAQs for Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics, including endpoint analytics issues, data refresh, and dashboard customization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/advanced-analytics-troubleshooting-faqs</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an Enterprise App Catalog App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add an Enterprise App Catalog app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-enterprise-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover what Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics is, how it extends endpoint analytics with advanced device insights, proactive troubleshooting, and enhanced reporting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/advanced-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Scopes in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device scopes in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics with scope tags for custom device reporting and targeted insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/device-scopes</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Follow the steps to deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Microsoft Tunnel with Mobile Application Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Tunnel for MAM with Android and iOS devices. Tunnel for MAM expands access to your organizational resources for devices that aren't or can't enroll with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-mam</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Performance Report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Explore the resource performance report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics for CPU and RAM insights, device performance analysis, and proactive endpoint analytics.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/resource-performance-report</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot and monitor Remote Help for Microsoft Intune. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the troubleshooting and monitoring information for Remote Help with Microsoft Intune to ensure healthy and successful deployment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-troubleshoot-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Specialty devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides information about specialty devices and how can you manage them with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/specialty-devices-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics, enable advanced analytics features, and integrate endpoint analytics for proactive device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/advanced-analytics-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune Suite add-on capabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune Suite unifies a series of mission-critical advanced endpoint management and security capabilities. The capabilities of the suite are integrated with Microsoft 365 and Microsoft Security across endpoint platforms for both cloud and on-premises co-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-add-ons</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan for Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the requirements and capabilities of Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating elevation rules with Endpoint Privilege Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View guidance on how to create strong file elevation rules with Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-elevation-rules</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Query for Multiple Devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use device query for multiple devices in Microsoft Intune to run Kusto Query Language (KQL) queries, analyze device inventory, and gain cross-platform insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/device-query-multiple-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Device Timeline in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover the enhanced device timeline in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics for detailed device event history and advanced troubleshooting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/enhanced-device-timeline</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to Assist Authenticated Users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-use</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use EPM support approvals for file elevation requests with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage support approvals for elevation requests when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-support-approved</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan for Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics by understanding requirements, prerequisites, and best practices for endpoint analytics and advanced reporting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/advanced-analytics-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To enhance the security of your organization, set your users to run with standard permissions while Endpoint Privilege Management ensures those users can seamlessly run specified files with elevated rights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battery Health Report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how the battery health report in Microsoft Intune Advanced Analytics provides insights into device battery performance, degradation, and proactive replacement strategies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/battery-health</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan and Prepare for Endpoint Privilege Management Deployment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan your Endpoint Privilege Management deploying by understanding requirements, fundamentals, and security recommendations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review App Protection Policy Logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor results of your device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the device compliance dashboard to understand overall device compliance the per policy and per setting device compliance results.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Windows, Windows Holographic, and Surface Hub devices in Microsoft Intune. Check for compliance on the minimum and maximum operating system, set password restrictions and length, check for partner anti-virus (AV) solutions, enable encryption on data storage, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Intune security baselines for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that have preset and recommended configurations to the Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure device configuration profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or configure a device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Select the platform type, configure the settings, and add a scope tag. Learn more about applicability rules, and the policy refresh cycle times.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-create</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure compliance policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Description for configuring compliance policies</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-compliance-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune to remediate vulnerabilities found by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune Security Tasks to manage threats and vulnerabilities identified by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/atp-manage-vulnerabilities</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune capabilities that can help you protect your devices and data against unauthorized access and other threats.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-protect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies with tenant attached Configuration Manager devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use tenant attach to add Configuration Manager devices to Microsoft Intune and then deploy Intune policies to those devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/tenant-attach-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Enterprise security configurations for personally-owned work profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review example configurations of basic, enhanced, and high security for devices with Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/android-personally-owned-security-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device compliance security configurations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review example device compliance configurations of basic, enhanced, and high security for iOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/ios-ipados-device-compliance-security-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Defender for Endpoint Web protection on Android devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender for Endpoint web protection settings on Android devices managed by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-configure-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint detection and response policy. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security endpoint detection and response policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-edr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Enterprise security configurations for corporate-owned fully managed profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review example configurations of basic, enhanced, and high security for devices with Android Enterprise corporate-owned fully managed profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/android-fully-managed-security-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings you can manage with Intune Endpoint Protection profiles for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the available settings in Intune endpoint protection profiles for managed Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-protection-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Defender for Endpoint in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Install and configure Microsoft Tunnel Gateway on a Linux server to support Intune managed cloud-based devices in connecting to your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compliance in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about compliance, dependencies, and features in Microsoft Intune supporting data protection and regulatory requirements.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/compliance-in-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot-agents-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Scenario - Cloud-Managed Modern Desktop - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the guided scenario to set up and configure a basic Modern Desktop from the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-cloud-managed-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) with your Mobile Threat Defense partner to protect access to company resources based on device risk.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mobile-threat-defense</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Intune, including device compliance and onboarding status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune manages users and devices, simplifies app management and automated policy deployment, and integrates with mobile threat defense. It connects to Managed Google Play, Apple tokens and certificates, and Teamviewer for remote assistance. Can use MDM or MAM to protect data, configure devices, and simplify access to company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage endpoint security in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security node to manage device security and remediate issues for devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard and Configure Devices with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint via Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune, including connecting the products, onboarding devices, and assigning policies for compliance and risk level assessment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-integrate</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to Android DA devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a custom profile for Android device administrator (DA) devices in Microsoft Intune. Create a WiFi profile with a preshared key, create a per-app VPN profile, or allow/block apps for Samsung Knox Standard devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain join profile settings for Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a domain join device configuration profile for Microsoft Entra hybrid joined devices. Use this profile to deploy on-premises Active Directory domain information to devices provisioned with Windows Autopilot and Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/domain-join-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune product and capabilities documentation</title>
      <description>Learn more about how Microsoft Intune products and capabilities can help you secure, deploy, and manage users, apps, and endpoint devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, administrative templates (ADMX), and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect Intune account to managed Google Play account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect your Intune account to your Managed Google Play account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/connect-intune-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect device hardware info with the properties catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the properties catalog in Microsoft Intune view and collect enhanced device hardware info on Windows devices you manage with Intune. You can collect info like BIOS version, TPM status, disk info, memory details, and network adapter configurations. Use this information to get deeper visibility into your device inventory and troubleshoot issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Collect Diagnostics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Find lost devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Locate lost or stolen devices by using the locate device feature in Microsoft Intune. Get details on security and privacy information when using the locate device action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-locate</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Disable Activation Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune to disable Activation Lock on Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-activation-lock-disable</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Reset Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to reset a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-passcode-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Sync - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the device sync remote action in Intune to apply policy, app, and configuration updates to managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Send Custom Notifications - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work From Anywhere Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how the Work from Anywhere report in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides insights into remote productivity, device readiness, and user experience.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/work-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security, email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4 to deploy device configuration profiles as part of the minimum set of policies for your devices using Microsoft Intune. The starting point is to enable the firewall, install AV, scan for malware, install software updates, create a strong PIN policy, and create email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-configuration-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>