<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:05:58 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:05:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent to Manage Vulnerabilities</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify, prioritize, and remediate security vulnerabilities across your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/vulnerability-remediation-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Apps and Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how apps and configurations can be removed temporarily, then restored automatically or manually using the Remove apps and configuration device action with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/remove-apps-config</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center copy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices copy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO and deploy the configuration to your macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using Microsoft Entra ID with the Secure Enclave, smart card, or password authentication methods. You create a settings catalog policy to configure the settings. This article is a step-by-step guide to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Update Policies for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure software update policies for Apple devices using Apple's Declarative Device Management (DDM) model. Improve security, reduce user disruption, and ensure compliance with reliable, automated updates across your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/updates/apple</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with the Device Offboarding Agent</title>
      <description>Learn about the Device Offboarding Agent in Microsoft Intune, its prerequisites, how it works, and how to configure it.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/device-offboarding-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to Assist Users Authenticated by your Organization - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Collect Diagnostics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan for Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the requirements and capabilities of Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eSIM configuration of a download server - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about configuration of an eSIM Download Server from Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/esim-device-configuration-download-server</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work From Anywhere Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how the Work from Anywhere report in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides insights into remote productivity, device readiness, and user experience.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/work-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Remediation Agent Overview and Set Up</title>
      <description>Learn about the Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune, its prerequisites, how it works, and how to set it up. The agent uses AI to identify and prioritize vulnerability remediation based on Microsoft Defender Vulnerability Management data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/vulnerability-remediation-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Review Agent Overview</title>
      <description>Learn about the Change Review Agent in Microsoft Intune, its prerequisites, and how it works.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/change-review-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable eSIM data connections in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or use eSIM to get internet and data access using different data plans. In Intune, add or import activation codes, and then assign these activation codes using a configuration profile. You can also monitor the eSIM profiles and check the status of the eSIM-enabled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/esim-device-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Actions – Wipe, Lock, Locate, and More - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how to use Microsoft Intune to remotely manage, wipe, lock, restart, and secure Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, Windows, and ChromeOS devices. Learn about available remote actions, prerequisites, and bulk actions for IT admins.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Policy Configuration Agent and set it up</title>
      <description>Learn about the Policy Configuration Agent in Microsoft Intune, its prerequisites, how it works, and how to set it up. The agent is a generative AI feature that helps create Intune policies based on uploaded documents or benchmarks. The Policy Configuration Agent is a feature of Security Copilot in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/policy-configuration-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Follow the steps to deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot and monitor Remote Help for Microsoft Intune. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the troubleshooting and monitoring information for Remote Help with Microsoft Intune to ensure healthy and successful deployment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-troubleshoot-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to Assist Authenticated Users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-use</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable autodiscovery of Intune enrollment server - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Simplify enrollment for users by enabling automatic discovery of the Intune enrollment server.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-create-cname</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows Backup for Organizations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows backup and restore in Intune for employees or students.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-backup-restore</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View enrollment reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor and troubleshoot issues with enrollment restrictions and enrollment status page assignments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/view-enrollment-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot Agents in Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how Microsoft Security Copilot enhances Microsoft Intune through AI-powered security agents. Learn about available agents and explore their capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Change Review Agent</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Change Review Agent in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/change-review-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assignment filter properties and operators reference - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference guide for device and app properties, operators, and rule syntax when creating assignment filters in Microsoft Intune. Includes examples and supported values.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-device-properties</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device platform restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Restrict personally owned devices, and specific device platforms and OS versions from enrolling in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/create-device-platform-restrictions</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration Policies for Intune App SDK Managed Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure policies for Intune App SDK managed apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-managed-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assignment Filter Performance Tips for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Optimize Microsoft Intune performance with assignment filters. Learn to use virtual groups, reuse groups, and apply filters effectively. Improve policy deployment speed with incremental group changes, and use assignment filters to include and exclude.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-performance-recommendations</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse Collections - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune Data Warehouse collections provide details related to the Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/intune-data-warehouse-collections</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platforms and policy types supported by assignment filters - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn which apps, compliance policies, and device configuration profiles and their platforms support assignment filters in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-supported-workloads</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assignment filter reports &amp; troubleshooting - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use assignment filter reports to troubleshoot policies in Microsoft Intune. View filter evaluation results, resolve conflicts, and understand include vs. exclude modes.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-reports-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create assignment filters in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create assignment filters in Microsoft Intune to target policies based on device properties like OS version or manufacturer. Learn to create, update, and delete filters for managed devices and apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devices - Intune Data Warehouse - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference article for the Devices category of entity collections in the Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Wipe - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wipe, or factory reset, devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Device Offboarding Agent</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Device Offboarding Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify and offboard devices that are no longer in use.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/device-offboarding-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Multi Admin Approval in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Multi Admin Approval to protect your tenant against the use of compromised administrative accounts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/multi-admin-approval</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune contributes to a strong Zero Trust strategy and architecture.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/zero-trust-with-microsoft-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune to remediate vulnerabilities found by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune Security Tasks to manage threats and vulnerabilities identified by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/atp-manage-vulnerabilities</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Admin Tasks - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the centralized Admin tasks view in Microsoft Intune to manage tasks across capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/admin-tasks</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Intune features overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Security Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues and query devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/security-copilot-agents-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Policy Configuration Agent to create policies</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Policy Configuration Agent in Microsoft Intune to create policies. You can create policies on files you uploaded, natural language prompts, or industry baselines. The Policy Configuration Agent is a feature of Security Copilot in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/policy-configuration-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use EPM support approvals for file elevation requests with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage support approvals for elevation requests when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-support-approved</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Apps to Groups in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign an Intune app to groups of users or devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovered Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand details about the detected apps that Intune found on a device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-discovered-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iVerify Enterprise Mobile Threat Defense with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up iVerify Enterprise Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/iverify-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) with your Mobile Threat Defense partner to protect access to company resources based on device risk.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mobile-threat-defense</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Protection Policies Overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune Management Extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Web Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding web apps (client-server applications) to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/web-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of Intune App SDK - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune App SDK is available for both the iOS and Android platforms, and enables mobile app management features with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android Developer Integration and Testing Guide - MAM Integration Essentials - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand MAM integration essentials to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase4</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS Developer Guide - Web-View Features - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Web-view features</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase7</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported Microsoft Intune Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides lists of support partner and Microsoft apps that are commonly used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-supported-intune-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the App Lifecycle for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the managed apps lifecycle in Microsoft Intune. The app lifecycle involves adding, deploying, configuring, protecting, and retiring apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-lifecycle</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for iOS/iPadOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned Macs into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android Developer Integration and Testing Guide - Get Started With MAM - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get started with Intune before incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase3</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android Developer Integration and Testing Guide - App Participation Features - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand App participation features when incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase7</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about Microsoft Intune's unified endpoint management and security solutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune product and capabilities documentation</title>
      <description>Learn more about how Microsoft Intune products and capabilities can help you secure, deploy, and manage users, apps, and endpoint devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS Developer Guide - Intune SDK Integration Into Your iOS App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Intune SDK integration into your iOS app</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase3</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows compatibility reports for Windows updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the app and driver compatibility reports for Windows devices before you deploy Intune policies for feature updates or update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-compatibility-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrap iOS Apps With the Intune App Wrapping Tool - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wrap your iOS apps without changing the code of the app itself. Prepare the apps so you can apply mobile app management policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-wrapper-prepare-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-supervised-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Update Supersedence for Enterprise App Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to update an Enterprise App Catalog app using supersedence with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-eam-supersedence</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an Enterprise App Catalog App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add an Enterprise App Catalog app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-enterprise-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Include and Exclude App Assignments in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to include and exclude app assignments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-inc-exl-assignments</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Group to Manage Users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to create a group based on existing users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-group</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use third-party certification authorities (CA) with SCEP in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, you can add a vendor or third-party certificate authority (CA) to issue certificates to mobile devices using the SCEP protocol. In this overview, a Microsoft Entra application gives Microsoft Intune permissions to validate certificates. Then, use the application ID, authentication key, and tenant ID of the Microsoft Entra application in the setup of your SCEP server to issue certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-authority-add-scep-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect Intune account to managed Google Play account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect your Intune account to your Managed Google Play account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/connect-intune-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about the Microsoft Tunnel VPN solution for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway, a VPN server for Intune that runs on Linux. With Microsoft Tunnel, cloud-based devices you manage with Intune can reach your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Intune data with natural language and take action - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, use Explorer to query your data in natural language and run built-in queries that match your request. Copilot summarizes the results, and provides recommendations and actions based on the query results. You can also create policies that target users and groups in the query results. Use this feature to explore your Intune data, troubleshoot issues, and create custom reports.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-explorer</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control AI features on Android Enterprise devices</title>
      <description>Using Microsoft Intune, you can manage and restrict AI usage on Android devices enrolled in Intune. This guide provides lists the steps in Intune to block AI apps, websites, screen-driven experiences, on-device AI services, and OEM-specific AI features. You can manage Microsoft Copilot, Google Gemini, Samsung Galaxy AI, claude.ai, ChatGPT, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/ai/manage-ai-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Protection Policy Settings for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy (APP) settings for MAM on Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common tasks and features in the settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure common features. You can create a Universal Print policy, configure Microsoft Edge and Google Chrome web browsers, and use built in settings instead of plist files for macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-common-features</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign Managed Google Play Apps to Android Enterprise Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how to synchronize and assign apps to Android Enterprise devices from the Managed Google Play store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-managed-home-screen-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android configuration list for Intune settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune settings catalog to add, configure, or restrict features on Android devices. This article lists and describes the settings you can configure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple User Enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple User Enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-user-enrollment-supported-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Managed Google Play apps on Intune-managed devices - Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot common issues with Managed Google Play for Android Enterprise devices enrolled in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/app-management/troubleshoot-google-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 02:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS device enrollment guide for  Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll macOS devices using device enrollment, automated device enrollment (DEP), and Apple Configurator enrollment options in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device enrollment guide for  Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll iOS and iPadOS devices using user and device enrollment, automated device enrollment (DEP), and Apple Configurator in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-passcode</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor your Endpoint Privilege Management policies for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View reports for managed and unmanaged file elevations when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple Volume-Purchased Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to improve your security posture with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-configure-security</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased device security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure devices with Microsoft Intune to support your Zero Trust journey.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-secure-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>