<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:22:36 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:22:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Administrative templates in Microsoft Intune to create groups of settings for Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a device configuration profile. You can control Office programs, Microsoft Edge, access OneDrive, use remote desktop, enable Auto-Play, set power management settings, use HTTP printing, control user sign-in, and change the event log size.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure device configuration profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or configure a device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Select the platform type, configure the settings, and add a scope tag. Learn more about applicability rules, and the policy refresh cycle times.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-create</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict devices features using policy in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a device configuration profile to restrict features on Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, AOSP, macOS, iOS, iPadOS, and Windows 10/11 client devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, Windows Information Protection, administrative templates, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Windows BIOS using configuration MDM policy</title>
      <description>Learn more about the BIOS configuration profile that can manage traditional BIOS settings in Microsoft Intune. You use an OEM tool to create a configuration file with the settings. You deploy an OEM Win32 app to the devices to read the configuration file and BIOS passwords. Then, you create a BIOS configuration policy in Intune to add the configuration file and assign the policy to your devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/bios-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Windows BIOS features using DFCI MDM policies</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Device Firmware Configuration Interface (DFCI) profile to manage UEFI settings in Microsoft Intune. To use DFCI profiles, create Microsoft Entra security groups, the Windows Autopilot deployment profile, and the Enrollment State Page profile.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-firmware-configuration-interface-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Defender Application Control on HoloLens 2 devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure the Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC) CSP to allow or block apps from opening on HoloLens 2 devices in Microsoft Intune. Use PowerShell and a custom configuration profile.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-profile-hololens</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Import custom and third-party partner ADMX templates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can add, upload, or import custom and third-party partner ADMX and ADML files in Microsoft Intune. When they're imported, create a device configuration profile and assign the profile to your Windows 10/11 client devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-import-custom</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions with policies and profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Common questions, answers, and scenarios with device policies and profiles in Microsoft Intune. Learn more about profile changes not applying to users or devices, how long it takes for new policies to deploy, which settings apply when there are conflicts, what happens when you delete or remove a profile, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings for Windows devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a custom profile to use the OMA-URI settings for devices running Windows 10/11 client in Microsoft Intune. Use a custom profile to add custom settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use custom device settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a profile to use custom settings for Windows 10/11 client, Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, macOS, and iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign device profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to assign device configuration profiles and policies to users and devices. Learn how to exclude groups from a profile assignment in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See device configuration policies with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See and manage the device configuration policy details in Microsoft Intune. Look at a graphical chart of the number of devices assigned to a policy, and see which devices have policies assigned or deployed. Can also troubleshoot policies that have conflict settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can use Security Copilot to get information about your Intune data, including devices, apps, policies, and groups managed in Intune. You can also compare policies, get device specific details, and get target info for policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Intune features overview</title>
      <description>Microsoft Security Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues and query devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Intune data with natural language and take action</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, use Explorer to query your data in natural language and run built-in queries that match your request. Copilot summarizes the results, and provides recommendations and actions based on the query results. You can also create policies that target users and groups in the query results. Use this feature to explore your Intune data, troubleshoot issues, and create custom reports.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-explorer</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copilot in Intune shows device information and helps troubleshoot</title>
      <description>Microsoft Security Copilot in Intune can help you get information about your devices, compare devices, and get error information. Use this information to help you manage and troubleshoot device issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ for Microsoft Copilot in Intune</title>
      <description>Get answers to common questions when using Copilot in Microsoft Intune, including accessing Copilot, licensing, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-faq</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Properties catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Properties catalog policy to manage Device Inventory settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Intune security baselines for Windows devices</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that have preset and recommended configurations to the Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Categorize devices into groups in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Categorize Intune-managed devices into groups for easier management in the admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-group-mapping</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run remote actions on devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to run remote actions on Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Windows devices. You can reset the password, lock the device, wipe or reset the OS, scan for viruses, and more. Use this feature to remotely manage devices and have help desk run common tasks.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use multiple administrative approvals in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure multi-admin approval to protect your tenant against the use of compromised administrative accounts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/multi-admin-approval</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor security baselines deployed by Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor device and per-setting results of security baselines you deploy with Microsoft Intune, and identify conflicts for devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft HoloLens 2 advanced security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune advanced security baseline for Microsoft HoloLens 2. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-hololens2-advanced</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft Edge security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline version 112 and later, for the Microsoft Edge browser. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-v2-edge-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft 365 Apps for Enterprise security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Office apps. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-v2-office-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Edge security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Edge browser. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft HoloLens 2 standard security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune standard security baseline for Microsoft HoloLens 2. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-hololens2-standard</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security baseline policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that establish a default and recommended security postures on Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device restriction settings for Android in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>On Android Enterprise or Android for Work devices owned by your organization, you can restrict settings on the device using Microsoft Intune. Allow copy and paste, notifications, app permissions, data sharing, password length, sign in failures, use fingerprint to unlock, reuse passwords, and enable bluetooth sharing of work contacts. Configure devices as a dedicated device kiosk to run one app, or multiple apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Windows 365 Cloud PC security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Windows 365 Cloud PC. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-windows-365</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Default configuration of Intune's Windows security baselines - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the default setting configuration of the various Microsoft Intune security baselines for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-mdm-all</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android configuration list for Intune settings catalog</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune settings catalog to add, configure, or restrict features on Android devices. This article lists and describes the settings you can configure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review app protection policy logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 11:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased security</title>
      <description>Learn how to improve your security posture with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-configure-security</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 02:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the settings catalog to configure DDM software updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Apple's declarative device management (DDM) settings to install a specific update by an enforced deadline. This feature uses the settings catalog to configure managed software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS and managed macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/managed-software-updates-ios-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to configure the Intune Company Portal apps, Company Portal website, and Intune app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can configure the Intune Company Portal apps, Company Portal website, and Intune app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operating systems and browsers supported by Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Lists supported device platforms and browsers for Intune device management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/supported-devices-browsers</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment models for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the deployment options for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-deployment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor your Endpoint Privilege Management policies for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View reports for managed and unmanaged file elevations when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Elevation Settings for Endpoint Privilege Management</title>
      <description>View guidance on how to manage the Endpoint Privilege Management client, including reporting level and default elevation response.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-elevation-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review the type of data that Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management collects</title>
      <description>View details about the type of data Endpoint Privilege Management can collect and store when used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-data-collection</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known Issues for Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure policies that define how Endpoint Privilege Management functions in your tenant, and behaviors when elevating files to run in administrative context.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-known-issues</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrator to standard user</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for using Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrators to standard users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-transition-administrator-to-standard-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for deploying Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions for Endpoint Privilege Management</title>
      <description>A list of frequently asked questions for customers deploying Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-frequently-asked-questions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating elevation rules with Endpoint Privilege Management</title>
      <description>View guidance on how to create strong file elevation rules with Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-elevation-rules</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use EPM support approvals for file elevation requests with Intune</title>
      <description>Manage support approvals for elevation requests when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-support-approved</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To enhance the security of your organization, set your users to run with standard permissions while Endpoint Privilege Management ensures those users can seamlessly run specified files with elevated rights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use reusable groups of settings policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage groups of settings for Intune profiles as a single object and then add that settings group object to multiple profile instances. Later changes you make to the settings groups  automatically apply to each profile that includes the reusable settings group.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/reusable-settings-groups</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan and Prepare for Endpoint Privilege Management Deployment</title>
      <description>Plan your Endpoint Privilege Management deploying by understanding requirements, fundamentals, and security recommendations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center copy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices copy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Windows 10, Windows 11, Windows Holographic, and Surface Hub devices in Microsoft Intune. Check for compliance on the minimum and maximum operating system, set password restrictions and length, check for partner anti-virus (AV) solutions, enable encryption on data storage, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure compliance policies with actions for noncompliance in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your compliance policies with one or more actions for noncompliance to protect devices and your organization from unprotected devices. Actions can remotely lock devices, send email or notifications to device users, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/actions-for-noncompliance</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create device compliance policies for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/create-compliance-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for iOS/iPadOS that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create discovery scripts for custom compliance policy in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create scripts for Linux or Windows devices to discover the settings you define as custom compliance settings for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-custom-script</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use app-based Conditional Access policies with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using app-based Conditional Access policies with Microsoft Intune for both enrolled and unenrolled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/app-based-conditional-access-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a JSON file for custom compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create the JSON file that defines custom settings and values for use with device compliance policies in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-custom-json</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View the Android device administrator compliance settings for Microsoft Intune compliance policies</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings that are available for Android device administrator devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android (AOSP) compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Android (AOSP) that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android-aosp</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compliance for Windows Subsystem for Linux</title>
      <description>Evaluate WSL attributes on a host device for compliance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-wsl</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 8.1 compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Windows 8.1 that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows-8-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Linux that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Enterprise compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune. Set password rules, choose a minimum or maximum operating system version, restrict specific apps, prevent reusing password, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor results of your device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the device compliance dashboard to understand overall device compliance the per policy and per setting device compliance results.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up app-based Conditional Access policies with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Conditional Access policies that work with Intune app protection policies</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/app-based-conditional-access-intune-create</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use custom compliance settings for Linux and Windows devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage custom compliance settings for Linux and Windows devices by using JSON files and discovery scripts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-use-custom-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for macOS devices that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-mac-os</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up device-based Conditional Access policies with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure a device-based Conditional Access policy that uses device status from a Microsoft Intune device compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/create-conditional-access-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenarios for using Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Conditional Access is commonly used with Intune compliance policy for devices and apps</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-intune-common-ways-use</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Jamf Pro Cloud Connector to integrate Jamf Pro with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Jamf Cloud Connector to integrate Jamf Pro with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-jamf-cloud-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to detect and fix support issues</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune compliance policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Combine Conditional Access with Intune compliance policies to define the requirements that users and devices must meet before gaining access your organizations resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Tunnel VPN with iOS/iPad devices that don't enroll with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add support for Mobile Application Management (MAM) for iOS to the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. Tunnel support for MAM expands access to your organizational resources for devices that can't or haven't enrolled with Microsoft Intune. Admins should use this article to create policies that support per-app VPN in line of business (LOB) apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-mam-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune compliance and Microsoft Entra Conditional Access policies with Jamf Pro - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Intune compliance policies and Microsoft Entra Conditional Access to help secure Jamf-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-assign-jamf</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Graph API - Reports and properties</title>
      <description>Learn about Intune reports and properties provided via Graph API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-available-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add PowerShell scripts to Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and run PowerShell scripts, assign the script policy to Microsoft Entra groups, and use reports to monitor the scripts. See the steps to delete scripts you add on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune. Read common issues and resolutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/powershell-scripts</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually configure Jamf Pro integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manually configure Jamf Pro integration with Intune when you can't use the Jamf Cloud Connector.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-integrate-jamf</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of Microsoft Intune device compliance, including tenant-wide compliance policy settings and device compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-compliance-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retire or wipe devices using Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Retire or wipe a device on an Android, Android work profile, AOSP, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, or Windows device using Microsoft Intune. Also delete a device from Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/devices-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for US government deployments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the list of US government endpoint URLs that Intune needs and requires. Allow the ports, IP addresses, and endpoint URLs in your proxy server configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-us-government-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network access control integration with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Network access control (NAC) solutions check enrollment and compliance for devices with Intune. NAC includes certain behaviors and works with Conditional Access. See the steps to get onboarded, and get a list of partner solutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/network-access-control-integrate</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-managed-home-screen-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to import and analyze group policies</title>
      <description>Import and analyze your group policy objects using the Group Policy analytics tool. See the policies that are supported and aren't supported in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/group-policy-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate your imported group policy to a policy in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>After you import your Windows group policy objects in Microsoft Intune, use the migrate feature to transfer your GPOs to a Settings Catalog policy. This policy uses your imported GPOs, and can be assigned to users and devices managed by your organizations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/group-policy-analytics-migrate</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security, email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4 to deploy device configuration profiles as part of the minimum set of policies for your devices using Microsoft Intune. The starting point is to enable the firewall, install AV, scan for malware, install software updates, create a strong PIN policy, and create email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-configuration-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Store apps to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Store apps to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>