<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:04:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign a role to an Intune administrator - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign a built-in or custom role to a user in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/assign-role</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the prerequisites for installation and use of the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. These include Linux servers, network, and firewall configurations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot-agents-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to set up and use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent for Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/vulnerability-remediation-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO and deploy the configuration to your macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using Microsoft Entra ID with the Secure Enclave, smart card, or password authentication methods. You create a settings catalog policy to configure the settings. This article is a step-by-step guide to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign device profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to assign device configuration profiles and policies to users and devices. Learn how to exclude groups from a profile assignment in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Administrative templates in Microsoft Intune to create groups of settings for Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a device configuration profile. You can control Office programs, Microsoft Edge, access OneDrive, use remote desktop, enable Auto-Play, set power management settings, use HTTP printing, control user sign-in, and change the event log size.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Properties catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Properties catalog policy to manage Device Inventory settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to import and analyze group policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Import and analyze your group policy objects using the Group Policy analytics tool. See the policies that are supported and aren't supported in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/group-policy-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Universal Print policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to create a Universal Print policy for Windows 10/11 client devices. The policy automatically installs printers on your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-printer-provisioning</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure device configuration profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or configure a device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Select the platform type, configure the settings, and add a scope tag. Learn more about applicability rules, and the policy refresh cycle times.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-create</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure macOS Enterprise SSO app extension with MDMs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Microsoft Enterprise single sign-on (SSO) app extension plug-in. Add or create an macOS device profile using the SSO app extension in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-macos-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict devices features using policy in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a device configuration profile to restrict features on Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, AOSP, macOS, iOS, iPadOS, and Windows 10/11 client devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Wi-Fi profile for devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the steps to create a Wi-Fi device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Create profiles for Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, Android kiosk, iOS, iPadOS, macOS, Windows 10/11, and Windows Holographic for Business. Use these profiles to create a WiFi connection to use certificates, choose an EAP type, select an authentication method, enable a proxy, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared or multi-user Windows device settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add and use Windows 10/11 and Windows Holographic for Business devices that are shared, or used by multiple users in Microsoft Intune. See a list of all the settings and what they do on the devices, including Microsoft HoloLens. Control guest accounts, manage accounts and delete inactive accounts, allow or prevent saving to local storage, set power and sleep options, choose when updates are installed, and use devices in education environments in a device configuration profile.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/shared-user-device-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, administrative templates, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Windows BIOS using configuration MDM policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the BIOS configuration profile that can manage traditional BIOS settings in Microsoft Intune. You use an OEM tool to create a configuration file with the settings. You deploy an OEM Win32 app to the devices to read the configuration file and BIOS passwords. Then, you create a BIOS configuration policy in Intune to add the configuration file and assign the policy to your devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/bios-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add VPN settings to devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>On Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, macOS, and Windows devices, use built-in settings to create virtual private network (VPN) connections in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate your imported group policy to a policy in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>After you import your Windows group policy objects in Microsoft Intune, use the migrate feature to transfer your GPOs to a Settings Catalog policy. This policy uses your imported GPOs, and can be assigned to users and devices managed by your organizations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/group-policy-analytics-migrate</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiosk settings for Windows and Holographic devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your Windows 10/11 and Windows Holographic for Business devices as single-app and multi-app kiosks, customize the start menu, add apps, show the task bar, and configure a web browser in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kiosk-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See device configuration policies with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See and manage the device configuration policy details in Microsoft Intune. Look at a graphical chart of the number of devices assigned to a policy, and see which devices have policies assigned or deployed. Can also troubleshoot policies that have conflict settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up per-app VPN for iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the prerequisites, create a group for the virtual private network (VPN) users, add a SCEP certificate profile, configure a per-app VPN profile, and assign some apps to the VPN profile in Microsoft Intune on iOS/iPadOS devices. Also lists the steps to verify the VPN connection on the device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-setting-configure-per-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Import Wi-Fi settings for Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Export Wi-Fi settings from a Windows device as an XML file using the network shell (netsh wlan) command. Then, import this file in Intune to create a Wi-Fi profile for devices running Windows 10/11 and Windows Holographic for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-settings-import-windows-8-1</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create iOS/iPadOS or macOS device profile with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create an iOS, iPadOS, or macOS device profile. Configure settings for AirPrint, layout of the home screen, app notifications, shared device, single sign-on, and web content filter settings in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-features-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Wi-Fi profile with preshared key in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a custom profile to create a Wi-Fi profile with a preshared key (PSK), and get sample XML code for Android, Android Enterprise, Windows, and EAP-based Wi-Fi profiles in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-profile-shared-key</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Windows BIOS features using DFCI MDM policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Device Firmware Configuration Interface (DFCI) profile to manage UEFI settings in Microsoft Intune. To use DFCI profiles, create Microsoft Entra security groups, the Windows Autopilot deployment profile, and the Enrollment State Page profile.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-firmware-configuration-interface-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set permissions to Managed Home Screen using Android Enterprise OEMConfig - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add the Samsung Knox Service Plugin, Zebra OEMConfig Powered by MX, and Legacy Zebra OEMConfig apps to Intune, and use the app schemas to configure permissions for the Managed Home Screen (MHS) app on Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/oemconfig-managed-home-screen-permissions-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eSIM configuration of a download server - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about configuration of an eSIM Download Server from Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/esim-device-configuration-download-server</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure 802.1x wired network settings for macOS and Windows devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create or add a wired network device configuration profile or policy using the IEEE 802.1X standard for macOS, Windows 10, and Windows 11 devices and computers. See the different settings, add certificates, choose an EAP type, and select an authentication method in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wired-networks-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Export iOS and iPadOS settings from Apple Configurator or Apple Profile Manager tools, and then import these settings into Microsoft Intune. These settings can create, use, and control custom settings and features on iOS/iPadOS devices. This custom profile can then be assigned or distributed to iOS/iPadOS devices in your organization to create a baseline or standard.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create macOS system and kernel extensions with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about system extensions and kernel extensions for macOS devices. In Microsoft Intune, add or create a device configuration policy that configures kernel extensions. In the extension, you can allow user override, add a team identifier, and add a bundle and team identifier.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kernel-extensions-overview-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy OEMConfig profiles to Zebra devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to create and deploy multiple OEMConfig device configuration profiles on Zebra devices running Android Enterprise. Use Zebra actions and steps to order your profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/oemconfig-zebra-android-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create an email device profile for iOS/iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune to create an email device profile so iOS/iPadOS devices can securely connect to company organization email.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/quickstart-email-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allow or block apps for Samsung Knox Standard devices</title>
      <description>Create a custom profile to allow and block apps for Samsung Knox Standard Android device administrator devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/samsung-knox-apps-allow-block</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom per-app VPN profile for Android DA in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a custom profile for per-app VPN profiles on Android device administrator with the Pulse Secure or Citrix VPN connection types in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/android-pulse-secure-per-app-vpn</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Defender Application Control on HoloLens 2 devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure the Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC) CSP to allow or block apps from opening on HoloLens 2 devices in Microsoft Intune. Use PowerShell and a custom configuration profile.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-profile-hololens</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add or configure education settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Take a Test app in a device configuration profile on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune. Create a configuration profile using the Education settings, and enter a test app URL, choose how users sign-in, monitor the screen during the test, and allow or prevent text suggestions during the test.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/education-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to Linux devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add Bash scripts to create a custom Linux profile in Microsoft Intune. Use the script to create, use, and control custom settings and features on Linux devices. This custom profile can then be assigned or distributed to Linux devices in your organization to create a baseline or standard.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable eSIM data connections in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or use eSIM to get internet and data access using different data plans. In Intune, add or import activation codes, and then assign these activation codes using a configuration profile. You can also monitor the eSIM profiles and check the status of the eSIM-enabled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/esim-device-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common tasks and features in the settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure common features. You can create a Universal Print policy, configure Microsoft Edge and Google Chrome web browsers, and use built in settings instead of plist files for macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-common-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Microsoft 365 apps with the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to update Microsoft 365 apps to the latest version, and choose how frequently Office checks for updates. See the device registry keys that are updated when an Intune policy to Office update is applied.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-update-office</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict USB devices using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to restrict USB devices, including thumb drives, flash drives, USB cameras, and more. Use other settings to allow specific USB devices on Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-restrict-usb</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Delivery Optimization settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure device configuration policy to manage Delivery Optimization settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/delivery-optimization-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade Windows editions or switch S mode using Intune policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to upgrade Windows 10/11 client devices to a different edition, or switch S mode. Administrators can use a device configuration profile to upgrade Windows client Professional to Windows client Enterprise, and switch out of S mode. See the supported upgrade paths for Windows 10/11 Pro, N Edition, Education, Cloud, Enterprise, Core, and Holographic.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/edition-upgrade-configure-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions with policies and profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Common questions, answers, and scenarios with device policies and profiles in Microsoft Intune. Learn more about profile changes not applying to users or devices, how long it takes for new policies to deploy, which settings apply when there are conflicts, what happens when you delete or remove a profile, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Import custom and third-party partner ADMX templates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can add, upload, or import custom and third-party partner ADMX and ADML files in Microsoft Intune. When they're imported, create a device configuration profile and assign the profile to your Windows 10/11 client devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-import-custom</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single sign-on (SSO) for iOS/iPadOS and macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of Microsoft Enterprise SSO plug-in in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers. The Enterprise SSO plug-in is available on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-ios-ipados-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings for Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a custom profile to use the OMA-URI settings for devices running Windows 10/11 client in Microsoft Intune. Use a custom profile to add custom settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Zebra Mobility Extensions on Android devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and use Zebra devices running Android with Zebra Mobility Extensions (MX). See all the steps, including install the Company Portal app, sideload the app, assign device administrator role, create a StageNow profile, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/android-zebra-mx-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use OEMConfig on Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and use devices running Android Enterprise with OEMConfig. See all the steps, including an overview, see the prerequisites, create the configuration profile in Intune, and see a list of supported OEMConfig apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/android-oem-configuration-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add preference file settings to macOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add an xml or plist file that includes key information about your app. Use a preference file device configuration profile to change key information in the property list file, and assign it to your macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/preference-file-settings-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Microsoft Edge policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create settings using the settings catalog to configure Microsoft Edge on Windows and macOS devices. Using Microsoft Intune, you can configure group policy settings, and deploy these settings to Microsoft Edge users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-configure-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to macOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Import custom macOS settings into Microsoft Intune. These settings can create, use, and control custom settings and features on macOS devices. This custom profile can then be assigned or distributed to macOS devices in your organization to create a baseline or standard.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure email settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create an email device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune, and deploy this profile to Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, and Windows devices. Use email profiles to configure common email settings, including a Microsoft Exchange email server. Add authentication methods to connect to corporate email on devices you manage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/email-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walkthrough-Create a settings catalog policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This tutorial or walkthrough steps through creating and comparing an on-premises Administrative Templates (ADMX) Group Policy and Microsoft Intune cloud-based settings catalog policy. It shows similar settings in on-premises and the Intune settings catalog to create and manage policies for Office, Windows, and Microsoft Edge on Windows 10/11 client devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/tutorial-settings-catalog-group-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Windows Network Boundary profile in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a Windows Network Boundary policy to Windows devices using Microsoft Intune. Add trusted sites, trusted domains, IPv4 and IPv6 ranges, and proxy servers to a device configuration policy. Microsoft Defender Application Guard in Microsoft Edge trusts sites in this boundary.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/network-boundary-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platform SSO scenarios for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure common Platform SSO scenarios for macOS devices. You can enable Kerberos SSO to on-premises Active Directory and cloud-based Microsoft Entra ID, use Touch ID biometric policy with Secure Enclave authentication, and enable SSO on non-Microsoft apps. You can also configure end user experience settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-scenarios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Windows Health Monitoring profile in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a Windows Health Monitoring profile to collect endpoint analytics and software update events on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune. Use this data to recommend software, review startup performance, and fix support issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/windows-health-monitoring</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use StageNow logs on Android Zebra devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See common issues and resolutions when using StageNow on Android devices with Microsoft Intune. Also learn how to get logs, and see examples of how to read the logs for success or errors.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/android-zebra-mx-logs-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain join profile settings for Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a domain join device configuration profile for Microsoft Entra hybrid joined devices. Use this profile to deploy on-premises Active Directory domain information to devices provisioned with Windows Autopilot and Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/domain-join-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use custom device settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a profile to use custom settings for Windows 10/11 client, Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, macOS, and iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure iOS/iPadOS Enterprise SSO app extension with MDMs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Microsoft Enterprise single sign-on (SSO) plug-in. Add or create an iOS or iPadOS device configuration profile using the Microsoft Enterprise SSO plug-in app extension in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-ios-ipados-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to Android DA devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a custom profile for Android device administrator (DA) devices in Microsoft Intune. Create a WiFi profile with a preshared key, create a per-app VPN profile, or allow/block apps for Samsung Knox Standard devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policies overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple volume-purchased apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft 365 Apps to Windows 10/11 devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to install Microsoft 365 apps on Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-office365</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign apps to groups in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign an Intune app to groups of users or devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App configuration policies for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use app configuration policies on an iOS/iPadOS or Android device in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Win32 app supersedence - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Win32 app supersedence with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-supersedence</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Win32 apps in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the most common methods to troubleshoot Win32 app issues with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add a Windows line-of-business app to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add a Windows line-of-business (LOB) app using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how your workforce can manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app to their PC from the Microsoft Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows app deployment by using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Windows 10/11 app deployment scenarios available with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-windows-10-app-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add web apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding web apps (client-server applications) to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/web-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use shell scripts on macOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create, assign, monitor, and troubleshoot shell scripts for macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/macos-shell-scripts</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add app configuration policies for managed Android Enterprise devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use app configuration policies in Microsoft Intune to supply settings when users run a Managed Google Play app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-use-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join your cloud-native endpoints to Microsoft Entra - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>When moving to or using cloud-native endpoints, use Microsoft Entra joined endpoints. When your endpoints are joined to Microsoft Entra, you can use Windows Autopilot to provision or get devices ready for organization use. Learn more about the benefits to IT admins and end-users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/azure-ad-joined-hybrid-azure-ad-joined</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an unmanaged macOS PKG app to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add an unmanaged macOS PKG app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/macos-unmanaged-pkg</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data protection for Windows MAM - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable protected MAM access to org data using Windows MAM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/protect-mam-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Include and exclude app assignments in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to include and exclude app assignments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-inc-exl-assignments</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add iOS store apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding iOS store apps to Microsoft Intune. You can assign apps using this method if the apps are free of charge in the App Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign an app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to add and assign an app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-add-assign-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Windows virtual machines with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the general guidelines for using Windows 10/11 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-10-virtual-machines</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policies for Microsoft 365 apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the policies available for Microsoft 365 apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-office-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android to ensure collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-office</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration policies for Intune App SDK managed apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure policies for Intune App SDK managed apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-managed-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Android store apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add Android store apps from the Google Play store to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Microsoft Intune management agent for macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Microsoft Intune management agent for macOS.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-macos-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Application Management (MAM) and Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the available features when deciding to use Mobile Application Management (MAM) and/or Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles for personal or BYOD Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/android-deployment-scenarios-app-protection-work-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Google Chrome for Android devices using Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune configuration policies with Google Chrome for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-configure-chrome-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get app bundle ID - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get the app bundle ID in Microsoft Intune for Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Windows apps. Use the bundle ID in your app policies, device configuration profiles, enrollment policies, and compliance policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/get-app-bundle-id-intune-admin-center</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand app protection policy delivery and timing - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the different deployment windows for app protection policies to understand when changes should appear on your end user devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-delivery</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-advanced-threat-protection-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>