<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:12:36 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:12:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Centrally manage Admin Tasks - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the centralized Admin tasks view in Microsoft Intune to manage common administrative tasks from across Intune capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/admin-tasks</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics, including device enrollment issues, startup performance, and data collection problems.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up SentinelOne MTD with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the SentinelOne Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/sentinelone-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use CrowdStrike Falcon for Mobile with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up CrowdStrike Falcon Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/crowdstrike-falcon-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up CrowdStrike Falcon for Mobile integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up CrowdStrike Falcon Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/crowdstrike-falcon-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Mobile Threat Defense compliance policies in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create an Intune device compliance policy that uses your MTD partner threat levels to determine if a mobile device can access company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-device-compliance-policy-create</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign MTD apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to add Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) apps, Microsoft Authenticator app, and iOS configuration policy in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-apps-ios-app-configuration-policy-add-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) app protection policy with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) app protection policy with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Mobile Threat Defense connector in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable the connector between your Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) partner and Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-connector-enable</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Mobile Threat Defense apps to unenrolled devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add Mobile Threat Defense apps to unenrolled devices by device users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-add-apps-unenrolled-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable the Mobile Threat Defense connector for unenrolled devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable the Mobile Threat Defense connector in Microsoft Intune for unenrolled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-enable-unenrolled-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SentinelOne MTD connector with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up SentinelOne Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/sentinelone-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Lookout Mobile Endpoint Security with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Lookout Mobile Endpoint Security and Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/lookout-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Zimperium MTD integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Zimperium Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zimperium-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Sophos Mobile integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Sophos Mobile solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/sophos-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zimperium MTD connector with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Zimperium Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zimperium-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Trend Micro MTD integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Trend Micro Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/trend-micro-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro Mobile Security and Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Trend Micro Mobile Threat Defense with with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/trend-micro-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Check Point Harmony integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up CheckPoint Harmony Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/checkpoint-sandblast-mobile-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Jamf Mobile Security with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Jamf Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/jamf-mtd-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Jamf Mobile Threat Protection integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Jamf Mobile Threat Protection solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/jamf-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Mobile Threat Defense with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Better Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/better-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up BlackBerry Protect with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the CylancePROTECT (BlackBerry) MTD solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/blackberry-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symantec Endpoint Protection Mobile connector with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Symantec Endpoint Protection Mobile with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/skycure-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check Point Harmony Mobile Mobile Threat Defense Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Check Point Harmony Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/checkpoint-sandblast-mobile-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trellix Mobile Security connector with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Trellix Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/trellix-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pradeo Mobile Threat Defense connector and Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Pradeo Mobile Threat Protection with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/pradeo-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Better Mobile integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate the third-party mobile threat defense solution of Better Mobile with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/better-mobile-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Trellix Mobile Security MTD with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Trellix Mobile Security mobile threat defense (MTD) solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/trellix-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Pradeo Mobile Threat Defense to integrate with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Pradeo Mobile Threat Protection solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/pradeo-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Sophos Mobile with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to use the Sophos Mobile solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/sophos-mtd-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lookout Mobile Endpoint with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Lookout Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) How to set up to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/lookout-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Symantec Endpoint Protection Mobile integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Symantec Endpoint Protection Mobile solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/skycure-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) with your Mobile Threat Defense partner to protect access to company resources based on device risk.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mobile-threat-defense</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackBerry Protect Mobile MTD and Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up CylancePROTECT Mobile (BlackBerry) with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/blackberry-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure schedules to gradually roll out Windows Updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure schedules that manage how and when Windows updates roll out to your managed devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/rollout-options</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 03:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, administrative templates (ADMX), and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Windows Driver updates policy for Windows devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using Microsoft Intune policy to manage Windows driver updates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/driver-updates-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an iOS/iPadOS Line-of-Business App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add an iOS/iPadOS line-of-business (LOB) app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data storage and processing in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how personal data is stored and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-store-process</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune Management Extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually Add the Windows Company Portal App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how your workforce can manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app to their PC from the Microsoft Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor App Information and Assignments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>After you assign an app to users or devices, use this information to help you monitor the app's status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>File and command reference for Microsoft Tunnel Gateway, a VPN solution for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find file and command-line references for tools you use to install or manage the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway, a VPN server that runs on Linux.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-reference</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data collection in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about personal data collected in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-collect</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune product and capabilities documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about how Microsoft Intune products and capabilities can help you secure, deploy, and manage users, apps, and endpoint devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Windows Update rings policy in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows update rings. You can configure, deploy, and pause update installation with Windows Update client policies using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/update-rings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Update for Business reports for Windows Updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Windows Update for Business reports to view data for Windows Updates you deploy with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Delivery Optimization settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure device configuration policy to manage Delivery Optimization settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/delivery-optimization-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Update settings you can manage with Intune Update Ring policies for Windows devices. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings for Windows Update that you can manage through Intune policy for Update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/settings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple configuration list for Intune settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune settings catalog to add, configure, or restrict features on Apple devices. This article lists and describes the settings you can configure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/apple-settings-catalog-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Delivery Optimization settings for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Delivery Optimization settings for Windows devices that you can deploy using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/delivery-optimization-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune to expedite Windows quality updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to expedite the installation of Windows updates on managed devices as soon as possible.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/expedite-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to manage software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set permissions to Managed Home Screen using Android Enterprise OEMConfig - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add the Samsung Knox Service Plugin, Zebra OEMConfig Powered by MX, and Legacy Zebra OEMConfig apps to Intune, and use the app schemas to configure permissions for the Managed Home Screen (MHS) app on Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/oemconfig-managed-home-screen-permissions-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune capabilities that can help you protect your devices and data against unauthorized access and other threats.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-protect</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security, email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4 to deploy device configuration profiles as part of the minimum set of policies for your devices using Microsoft Intune. The starting point is to enable the firewall, install AV, scan for malware, install software updates, create a strong PIN policy, and create email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-configuration-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows compatibility reports for Windows updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the app and driver compatibility reports for Windows devices before you deploy Intune policies for feature updates or update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/compatibility-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows cloud configuration step by step guide - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use this Windows 10/11 cloud configuration step-by-step setup guide to create your own cloud configuration deployment. You create the Microsoft Entra group and policies using Microsoft Intune, including the enrollment profile, compliance policy, and security baseline. You also deploy apps and resources that users need to do their jobs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/cloud-configuration-setup-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent to Manage Vulnerabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify, prioritize, and remediate security vulnerabilities across your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/vulnerability-remediation-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android FOTA Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates on Android devices. A FOTA update can include software and security patches, feature updates, and other changes to the device's firmware.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/fota-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zebra LifeGuard Over-the-Air Integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates for supported Zebra devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/zebra-lifeguard-ota-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows quality update policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Hotpatch updates to receive security updates without restarting your device</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/quality-updates-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin guide and checklist for macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updates for macOS devices using Microsoft Intune. Use this article to help manage software updates on your organization-owned devices, including how to create policies, manage updates, and review update status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-guide-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for software updates on BYOD in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for BYOD and personally owned devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on personal devices on Android and iOS/iPadOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/byod-software-updates-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Holographic devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and complete different tasks on devices running Windows Holographic for Business and HoloLens. You can configure the Company Portal app, create a compliance policy, customize OMA-URI settings, deploy apps, categorize devices in groups, create profiles, restrict devices, enable software updates, set terms and conditions, configure VPN and Wi-Fi settings, and use Hello for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-holographic-for-business</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View Software Update Reports for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Track Apple device update status in real time with Intune's declarative software update reporting. Learn how Microsoft Intune surfaces update changes directly from managed Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows cloud configuration in a guided scenario - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a guided scenario to configure Windows 10/11 client devices in a cloud configuration in Microsoft Intune. Cloud config focuses on a simplified device experience for internet browsing and using Microsoft 365 apps, including Microsoft Teams.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/cloud-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software update errors and descriptions in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the Software Update agent error code in Microsoft Intune, including the error code, symbolic name, and error description.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/software-update-agent-error-codes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common tasks and features in the settings catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure common features. You can create a Universal Print policy, configure Microsoft Edge and Google Chrome web browsers, and use built in settings instead of plist files for macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-common-features</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable use of Windows diagnostic data by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows diagnostic data in processor configuration for your tenant to enable its use by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/data-enable-windows-data</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To support hybrid and remote workers, convert or migrate your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints. This planning guide focuses on deploying apps and updates with Intune, moving from Group Policy Objects, and using Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-endpoints-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Windows Driver updates policy in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage policies that install Windows driver updates on your Intune managed Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/driver-updates-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Follow the steps to deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for Android software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for Android devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on corporate owned Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/software-updates-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune Suite add-on capabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune Suite unifies a series of mission-critical advanced endpoint management and security capabilities. The capabilities of the suite are integrated with Microsoft 365 and Microsoft Security across endpoint platforms for both cloud and on-premises co-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-add-ons</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Update Policies for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure software update policies for Apple devices using Apple's Declarative Device Management (DDM) model. Improve security, reduce user disruption, and ensure compliance with reliable, automated updates across your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure feature updates policy for Windows devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows feature updates. Configure and deploy policy to maintain the Windows feature version of Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/feature-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work From Anywhere Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how the Work from Anywhere report in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides insights into remote productivity, device readiness, and user experience.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/work-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom settings - Windows Holographic for Business devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a custom profile to use the OMA-URI settings for devices running Windows Holographic for Business in Microsoft Intune, including Microsoft HoloLens. You can set AllowFastReconnect, AllowVPN, AllowUpdateService, UpdateServiceURL, RequireUpdatesApproval, ApprovedUpdates, and ApplicationLaunchRestrictions policy configuration service provider (CSP) settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-windows-holographic</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed IT with multiple admins - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about scaling guidelines for Microsoft Intune when you have a large number of local admins who need to manage their own users/devices and policies within the same tenant. Use Microsoft Intune's Role Based Access Control to manage access.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-scale-guidelines</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Windows Update client policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage Windows software updates by using Intune policy for Update rings for Windows and Windows feature updates for Windows Update client policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for US government deployments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the list of US government endpoint URLs that Intune needs and requires. Allow the ports, IP addresses, and endpoint URLs in your proxy server configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-us-government-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>