<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:31:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, administrative templates (ADMX), and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog to configure administrative templates (ADMX) in Microsoft Intune on Windows 10/11 client devices. You can configure some Control Panel features, Start menu and task bar notifications, event log service, prevent IIS installation, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop-multi-session</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy sets - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use policy sets to group collections of management objects in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-sets</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Android, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows devices in Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to assist users authenticated by your organization. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set the mobile device management authority - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to set the mobile device management authority in Microsoft Intune and some key considerations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/mdm-authority-set</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1 for deploying or setting up Intune. The starting point is to review supported configurations, sign up for the trial, configure the custom domain name, add users and groups to Intune, assign licenses to users, manage roles, grant admin permissions, and set the MDM authority.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration guide to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deployment guide to set up, onboard, or move to Intune. These steps include moving from partner MDM providers, using co-management, moving from on-premises group policy, and moving from Office 365 device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-intune-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS device enrollment guide for  Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll macOS devices using device enrollment, automated device enrollment (DEP), and Apple Configurator enrollment options in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage and secure devices overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get an overview of the concepts and features you should know when managing devices that access organization resources in Microsoft Intune. You can manage new and existing devices, including BYOD personal devices, check health compliance and view reports, configure device features, and secure devices using mobile threat solutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/manage-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add groups to organize users and devices for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Microsoft Entra groups to organize users and devices for use with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/groups-add</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is device management? - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about what device management means and how it can help organizations, including Microsoft 365 small &amp; medium business, and enterprise. See a list of features and benefits, including mobile device management (MDM) and mobile application management (MAM), and learn about Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-device-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>ServiceNow integration enables help desk staff, who are licensed to use Remote Help, to use ServiceNow to view incidents and details of the tech issue that an employee is facing from the Troubleshooting pane. This article also describes how to configure ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/service-now-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-level architecture for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This reference architecture shows options for integrating Microsoft Intune in your Azure environment with Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/high-level-architecture</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit changes and events in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to review audit logs that record Microsoft Intune activities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/monitor-audit-logs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-protect-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage and secure apps overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get an overview of the concepts and features you should know when managing apps that access organization resources in Microsoft Intune. You can deploy apps used by your organization, including Microsoft Edge and Microsoft 365. You can also configure apps, protect apps on organizations owned and BYOD personal devices, and update apps that you deploy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/manage-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Route logs to Azure Monitor using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Diagnostics Settings to send audit logs and operational logs in Microsoft Intune to Azure Storage account, Event Hubs, or Log Analytics. Choose how long you want to keep the data, and see some estimated costs for different size tenants.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/review-logs-using-azure-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure compliance policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Description for configuring compliance policies</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-compliance-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Windows virtual machines with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the general guidelines for using Windows 10/11 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-10-virtual-machines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Graph APIs to export Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about exporting Intune reports using Graph APIs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-apis</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlicensed admins in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to give unlicensed admins permissions to access Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/unlicensed-admins</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune contributes to a strong Zero Trust strategy and architecture.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/zero-trust-with-microsoft-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help on Android to assist users authenticated by your organization. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app in Android, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security, email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4 to deploy device configuration profiles as part of the minimum set of policies for your devices using Microsoft Intune. The starting point is to enable the firewall, install AV, scan for malware, install software updates, create a strong PIN policy, and create email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-configuration-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign a role to an Intune administrator - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign a built-in or custom role to a user in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/assign-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Multi Admin Approval in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Multi Admin Approval to protect your tenant against the use of compromised administrative accounts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/multi-admin-approval</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Linux devices in Intune using the Intune app. Set an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance recommendations when using filters - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>When using filters in Microsoft Intune, use Intune virtual groups that don't require Microsoft Entra ID syncing. To improve performance, reuse groups, make incremental group changes, and use filters to include and exclude.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-performance-recommendations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a user in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a user in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protection and configuration levels overview in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the different levels of protection and configuration in Microsoft Intune, including minimum, enhanced, and high levels.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/protection-configuration-levels</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure a custom domain name - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a custom domain name for your Microsoft Intune subscription</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/custom-domain-name-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows cloud configuration step by step guide - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use this Windows 10/11 cloud configuration step-by-step setup guide to create your own cloud configuration deployment. You create the Microsoft Entra group and policies using Microsoft Intune, including the enrollment profile, compliance policy, and security baseline. You also deploy apps and resources that users need to do their jobs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/cloud-configuration-setup-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help desk troubleshooting dashboard - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Help desk staff use the troubleshooting pane to solve users' technical problems.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/help-desk-operators</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune operated by 21Vianet in China - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune operated by 21Vianet in China.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/china</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune servicing information and details - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the frequency of the Microsoft Intune service updates, the release cadence, and how to check your tenant release version.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-service-servicing-information</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI updates for Intune end-user apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what has changed in UI for apps that work on end-user devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new-app-ui</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from Microsoft 365 Basic Mobility and Security to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to migrate your mobile device management from Microsoft 365 Basic Mobility and Security to Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/migrate-to-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Service Description - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a cloud-based service that helps you manage Windows, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/microsoft-intune-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided scenario - Deploy Microsoft Edge for Mobile - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the guided scenario to deploy Microsoft Edge for Mobile from the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided scenarios overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune guided scenarios available in the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and assign a custom role in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and assign a custom role for a remote device manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Holographic devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and complete different tasks on devices running Windows Holographic for Business and HoloLens. You can configure the Company Portal app, create a compliance policy, customize OMA-URI settings, deploy apps, categorize devices in groups, create profiles, restrict devices, enable software updates, set terms and conditions, configure VPN and Wi-Fi settings, and use Hello for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-holographic-for-business</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided scenario - Secure Microsoft Office mobile apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the guided scenario to deploy secure Microsoft Office mobile apps from the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-office-mobile</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune settings for the iOS/iPadOS Classroom app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the Intune settings you can use to control settings for the Classroom app on iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/education-settings-configure-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune shared device settings for the iOS/iPadOS Classroom app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the Intune settings you can use to control settings for the Classroom app on shared iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/education-settings-configure-ios-shared</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configurations policy mapping from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A detailed list of the policy map between Basic Mobility and Security configurations and Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-map-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to detect and fix support issues - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows cloud configuration in a guided scenario - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a guided scenario to configure Windows 10/11 client devices in a cloud configuration in Microsoft Intune. Cloud config focuses on a simplified device experience for internet browsing and using Microsoft 365 apps, including Microsoft Teams.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/cloud-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remotely administer devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the required roles to use TeamViewer, how to install the TeamViewer connector, and step-by-step guidance to remotely administer devices using Microsoft Intune in the Azure portal</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/teamviewer-support</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See an overview of the steps to start using Intune. Plan your move and deployment of Intune, determine your licensing needs and any platform requirements, use compliance and Conditional Access, deploy apps, create device configuration profiles, and enroll your devices to be managed. Get more information on mobile application management for BYOD or personal devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/get-started-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags for distributed IT - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags to filter configuration profiles to specific roles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/scope-tags</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Android and Android Enterprise corporate-owned work profile, personally owned devices with a work profile, fully managed, AOSP, and dedicated devices in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a group to manage users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to create a group based on existing users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-group</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View device details with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View your device details, including operating systems, storage space, manufacturer, and model. Get a list of installed apps, check compliance policies, and set up TeamViewer with Microsoft Intune in Azure. Similar to viewing inventory of the devices you manage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-inventory</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filter reports and troubleshooting in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the device and app filter reports to get more information on successfully applied filters. Learn the effect of include and exclude filters in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-reports-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find the primary user of a Microsoft Intune device. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find the primary user (or User Device Affinity) of an Intune device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/find-primary-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create filters in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about policy assignment filters, and see the steps to create, update, or delete a filter in Microsoft Intune. Create an assignment filter for managed devices or managed apps scenarios.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Windows devices using Automatic enrollment, Windows Autopilot, group policy, and co-management enrollment options in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try Microsoft Intune overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Evaluate Microsoft Intune by stepping through common Intune settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/try-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Microsoft Intune licenses - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Assign licenses to users so they can enroll in Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/licenses-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage device operating system versions with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the methods for managing device operating system versions supported by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/manage-os-versions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Graph API - Reports and properties - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Intune reports and properties provided via Graph API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-available-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Walkthrough the Microsoft Intune admin center - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will tour Microsoft Intune in the Microsoft Intune admin center to better understand how to accomplish tasks.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/tutorial-walkthrough-endpoint-manager</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the Microsoft Intune MDM lifecycle - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Intune helps you manage devices through their lifecycle - from enrollment, through configuration, to eventual retirement.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-lifecycle</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune classic groups in the Azure portal - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn what's new with groups in the Microsoft Intune Azure portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/groups-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device enrollment guide for  Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll iOS and iPadOS devices using user and device enrollment, automated device enrollment (DEP), and Apple Configurator in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a custom role in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a custom role in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage and secure user and group identities overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get an overview of the concepts and features you should know when managing identities in Microsoft Intune. Use existing users and groups, control access using RBAC, establish user affinity, and secure and authenticate users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/manage-identities</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help Web App. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help web app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-webapp</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Specialty devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides information about specialty devices and how can you manage them with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/specialty-devices-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune Suite add-on capabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune Suite unifies a series of mission-critical advanced endpoint management and security capabilities. The capabilities of the suite are integrated with Microsoft 365 and Microsoft Security across endpoint platforms for both cloud and on-premises co-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-add-ons</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public preview overview in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about public preview features in Microsoft Intune, and see an example. See a list of limitations, restrictions, and more in the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/public-preview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Licenses available for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune is available with these licenses</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/licenses</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the Microsoft Intune tenant status page - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune tenant status page displays details about your tenant and the status of connectors you've configured, and messages intended for tenants and about the Intune service health.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/tenant-status</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compliance in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about compliance, dependencies, and features in Microsoft Intune supporting data protection and regulatory requirements.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/compliance-in-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add users to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add and managing Microsoft Entra user accounts from within Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/users-add</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Linux device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Linux device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings insight - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Settings insight feature adds insights giving you confidence in configurations that are successfully adopted by similar organizations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/settings-insight</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided scenario - Cloud-managed Modern Desktop - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the guided scenario to set up and configure a basic Modern Desktop from the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-cloud-managed-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View ChromeOS device information - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View ChromeOS devices and details synced with the Chrome Enterprise connector in the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/chrome-enterprise-device-details</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune manages users and devices, simplifies app management and automated policy deployment, and integrates with mobile threat defense. It connects to Managed Google Play, Apple tokens and certificates, and Teamviewer for remote assistance. Can use MDM or MAM to protect data, configure devices, and simplify access to company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed IT with multiple admins - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about scaling guidelines for Microsoft Intune when you have a large number of local admins who need to manage their own users/devices and policies within the same tenant. Use Microsoft Intune's Role Based Access Control to manage access.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-scale-guidelines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try Microsoft Intune for free - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a free trial subscription, understand supported configurations and networking requirements, and optionally configure your domain name.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/free-trial-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>