<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:02:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Intune security baselines for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that have preset and recommended configurations to the Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure device configuration profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or configure a device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Select the platform type, configure the settings, and add a scope tag. Learn more about applicability rules, and the policy refresh cycle times.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-create</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security firewall settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security firewall policy settings for Windows and macOS in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-firewall-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Microsoft Entra ID to Access Intune APIs in Microsoft Graph - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes steps needed for apps to use Microsoft Entra ID to access the Intune APIs in Microsoft Graph.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/intune-graph-apis</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security Account protection (Preview) policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security Account protection policy settings in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security Attack surface reduction settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Details about the settings in the endpoint security Attack surface reduction policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-asr-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings you can manage with Intune Endpoint Protection profiles for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the available settings in Intune endpoint protection profiles for managed Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-protection-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Update settings you can manage with Intune Update Ring policies for Windows devices. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings for Windows Update that you can manage through Intune policy for Update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft HoloLens 2 advanced security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune advanced security baseline for Microsoft HoloLens 2. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-hololens2-advanced</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft Edge security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline version 112 and later, for the Microsoft Edge browser. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-v2-edge-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft 365 Apps for Enterprise security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Office apps. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-v2-office-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Edge security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Edge browser. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft HoloLens 2 standard security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune standard security baseline for Microsoft HoloLens 2. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-hololens2-standard</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Windows 365 Cloud PC security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Windows 365 Cloud PC. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-windows-365</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Default configuration of Intune's Windows security baselines - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the default setting configuration of the various Microsoft Intune security baselines for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-mdm-all</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Windows, Windows Holographic, and Surface Hub devices in Microsoft Intune. Check for compliance on the minimum and maximum operating system, set password restrictions and length, check for partner anti-virus (AV) solutions, enable encryption on data storage, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for iOS/iPadOS that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings for Microsoft Defender Antivirus for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the settings in the Microsoft Defender Antivirus profile for Windows devices. You can configure these settings as part of Endpoint security Antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Started With the Microsoft Intune App SDK - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Quickly enable your mobile app for mobile application management (MAM) with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View the Android device administrator compliance settings for Microsoft Intune compliance policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings that are available for Android device administrator devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android (AOSP) compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Android (AOSP) that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android-aosp</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security firewall settings for Configuration Manager devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security firewall policy settings for tenant attached devices you manage with Configuration Manager. You can configure firewall setting after you configure tenant attach for Configuration Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-firewall-profile-settings-tenant-attach</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antivirus policy settings for Windows Security experience policy for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security Antivirus policy settings for the Windows Security app in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-security-experience-windows-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings from Windows security settings for tenant attached devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the settings in the *Windows Security experience* profile for tenant attached devices. To use this Endpoint security Antivirus policy, you must first configure tenant attach for Configuration Manager for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-windows-security-settings-windows-tenant-attach</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 8.1 compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Windows 8.1 that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows-8-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Enterprise compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune. Set password rules, choose a minimum or maximum operating system version, restrict specific apps, prevent reusing password, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Tunnel VPN with iOS/iPad devices that don't enroll with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add support for Mobile Application Management (MAM) for iOS to the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. Tunnel support for MAM expands access to your organizational resources for devices that can't or haven't enrolled with Microsoft Intune. Admins should use this article to create policies that support per-app VPN in line of business (LOB) apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-mam-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use a PKCS certificate profile to provision devices with certificates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificates with Microsoft Intune, work with root certificates and certificate templates, and use device configuration profiles for a PKCS Certificate.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-pfx-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage antivirus settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies and use reports for devices you manage with endpoint security antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-antivirus-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Hello for Business settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View details for Windows Hello for Business settings you configure in an Intune identity protection profile for device groups in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/identity-protection-windows-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the prerequisites for installation and use of the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. These include Linux servers, network, and firewall configurations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings from Microsoft Defender Antivirus for tenant attached devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the settings in the Microsoft Defender Antivirus profile for Windows devices managed by Configuration Manager. You can configure these settings as part of Endpoint security Antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune after you configure tenant attach for Configuration Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows-tenant-attach</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign MTD apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to add Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) apps, Microsoft Authenticator app, and iOS configuration policy in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-apps-ios-app-configuration-policy-add-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for macOS devices that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-mac-os</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Protection Policies Overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune Management Extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple Volume-Purchased Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Win32 App Supersedence - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Win32 app supersedence with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-supersedence</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually Add the Windows 10 Company Portal App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how your workforce can manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app to their PC from the Microsoft Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell Scripts for Remediations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>PowerShell script reference for Remediations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/powershell-scripts-remediation</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Web Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding web apps (client-server applications) to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/web-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Level Architecture for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This reference architecture shows options for integrating Microsoft Intune in your Azure environment with Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/high-level-architecture</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add, Configure, and Protect Apps with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-protect-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Protection for Windows MAM - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable protected MAM access to org data using Windows MAM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/protect-mam-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign an App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to add and assign an app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-add-assign-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Graph APIs to Export Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about exporting Intune reports using Graph APIs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-apis</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send Notifications to Noncompliant Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this topic, you use Microsoft Intune to send email notifications to noncompliant devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/quickstart-send-notification</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get App Bundle ID - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get the app bundle ID in Microsoft Intune for Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Windows apps. Use the bundle ID in your app policies, device configuration profiles, enrollment policies, and compliance policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/get-app-bundle-id-intune-admin-center</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help Desk Troubleshooting Dashboard - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Help desk staff use the troubleshooting pane to solve users' technical problems.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/help-desk-operators</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review App Protection Policy Logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 4. Create App Configuration Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4. Create app configuration policy for Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-4-acp-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Warehouse Data Model - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune Data Warehouse samples data daily to provide a historical view of your continually changing mobile environment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-data-model</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse API Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This reference topic describes the Microsoft Intune Data Warehouse API URL structure. Filter examples are provided.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-api-url</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and Assign an App Protection Policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you use Microsoft Intune to create and assign and app protection policy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-create-assign-app-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 2. Create App Protection Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-2-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Scenario - Deploy Microsoft Edge for Mobile - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the guided scenario to deploy Microsoft Edge for Mobile from the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Scenarios Overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune guided scenarios available in the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Scenario - Secure Microsoft Office Mobile Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the guided scenario to deploy secure Microsoft Office mobile apps from the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-office-mobile</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 5. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business End User Experience for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 5. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business end user experience Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-5-end-user-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Volume-Purchased Apps and Books with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how you can use Microsoft Intune to manage and monitor your use of volume-purchased apps and books from stores."</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 6. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business Data Security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 6. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business corporate data security in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-6-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Validate Your App Protection Policy Setup - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to test that your app protection policy is set up and working correctly in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-validate</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Configure Slack to Use Intune for EMM and App Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this tutorial you will configure Slack to use Intune for EMM and app configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/tutorial-configure-slack-enterprise-grid</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Volume-Purchased iOS/iPadOS eBooks - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync books you purchased in volume from the iOS store with Intune. You can then manage and track usage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-ebooks-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to Detect and Fix Support Issues - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Group to Manage Users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to create a group based on existing users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-group</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password Compliance Policy for Android Enterprise Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this topic, you will use Microsoft Intune to set the length of the password required for Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/quickstart-set-password-length-android</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try Microsoft Intune Overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Evaluate Microsoft Intune by stepping through common Intune settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/try-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Graph API - Reports and Properties - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Intune reports and properties provided via Graph API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-available-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block Apps with No Modern Authentication on Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about applications and modern authentication (MSAL) using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/app-modern-authentication-block</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Sets - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use policy sets to group collections of management objects in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-sets</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Walkthrough the Microsoft Intune Admin Center - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will tour Microsoft Intune in the Microsoft Intune admin center to better understand how to accomplish tasks.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/tutorial-walkthrough-endpoint-manager</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Transferring Data Between iOS Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how to use mobile app management policies in Microsoft Intune to manage data transfers between apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/data-transfer-between-apps-manage-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported Microsoft Intune Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides lists of support partner and Microsoft apps that are commonly used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-supported-intune-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse Change Log - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic provides a list of changes for the Microsoft Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-changelog</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Scenario - Cloud-Managed Modern Desktop - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the guided scenario to set up and configure a basic Modern Desktop from the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-cloud-managed-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovered Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand details about the detected apps that Intune found on a device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-discovered-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add PowerShell Scripts to Windows Devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and run PowerShell scripts, assign the script policy to Microsoft Entra groups, and use reports to monitor the scripts. See the steps to delete scripts you add on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune. Read common issues and resolutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/powershell-scripts</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try Microsoft Intune for Free - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a free trial subscription, understand supported configurations and networking requirements, and optionally configure your domain name.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/free-trial-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Hide Devices With Cleanup Rules - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune's device cleanup rules offer a simple, automated way to ensure that only actively managed devices remain visible in the admin center. Learn more about device cleanup rules and how to configure them.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-cleanup-rules</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Reset Protection Emails Not Enforced in Intune for Android - Intune</title>
      <description>Describes an issue in which an Android Enterprise device can be activated by using a Google account that isn't included in the "Factory reset protection emails" setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-configuration/factory-reset-protection-emails-not-enforced</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 18:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Route logs to Azure Monitor using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Diagnostics Settings to send audit logs and operational logs in Microsoft Intune to Azure Storage account, Event Hubs, or Log Analytics. Choose how long you want to keep the data, and see some estimated costs for different size tenants.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/review-logs-using-azure-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Use Microsoft Intune to protect Exchange Online email from unmanaged iOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune app protection policies and Conditional Access to prevent unmanaged iOS devices from accessing Exchange Online.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/tutorial-protect-email-on-unmanaged-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Protect Exchange Online email on managed iOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn to secure Exchange Online with iOS Intune compliance policies and Microsoft Entra Conditional Access to require managed devices and the Outlook app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/tutorial-protect-email-on-enrolled-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Microsoft 365 apps with the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to update Microsoft 365 apps to the latest version, and choose how frequently Office checks for updates. See the device registry keys that are updated when an Intune policy to Office update is applied.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-update-office</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune user help - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll your device in Intune to gain secure access to work-related email, apps, and Wi-Fi.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/user-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to assist users authenticated by your organization. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure a tenant-wide Windows Hello for Business policy with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Apply policy for Windows Hello for Business on devices at the time they enroll with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-hello</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create device compliance policies for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/create-compliance-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure compliance policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Description for configuring compliance policies</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-compliance-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a JSON file for custom compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create the JSON file that defines custom settings and values for use with device compliance policies in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-custom-json</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Endpoint protection settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Endpoint protection settings when you create a macOS or Windows device profile in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-protection-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>