<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 17:12:31 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 17:12:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on macOS to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Remote Help to provide remote assistance to authenticated users and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune product and capabilities documentation</title>
      <description>Learn more about how Microsoft Intune products and capabilities can help you secure, deploy, and manage users, apps, and endpoint devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policies overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple volume-purchased apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, administrative templates (ADMX), and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog to configure administrative templates (ADMX) in Microsoft Intune on Windows 10/11 client devices. You can configure some Control Panel features, Start menu and task bar notifications, event log service, prevent IIS installation, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft 365 Apps to Windows 10/11 devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to install Microsoft 365 apps on Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-office365</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign apps to groups in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign an Intune app to groups of users or devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App configuration policies for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use app configuration policies on an iOS/iPadOS or Android device in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Win32 app supersedence - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Win32 app supersedence with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-supersedence</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Win32 apps in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the most common methods to troubleshoot Win32 app issues with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add a Windows line-of-business app to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add a Windows line-of-business (LOB) app using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how your workforce can manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app to their PC from the Microsoft Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows app deployment by using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Windows 10/11 app deployment scenarios available with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-windows-10-app-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is device management? - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about what device management means and how it can help organizations, including Microsoft 365 small &amp; medium business, and enterprise. See a list of features and benefits, including mobile device management (MDM) and mobile application management (MAM), and learn about Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-device-management</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add web apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding web apps (client-server applications) to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/web-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use shell scripts on macOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create, assign, monitor, and troubleshoot shell scripts for macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/macos-shell-scripts</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add app configuration policies for managed Android Enterprise devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use app configuration policies in Microsoft Intune to supply settings when users run a Managed Google Play app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-use-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join your cloud-native endpoints to Microsoft Entra</title>
      <description>When moving to or using cloud-native endpoints, use Microsoft Entra joined endpoints. When your endpoints are joined to Microsoft Entra, you can use Windows Autopilot to provision or get devices ready for organization use. Learn more about the benefits to IT admins and end-users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/azure-ad-joined-hybrid-azure-ad-joined</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an unmanaged macOS PKG app to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add an unmanaged macOS PKG app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/macos-unmanaged-pkg</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data protection for Windows MAM - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable protected MAM access to org data using Windows MAM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/protect-mam-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Include and exclude app assignments in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to include and exclude app assignments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-inc-exl-assignments</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add iOS store apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding iOS store apps to Microsoft Intune. You can assign apps using this method if the apps are free of charge in the App Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign an app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to add and assign an app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-add-assign-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policies for Microsoft 365 apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the policies available for Microsoft 365 apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-office-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign a role to an Intune administrator - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign a built-in or custom role to a user in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/assign-role</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android to ensure collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-office</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration policies for Intune App SDK managed apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure policies for Intune App SDK managed apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-managed-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Android store apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add Android store apps from the Google Play store to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Microsoft Intune management agent for macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Microsoft Intune management agent for macOS.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-macos-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Application Management (MAM) and Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the available features when deciding to use Mobile Application Management (MAM) and/or Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles for personal or BYOD Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/android-deployment-scenarios-app-protection-work-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Google Chrome for Android devices using Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune configuration policies with Google Chrome for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-configure-chrome-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use on-premises services with cloud-native endpoints</title>
      <description>For cloud-native endpoints to access on-premises resources, such as file servers, printers, and web servers, use Windows integrated authentication (WIA) and Microsoft Entra Connect.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-endpoints-on-premises</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get app bundle ID - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get the app bundle ID in Microsoft Intune for Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Windows apps. Use the bundle ID in your app policies, device configuration profiles, enrollment policies, and compliance policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/get-app-bundle-id-intune-admin-center</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for Android software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for Android devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on corporate owned Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for software updates on BYOD in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for BYOD and personally owned devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on personal devices on Android and iOS/iPadOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-personal-byod</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand app protection policy delivery and timing - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the different deployment windows for app protection policies to understand when changes should appear on your end user devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-delivery</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-advanced-threat-protection-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are cloud-native Windows endpoints</title>
      <description>Learn more about cloud-native endpoints and what they are. See a list of benefits, and the effect on end users and IT administrators. Cloud-native endpoints help with remote workers and hybrid workers, and use Microsoft Intune to manage devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-endpoints-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure 802.1x wired network settings for macOS and Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create or add a wired network device configuration profile or policy using the IEEE 802.1X standard for macOS, Windows 10, and Windows 11 devices and computers. See the different settings, add certificates, choose an EAP type, and select an authentication method in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wired-networks-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add built-in apps to mobile devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Intune to make it easier to install built-in apps mobile devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-built-in</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure a VPN or per-app VPN for Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use an app configuration policy to add or create a VPN or per-app VPN profile for Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-vpn-ae</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Store apps to Intune (legacy) - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Store (legacy) apps to Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review app protection policy logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with frontline worker (FLW) device management</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage frontline worker devices using Android, iOS/iPadOS, and Windows devices in Microsoft Intune. Get guidance on device use and Intune features built for FLW, like Remote Help. Also, learn about Microsoft Entra shared device mode (SDM) for FLW.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/frontline-worker/frontline-worker-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to monitor app protection policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to monitor app protection policies in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create quiet time policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create quiet time policies for iOS/iPadOS and Android apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-quiet-time-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Export iOS and iPadOS settings from Apple Configurator or Apple Profile Manager tools, and then import these settings into Microsoft Intune. These settings can create, use, and control custom settings and features on iOS/iPadOS devices. This custom profile can then be assigned or distributed to iOS/iPadOS devices in your organization to create a baseline or standard.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create macOS system and kernel extensions with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about system extensions and kernel extensions for macOS devices. In Microsoft Intune, add or create a device configuration policy that configures kernel extensions. In the extension, you can allow user override, add a team identifier, and add a bundle and team identifier.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kernel-extensions-overview-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 4. Create app configuration policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4. Create app configuration policy for Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-4-acp-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and assign an app protection policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you use Microsoft Intune to create and assign and app protection policy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-create-assign-app-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apps for GCC High and DoD environments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about apps involving GCC High and DoD environments using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy-gcc-dod</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Edge for Windows with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune configuration policies with Edge for Windows to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policies for extensions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes the app protection policy (APP) for extensions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-extensions</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-2-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-1-mamca</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with Windows frontline worker devices</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage frontline worker devices using Windows devices in Microsoft Intune. Select the best enrollment option, configure the home screen, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/frontline-worker/frontline-worker-overview-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Microsoft 365 apps to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to install Microsoft 365 apps on macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-office365-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with Android frontline worker devices</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage frontline worker devices using Android devices in Microsoft Intune. Select the best enrollment option, configure the home screen, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/frontline-worker/frontline-worker-overview-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Win32 apps on S mode devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enable Win32 apps on S mode devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-s-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allow or block apps for Samsung Knox Standard devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a custom profile to allow and block apps for Samsung Knox Standard Android device administrator devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/samsung-knox-apps-allow-block</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided update supersedence for Enterprise App Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to update an Enterprise App Catalog app using supersedence with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-eam-supersedence</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 5. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business end user experience for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 5. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business end user experience Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-5-end-user-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage volume-purchased apps and books with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how you can use Microsoft Intune to manage and monitor your use of volume-purchased apps and books from stores."</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune settings for the iOS/iPadOS Classroom app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the Intune settings you can use to control settings for the Classroom app on iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/education-settings-configure-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense for App Protection Policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 3. Integrate Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-3-scc</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 6. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business data security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 6. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business corporate data security in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-6-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare a Win32 app to be uploaded to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to prepare a Win32 app to be uploaded to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-prepare</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage volume-purchased iOS/iPadOS eBooks - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync books you purchased in volume from the iOS store with Intune. You can then manage and track usage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-ebooks-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Configure Slack to use Intune for EMM and app configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this tutorial you will configure Slack to use Intune for EMM and app configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/tutorial-configure-slack-enterprise-grid</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policy settings for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy (APP) settings for MAM on Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor app information and assignments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>After you've assigned an app to users or devices, use this information to help you monitor the app's status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Validate your app protection policy setup - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to test that your app protection policy is set up and working correctly in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-validate</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to Linux devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add Bash scripts to create a custom Linux profile in Microsoft Intune. Use the script to create, use, and control custom settings and features on Linux devices. This custom profile can then be assigned or distributed to Linux devices in your organization to create a baseline or standard.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to wipe only corporate data from apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to selectively wipe only corporate data from Intune-managed apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-selective-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Store apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Store apps to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Teams for iOS and Android with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Teams for iOS and Android to ensure team collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-teams</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints</title>
      <description>To support hybrid and remote workers, convert or migrate your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints. This planning guide focuses on deploying apps and updates with Intune, moving from Group Policy Objects, and using Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-endpoints-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Android Enterprise system apps in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Android Enterprise system apps in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-ae-system</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win32 app management in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune. This article provides an overview of the Intune Win32 app delivery and management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an Enterprise App Catalog app to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add an Enterprise App Catalog app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-enterprise-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Intune in environments without Google Mobile Services - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune in environments without Google Mobile Services.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-without-gms</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get support in the Microsoft Intune admin center</title>
      <description>Get online and telephone support for Microsoft Intune and other device management cloud services from within the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/get-support</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Microsoft Intune licenses - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Assign licenses to users so they can enroll in Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/licenses-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Windows update packages in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to deploy a Windows update package (.msu file) in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-deploy-update-package</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add apps to Microsoft Intune so you can assign apps to users and devices. Intune supports a wide range of app types.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add a macOS DMG app to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a macOS DMG app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-macos-dmg</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign Win32 apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add, assign, and manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-add</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS app provisioning profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune gives you the tools to proactively assign a new provisioning profile to devices that have apps that are nearing expiry.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-provisioning-profile-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add app configuration policies for managed iOS/iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use app configuration policies to provide configuration data to an iOS/iPadOS app when it's run.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-use-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to add macOS line-of-business apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add macOS line-of-business (LOB) apps to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin guide and checklist for macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updates for macOS devices using Microsoft Intune. Use this article to help manage software updates on your organization-owned devices, including how to create policies, manage updates, and review update status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>