<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 12:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 12:02:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Intune operated by 21Vianet in China - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune operated by 21Vianet in China.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/china</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platforms and policy types supported by filters in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the supported apps, compliance policies, and device configuration profiles that support filters in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-supported-workloads</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and assign a custom role in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and assign a custom role for a remote device manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune product and capabilities documentation</title>
      <description>Learn more about how Microsoft Intune products and capabilities can help you secure, deploy, and manage users, apps, and endpoint devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk enrollment for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a bulk enrollment package for Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-bulk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenarios for using Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Conditional Access is commonly used with Intune compliance policy for devices and apps</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-intune-common-ways-use</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoid policy conflicts - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to avoid policy conflicts when creating and deploying new policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/manage-avoid-policy-conflicts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Intune for Education? - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Intune for Education and how it is different from the full Intune management experience.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/introduction-intune-education</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Education Windows Update configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about common Windows Update configuration used by Education organizations in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/common-config-windows-update</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Education Start menu configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about common Start menu configuration used by Education organizations in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/common-config-settings-catalog-start-menu</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Education device restrictions configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about common device restrictions configuration used by Education organizations in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/common-config-settings-catalog-device-restrictions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Education privacy configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about common privacy configuration used by Education organizations in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/common-config-settings-catalog-windows-privacy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan Education device grouping and targeting - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan how you'll group devices and users and target policies and applications.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/plan-grouping</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Intune service and set up the environment for education.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/industry/education/tutorial-school-deployment/set-up-microsoft-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiosk settings for Windows in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your Windows 10/11 client devices as single-app and multi-app kiosks, customize the start menu, add apps, show the task bar, and configure a web browser in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kiosk-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device restriction settings for Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings and their descriptions for creating device restrictions on Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a configuration profile to control screenshots, password requirements, kiosk settings, apps in the store, Microsoft Edge browser, Microsoft Defender, access to the cloud, start menu, and more in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict devices features using policy in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a device configuration profile to restrict features on Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, AOSP, macOS, iOS, iPadOS, and Windows 10/11 client devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eSIM configuration of a download server - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about configuration of an eSIM Download Server from Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/esim-device-configuration-download-server</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable eSIM data connections in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or use eSIM to get internet and data access using different data plans. In Intune, add or import activation codes, and then assign these activation codes using a configuration profile. You can also monitor the eSIM profiles and check the status of the eSIM-enabled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/esim-device-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade to Windows Holographic for Business in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Upgrade HoloLens (first gen) to Windows 10 Holographic for Business using a device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/holographic-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows VPN settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn and read about all the available VPN settings in Microsoft Intune, what they're used for, and what they do. See the traffic rules, Conditional Access, and DNS and proxy settings for Windows 10/11 and Windows Holographic for Business devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage antivirus settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies and use reports for devices you manage with endpoint security antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-antivirus-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported filter device and app properties &amp; operators in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>When using filters, get more information on the device properties, supported operators, and supported Windows OS SKUs, including examples. Use these features to create rule expressions in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-device-properties</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add, Configure, and Protect Apps with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-protect-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance recommendations when using filters - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>When using filters in Microsoft Intune, use Intune virtual groups that don't require Microsoft Entra ID syncing. To improve performance, reuse groups, make incremental group changes, and use filters to include and exclude.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-performance-recommendations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI updates for Intune end-user apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what has changed in UI for apps that work on end-user devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new-app-ui</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for China deployments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review China endpoints for Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/china-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Access requirements policy mapping from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A detailed list of the policy map between Basic Mobility and Security access requirements and Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-map-access-requirements</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to Detect and Fix Support Issues - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows cloud configuration in a guided scenario - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a guided scenario to configure Windows 10/11 client devices in a cloud configuration in Microsoft Intune. Cloud config focuses on a simplified device experience for internet browsing and using Microsoft 365 apps, including Microsoft Teams.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/cloud-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filter reports and troubleshooting in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the device and app filter reports to get more information on successfully applied filters. Learn the effect of include and exclude filters in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-reports-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create filters in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about policy assignment filters, and see the steps to create, update, or delete a filter in Microsoft Intune. Create an assignment filter for managed devices or managed apps scenarios.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Windows devices using Automatic enrollment, Windows Autopilot, group policy, and co-management enrollment options in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operating systems and browsers supported by Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Lists supported device platforms and browsers for Intune device management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/supported-devices-browsers</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Graph API - Reports and Properties - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Intune reports and properties provided via Graph API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-available-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage firewall settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security firewall policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-firewall-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop-multi-session</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a custom role in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a custom role in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the Microsoft Intune MDM lifecycle - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Intune helps you manage devices through their lifecycle - from enrollment, through configuration, to eventual retirement.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-lifecycle</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Sets - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use policy sets to group collections of management objects in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-sets</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Scenario - Cloud-Managed Modern Desktop - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the guided scenario to set up and configure a basic Modern Desktop from the Microsoft 365 Device Management portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/guided-scenarios-cloud-managed-pc</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure schedules to gradually roll out Windows Updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure schedules that manage how and when Windows updates roll out to your managed devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-rollout-options</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Intune security baselines for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that have preset and recommended configurations to the Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure device configuration profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or configure a device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Select the platform type, configure the settings, and add a scope tag. Learn more about applicability rules, and the policy refresh cycle times.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-create</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security firewall settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security firewall policy settings for Windows and macOS in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-firewall-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Microsoft Entra ID to Access Intune APIs in Microsoft Graph - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes steps needed for apps to use Microsoft Entra ID to access the Intune APIs in Microsoft Graph.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/intune-graph-apis</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security Account protection (Preview) policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security Account protection policy settings in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security Attack surface reduction settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Details about the settings in the endpoint security Attack surface reduction policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-asr-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings you can manage with Intune Endpoint Protection profiles for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the available settings in Intune endpoint protection profiles for managed Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-protection-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Update settings you can manage with Intune Update Ring policies for Windows devices. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings for Windows Update that you can manage through Intune policy for Update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft HoloLens 2 advanced security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune advanced security baseline for Microsoft HoloLens 2. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-hololens2-advanced</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft Edge security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline version 112 and later, for the Microsoft Edge browser. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-v2-edge-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft 365 Apps for Enterprise security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Office apps. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-v2-office-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Edge security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Edge browser. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of settings for the Microsoft HoloLens 2 standard security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune standard security baseline for Microsoft HoloLens 2. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-hololens2-standard</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Windows 365 Cloud PC security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Windows 365 Cloud PC. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-windows-365</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Default configuration of Intune's Windows security baselines - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the default setting configuration of the various Microsoft Intune security baselines for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-mdm-all</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Windows, Windows Holographic, and Surface Hub devices in Microsoft Intune. Check for compliance on the minimum and maximum operating system, set password restrictions and length, check for partner anti-virus (AV) solutions, enable encryption on data storage, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for iOS/iPadOS that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings for Microsoft Defender Antivirus for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the settings in the Microsoft Defender Antivirus profile for Windows devices. You can configure these settings as part of Endpoint security Antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Started With the Microsoft Intune App SDK - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Quickly enable your mobile app for mobile application management (MAM) with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View the Android device administrator compliance settings for Microsoft Intune compliance policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings that are available for Android device administrator devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android (AOSP) compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Android (AOSP) that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android-aosp</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security firewall settings for Configuration Manager devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security firewall policy settings for tenant attached devices you manage with Configuration Manager. You can configure firewall setting after you configure tenant attach for Configuration Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-firewall-profile-settings-tenant-attach</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antivirus policy settings for Windows Security experience policy for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security Antivirus policy settings for the Windows Security app in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-security-experience-windows-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings from Windows security settings for tenant attached devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the settings in the *Windows Security experience* profile for tenant attached devices. To use this Endpoint security Antivirus policy, you must first configure tenant attach for Configuration Manager for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-windows-security-settings-windows-tenant-attach</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 8.1 compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Windows 8.1 that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows-8-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Enterprise compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune. Set password rules, choose a minimum or maximum operating system version, restrict specific apps, prevent reusing password, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Tunnel VPN with iOS/iPad devices that don't enroll with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add support for Mobile Application Management (MAM) for iOS to the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. Tunnel support for MAM expands access to your organizational resources for devices that can't or haven't enrolled with Microsoft Intune. Admins should use this article to create policies that support per-app VPN in line of business (LOB) apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-mam-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use a PKCS certificate profile to provision devices with certificates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificates with Microsoft Intune, work with root certificates and certificate templates, and use device configuration profiles for a PKCS Certificate.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-pfx-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Hello for Business settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View details for Windows Hello for Business settings you configure in an Intune identity protection profile for device groups in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/identity-protection-windows-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the prerequisites for installation and use of the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. These include Linux servers, network, and firewall configurations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings from Microsoft Defender Antivirus for tenant attached devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the settings in the Microsoft Defender Antivirus profile for Windows devices managed by Configuration Manager. You can configure these settings as part of Endpoint security Antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune after you configure tenant attach for Configuration Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows-tenant-attach</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign MTD apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to add Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) apps, Microsoft Authenticator app, and iOS configuration policy in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-apps-ios-app-configuration-policy-add-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for macOS devices that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-mac-os</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Protection Policies Overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune Management Extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple Volume-Purchased Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Win32 App Supersedence - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Win32 app supersedence with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-supersedence</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually Add the Windows 10 Company Portal App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how your workforce can manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app to their PC from the Microsoft Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell Scripts for Remediations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>PowerShell script reference for Remediations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/powershell-scripts-remediation</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Web Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding web apps (client-server applications) to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/web-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Level Architecture for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This reference architecture shows options for integrating Microsoft Intune in your Azure environment with Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/high-level-architecture</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Protection for Windows MAM - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable protected MAM access to org data using Windows MAM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/protect-mam-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign an App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to add and assign an app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-add-assign-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Graph APIs to Export Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about exporting Intune reports using Graph APIs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-apis</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send Notifications to Noncompliant Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this topic, you use Microsoft Intune to send email notifications to noncompliant devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/quickstart-send-notification</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>