<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:33:23 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:33:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Retire or wipe devices using Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Retire or wipe a device on an Android, Android work profile, AOSP, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, or Windows device using Microsoft Intune. Also delete a device from Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/devices-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to assist users authenticated by your organization.</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure feature updates policy for Windows 10 Windows 11 devices in Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows feature updates. Configure and deploy policy to maintain the Windows feature version of Windows 10/11 devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-10-feature-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Properties catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Properties catalog policy to manage Device Inventory settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect diagnostics from an Intune managed device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics from an Intune managed device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find lost devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Locate lost or stolen devices by using the locate device feature in Microsoft Intune. Get details on security and privacy information when using the locate device action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-locate</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Windows Driver updates policy for Windows 10 Windows 11 devices in Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using Microsoft Intune policy to manage Windows driver updates on your Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-driver-updates-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disable Activation Lock on Apple devices with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune to disable Activation Lock on Apple devices to access locked devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-activation-lock-disable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the settings catalog to configure DDM software updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Apple's declarative device management (DDM) settings to install a specific update by an enforced deadline. This feature uses the settings catalog to configure managed software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS and managed macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/managed-software-updates-ios-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create device compliance policies for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/create-compliance-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run remote actions on devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to run remote actions on Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Windows devices. You can reset the password, lock the device, wipe or reset the OS, scan for viruses, and more. Use this feature to remotely manage devices and have help desk run common tasks.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View device details with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View your device details, including operating systems, storage space, manufacturer, and model. Get a list of installed apps, check compliance policies, and set up TeamViewer with Microsoft Intune in Azure. Similar to viewing inventory of the devices you manage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-inventory</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reset device passcodes with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Remove or reset the passcode by using the remove passcode action on devices you manage or monitor with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-passcode-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>ServiceNow integration enables help desk staff, who are licensed to use Remote Help, to use ServiceNow to view incidents and details of the tech issue that an employee is facing from the Troubleshooting pane. This article also describes how to configure ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/service-now-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sync devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Synchronize devices that are registered or managed with Microsoft Intune to get the latest policies and actions. Includes the steps to sync by using the Azure portal, and lists the error codes that can be retried.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add app configuration policies for managed Android Enterprise devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use app configuration policies in Microsoft Intune to supply settings when users run a Managed Google Play app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-use-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send custom notifications to users with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom push notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Windows Driver updates policy for Windows 10 Windows 11 devices in Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage policies that install Windows driver updates on your Intune managed Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-driver-updates-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a JSON file for custom compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create the JSON file that defines custom settings and values for use with device compliance policies in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-custom-json</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help on Android to assist users authenticated by your organization.</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app in Android, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activate iOS/iPadOS lost mode with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Turn on or start lost mode to customize a message that appears on the lock screen of a lost or stolen iOS/iPadOS device by using Microsoft Intune. And, get details on security and privacy information when you're using the lost mode action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-lost-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign a role to an Intune administrator</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign a built-in or custom role to a user in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/assign-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android FOTA Updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates on Android devices. A FOTA update can include software and security patches, feature updates, and other changes to the device's firmware.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/fota-updates-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use multiple administrative approvals in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure multi-admin approval to protect your tenant against the use of compromised administrative accounts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/multi-admin-approval</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Linux devices in Intune using the Intune app. Set an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for Android software updates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for Android devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on corporate owned Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for software updates on BYOD in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for BYOD and personally owned devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on personal devices on Android and iOS/iPadOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-personal-byod</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use bulk device actions in Microsoft Intune device.</title>
      <description>Use bulk remote device actions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/bulk-device-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy and personal data in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn what personal data is collected and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-personal-data</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune operated by 21Vianet in China</title>
      <description>Intune operated by 21Vianet in China.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/china</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit, export or delete personal data collected by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to audit, export, or delete personal data that is collected by Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-audit-export-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update cellular data plan for iOS/iPadOS devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to update the cellular data plan for iOS/iPadOS devices that support eSIM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/update-cellular-data-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data storage and processing in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how personal data is stored and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-store-process</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and assign a custom role in Intune</title>
      <description>Create and assign a custom role for a remote device manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remove a user from an iOS/iPadOS device with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a user from a shared iOS/iPadOS device with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optional diagnostic data that is collected by Intune client apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the optional diagnostic data that Intune Client apps collect.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/client-apps-optional-data</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View and correct personal data collected by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to view and correct personal data that's been collected by Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-view-correct</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Log out the user of an iOS/iPadOS device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to log out the current user of an iOS/iPadOS device with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-logout-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduce help desk costs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reducing help desk costs with self-service password reset</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/password-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shut down devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Shut down iOS/iPadOS devices using remote actions in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-shutdown</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Linux that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wipe a macOS device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wipe all data, including the operating system, from a macOS device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-wipe-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to manage software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor results of your device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the device compliance dashboard to understand overall device compliance the per policy and per setting device compliance results.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable use of Windows diagnostic data by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows diagnostic data in processor configuration for your tenant to enable its use by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/data-enable-windows-data</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows compatibility reports for Windows 10 and Windows 11 updates in Intune</title>
      <description>Use the app and driver compatibility reports for Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices before you deploy Intune policies for feature updates or update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-compatibility-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remotely administer devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the required roles to use TeamViewer, how to install the TeamViewer connector, and step-by-step guidance to remotely administer devices using Microsoft Intune in the Azure portal</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/teamviewer-support</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Update rings for Windows 10 and later policy in Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows update rings. You can configure, deploy, and pause update installation with Windows Update client policies using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-10-update-rings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Information Protection in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using Windows Information Protection with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-information-protection-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remove apps and configurations from devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how apps and configurations can be removed temporarily, then restored automatically or manually using the Remove apps and configuration device action by the IT administrator.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/remove-apps-config</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data collection in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about personal data collected in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-collect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Delivery Optimization settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure device configuration policy to manage Delivery Optimization settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/delivery-optimization-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zebra LifeGuard Over-the-Air Integration with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates for supported Zebra devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zebra-lifeguard-ota-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data security and sharing in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how personal data is secured and shared in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-secure-share</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin guide and checklist for macOS software updates</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updates for macOS devices using Microsoft Intune. Use this article to help manage software updates on your organization-owned devices, including how to create policies, manage updates, and review update status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use custom compliance settings for Linux and Windows devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage custom compliance settings for Linux and Windows devices by using JSON files and discovery scripts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-use-custom-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Windows Update client policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage Windows 10 and Windows 11 software updates by using Intune policy for Update rings for Windows and Windows feature updates for Windows Update client policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-for-business-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure schedules to gradually roll out Windows Updates in Intune</title>
      <description>Configure schedules that manage how and when Windows updates roll out to your managed devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-rollout-options</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help Web App. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help web app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-webapp</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Specialty devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides information about specialty devices and how can you manage them with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/specialty-devices-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune to expedite Windows quality updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to expedite the installation of Windows updates on managed devices as soon as possible.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-10-expedite-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows quality update policy</title>
      <description>Use Hotpatch updates to receive security updates without restarting your device</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-quality-update-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a custom role in Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a custom role in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compliance in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about compliance, dependencies, and features in Microsoft Intune supporting data protection and regulatory requirements.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/compliance-in-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune Suite add-on capabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune Suite unifies a series of mission-critical advanced endpoint management and security capabilities. The capabilities of the suite are integrated with Microsoft 365 and Microsoft Security across endpoint platforms for both cloud and on-premises co-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-add-ons</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Windows Update for Business reports for Windows Updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Windows Update for Business reports to view data for Windows Updates you deploy with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pause Config Refresh - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Config Refresh can be paused for a configurable period of time, after which it's automatically re-enabled, or can be manually turned back on at any time by an IT administrator.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/pause-config-refresh</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings insight</title>
      <description>The Settings insight feature adds insights giving you confidence in configurations that are successfully adopted by similar organizations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/settings-insight</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows backup and restore in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows backup and restore in Intune for employees or students.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-backup-restore</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-supervised-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View declarative device management-based software update reports for Apple devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to software updates reports for managed Apple devices based on Apples declarative device management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-reports-apple-declarative-based</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remotely lock devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote lock action in Microsoft Intune to lock a device that is protected by a PIN or password.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remote-lock</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rename a device with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Rename a device by using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rename</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find the primary user of a Microsoft Intune device.</title>
      <description>Find the primary user (or User Device Affinity) of an Intune device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/find-primary-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on macOS to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Remote Help to provide remote assistance to authenticated users and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up or sign in to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to sign up for a Microsoft Intune subscription or sign in to start with your subscription.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/account-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Remote Help on Android.</title>
      <description>Sometimes a Remote Help session starts in service but the client connection isn't established. Learn more about the possible causes in this article, and how to resolve them.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-android-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of Microsoft Intune device compliance, including tenant-wide compliance policy settings and device compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-compliance-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security policies and profiles to focus on security configuration of devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reset Windows 10 and 11 devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Fresh Start to remove or uninstall apps on Windows 10 and 11 by using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-fresh-start</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restart devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Restart Windows and iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune in the Azure portal using the Restart remote action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-restart</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Android Enterprise system apps in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Android Enterprise system apps in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-ae-system</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device restriction settings for Android in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>On Android Enterprise or Android for Work devices owned by your organization, you can restrict settings on the device using Microsoft Intune. Allow copy and paste, notifications, app permissions, data sharing, password length, sign in failures, use fingerprint to unlock, reuse passwords, and enable bluetooth sharing of work contacts. Configure devices as a dedicated device kiosk to run one app, or multiple apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APIs to onboard third party certificate authorities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or integrate the SCEP GitHub solution for third party certificate authorities (CA) to issue SCEP certificates to devices in Microsoft Intune. This solution includes Java and C# APIs that validate, send success and failure notifications to Intune, and use SSL socket factory when communicating with Intune. Also view an overview of the steps to test your SCEP CA configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/scep-libraries-apis</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS direct enrollment - Apple Configurator-Setup Assistant - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Apple Configurator to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices with Setup Assistant.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-configurator-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 22:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use direct enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy and enroll macOS devices in Microsoft Intune using direct enrollment with Apple Configurator.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-direct-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 22:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To enhance the security of your organization, set your users to run with standard permissions while Endpoint Privilege Management ensures those users can seamlessly run specified files with elevated rights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Win32 apps in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the most common methods to troubleshoot Win32 app issues with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Windows 365 Cloud PC security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Windows 365 Cloud PC. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-windows-365</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Copilot in Intune features overview</title>
      <description>Microsoft Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 14:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO and deploy the configuration to your macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using Microsoft Entra ID with the Secure Enclave, smart card, or password authentication methods. You create a settings catalog policy to configure the settings. This article is a step-by-step guide to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platform SSO scenarios for macOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure common Platform SSO scenarios for macOS devices. You can enable Kerberos SSO to on-premises Active Directory and cloud-based Microsoft Entra ID, use Touch ID biometric policy with Secure Enclave authentication, and enable SSO on non-Microsoft apps. You can also configure end user experience settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-scenarios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>