<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:54:21 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:54:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Migration guide to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deployment guide to set up, onboard, or move to Intune. These steps include moving from partner MDM providers, using co-management, moving from on-premises group policy, and moving from Office 365 device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-intune-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Tunnel VPN gateway with Conditional Access policies</title>
      <description>Configure your Azure tenant to support using Conditional Access policies to grant access to the Intune Microsoft Tunnel VPN gateway solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-conditional-access</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platforms and policy types supported by filters in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the supported apps, compliance policies, and device configuration profiles that support filters in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-supported-workloads</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the settings catalog to configure DDM software updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Apple's declarative device management (DDM) settings to install a specific update by an enforced deadline. This feature uses the settings catalog to configure managed software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS and managed macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/managed-software-updates-ios-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to manage software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin guide and checklist for macOS software updates</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updates for macOS devices using Microsoft Intune. Use this article to help manage software updates on your organization-owned devices, including how to create policies, manage updates, and review update status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using a Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported Microsoft Intune apps</title>
      <description>This article provides lists of support partner and Microsoft apps that are commonly used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-supported-intune-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for macOS</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned Macs into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Graph API - Reports and properties</title>
      <description>Learn about Intune reports and properties provided via Graph API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-available-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retire or wipe devices using Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Retire or wipe a device on an Android, Android work profile, AOSP, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, or Windows device using Microsoft Intune. Also delete a device from Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/devices-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure policies to manage Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure policies that define how Endpoint Privilege Management functions in your tenant, and behaviors when elevating files to run in administrative context.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Intune policies to configure and manage Windows LAPS</title>
      <description>Create policies to manage the Windows Local Administrator Policy Solution (LAPS) on Windows devices that enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-laps-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Zebra Mobility Extensions on Android devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and use Zebra devices running Android with Zebra Mobility Extensions (MX). See all the steps, including install the Company Portal app, sideload the app, assign device administrator role, create a StageNow profile, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/android-zebra-mx-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use OEMConfig on Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and use devices running Android Enterprise with OEMConfig. See all the steps, including an overview, see the prerequisites, create the configuration profile in Intune, and see a list of supported OEMConfig apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/android-oem-configuration-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 03:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to assist users authenticated by your organization.</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Cloud PKI for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>An overview of the Microsoft Cloud PKI service, available with Microsoft Intune Suite or as an Intune add-on.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Properties catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Properties catalog policy to manage Device Inventory settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Jamf Pro Cloud Connector to integrate Jamf Pro with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Jamf Cloud Connector to integrate Jamf Pro with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-jamf-cloud-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Jamf Mobile Threat Protection integration with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Jamf Mobile Threat Protection solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/jamf-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign MTD apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to add Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) apps, Microsoft Authenticator app, and iOS configuration policy in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-apps-ios-app-configuration-policy-add-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure iOS/iPadOS Enterprise SSO app extension with MDMs</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Microsoft Enterprise single sign-on (SSO) plug-in. Add or create an iOS or iPadOS device configuration profile using the Microsoft Enterprise SSO plug-in app extension in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-ios-ipados-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can use Security Copilot to get information about your Intune data, including devices, apps, policies, and groups managed in Intune. You can also compare policies, get device specific details, and get target info for policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Copilot in Intune features overview</title>
      <description>Microsoft Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Intune data with natural language and take action</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, use Explorer to query your data in natural language and run built-in queries that match your request. Copilot summarizes the results, and provides recommendations and actions based on the query results. You can also create policies that target users and groups in the query results. Use this feature to explore your Intune data, troubleshoot issues, and create custom reports.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-explorer</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Microsoft Surface Management Portal</title>
      <description>You can use Security Copilot to help you manage and monitor Surface devices at scale.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot-surface-portal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copilot in Intune shows device information and errors</title>
      <description>Microsoft Copilot in Intune can help you get information about your devices, compare devices, and get error information. Use this information to help you manage and troubleshoot device issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copilot in Intune FAQ</title>
      <description>Get answers to common questions when using Copilot in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-faq</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot the Enrollment Status Page (ESP) - Intune</title>
      <description>General troubleshooting guide for the Enrollment Status Page (ESP) for Windows Autopilot or OOBE for Microsoft Entra join.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/understand-troubleshoot-esp</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy OMA-URIs to target a CSP through Intune, and a comparison to on-premises - Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the significance of CSPs, Open Mobile Alliance – Uniform Resources (OMA-URIs), and how custom mobile device management (MDM) policies are delivered to a Windows 10-based device with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-configuration/deploy-oma-uris-to-target-csp-via-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot auto-enrolling existing Configuration Manager devices in Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Helps you understand and troubleshoot issues when you set up co-management by taking Path 1 - Auto-enroll existing Configuration Manager-managed devices into Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/comanage-configmgr/troubleshoot-co-management-auto-enrolling</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Windows 10 Intune auto-enrollment error 80180002b - Intune</title>
      <description>Fixes an issue in which Windows 10 Group Policy-based auto-enrollment to Microsoft Intune fails with the error code 0x80180002b in Event Viewer.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/windows10-enroll-error-80180002b</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Intune and Configuration Manager co-management workloads - Intune</title>
      <description>Helps you understand and troubleshoot issues that you may encounter when you configure workloads in an Intune and Configuration Manager co-management environment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/comanage-configmgr/troubleshoot-co-management-workloads</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error 0x87D13BA2 deploying a macOS LOB app in Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Fixes the 0x87D13BA2 error when you deploy a macOS LOB app that contains multiple components in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/app-management/error-0x87d13ba2-deploy-macos-lob-app</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to configure Android enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>This guide describes how to configure Android enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/configure-android-enterprise-devices-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDM enrollment error 0xcaa9001f for co-managed Windows devices - Intune</title>
      <description>Describes an issue in which MDM enrollment fails and generates error 0xcaa9001f for co-managed Windows devices that are Microsoft Entra hybrid joined and managed by using Configuration Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/mdm-enrollment-error-0xcaa9001f</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Microsoft Entra device registration and Windows Autopilot - Intune</title>
      <description>Provides tips for troubleshooting Microsoft Entra device registration and Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/azure-ad-device-registration-autopilot</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tips for assigning device password settings to Android Enterprise fully managed devices in Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Describes different behavior when a device restrictions profile that includes password settings is assigned to Android Enterprise fully managed devices before and after enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-configuration/assign-password-setting-android-fully-managed</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Configuration Management bootstrap with modern provisioning - Intune</title>
      <description>Helps you understand and troubleshoot issues that you may encounter when you set up co-management by taking path 2 - Bootstrap the Configuration Manager client with modern provisioning.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/comanage-configmgr/troubleshoot-co-management-bootstrap</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sysprep will not run correctly on a Windows 10 device that has been MDM enrolled - Intune</title>
      <description>Provides tips for troubleshooting when Sysprep will not run correctly on a Windows 10 device that has been enrolled in mobile device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/troubleshoot-sysprep-windows-10-device-enrolled-mdm</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error 0x80090014 installing NDES certificate - Intune</title>
      <description>Gives the resolution for an issue where the NDES connector for Microsoft Intune fails to install because the NDES certificate isn't installed.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/certificates/error-0x80090014-installing-ndes-certificate</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error 0x80004003 signing in to the Intune NDES Connector UI - Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot an unexpected error and an 0x80004003 error during sign-in to the Intune Certificate NDES UI when you configure NDES.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/certificates/ndes-connector-signin-error-80004003</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Update ring policies for Windows devices - Intune</title>
      <description>Provides troubleshooting guidance for configuring Update ring policies for Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-protection/troubleshoot-update-rings</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support Tip - Understanding the flow behind deployment, delivery, and processing of a Win32 application through Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>This article highlights and explains the flow that is associated with a Win32 app during its deployment, delivery, and processing through Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/app-management/develop-deliver-working-win32-app-via-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keychain error -25244 when enrolling macOS devices in Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Describes an issue in which you can't enroll a macOS device in Microsoft Intune because of stale or corrupted keychain entries.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/keychain-error-enrolling-macos-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot-agents-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to set up and use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent for Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/vulnerability-remediation-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune built-in roles reference</title>
      <description>Permissions reference for built-in roles for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control-reference</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard and Configure Devices with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint via Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune, including connecting the products, onboarding devices, and assigning policies for compliance and risk level assessment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/advanced-threat-protection-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared iPad devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Shared iPad devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-shared-ipad</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use multiple administrative approvals in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure multi-admin approval to protect your tenant against the use of compromised administrative accounts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/multi-admin-approval</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 17:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Windows LAPS with Microsoft Intune policies</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune application protection policy to manage the local administrator accounts on Windows devices. Through the Windows LAPS CSP, back up accounts and passwords to Microsoft Entra ID, define password requirements, and protect account passwords through scheduled password rotations and manual rotations at need.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-laps-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Use Microsoft Intune to protect Exchange Online email from unmanaged iOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune app protection policies and Conditional Access to prevent unmanaged iOS devices from accessing Exchange Online.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/tutorial-protect-email-on-unmanaged-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 03:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Install and configure Microsoft Tunnel Gateway on a Linux server to support Intune managed cloud-based devices in connecting to your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add groups to organize users and devices for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Microsoft Entra groups to organize users and devices for use with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/groups-add</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign a role to an Intune administrator</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign a built-in or custom role to a user in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/assign-role</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure a custom domain name - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a custom domain name for your Microsoft Intune subscription</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/custom-domain-name-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View ChromeOS device information</title>
      <description>View ChromeOS devices and details synced with the Chrome Enterprise connector in the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/chrome-enterprise-device-details</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags for distributed IT - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags to filter configuration profiles to specific roles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/scope-tags</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Microsoft Intune licenses</title>
      <description>Assign licenses to users so they can enroll in Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/licenses-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a custom role in Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a custom role in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add users to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add and managing Microsoft Entra user accounts from within Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/users-add</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up or sign in to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to sign up for a Microsoft Intune subscription or sign in to start with your subscription.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/account-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use SCEP certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and assign Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-profile-scep</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Intune sends to Google - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>List of data that Intune sends to Google when Android enterprise device management is enabled with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/data-intune-sends-to-google</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an Enterprise App Catalog app to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add an Enterprise App Catalog app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-enterprise-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Android, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows devices in Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set the mobile device management authority - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to set the mobile device management authority in Microsoft Intune and some key considerations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/mdm-authority-set</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, or create settings on iOS/iPadOS devices to restrict features in Microsoft Intune. Create password requirements, control the locked screen, use built-in apps, add restricted or approved apps, handle bluetooth devices, connect to the cloud for backup and storage, enable kiosk mode, add domains, and control how users interact with the Safari web browser.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1 for deploying or setting up Intune. The starting point is to review supported configurations, sign up for the trial, configure the custom domain name, add users and groups to Intune, assign licenses to users, manage roles, grant admin permissions, and set the MDM authority.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign device profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to assign device configuration profiles and policies to users and devices. Learn how to exclude groups from a profile assignment in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiosk settings for Windows 10/11 in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your Windows 10/11 client devices as single-app and multi-app kiosks, customize the start menu, add apps, show the task bar, and configure a web browser in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kiosk-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device restriction settings for Windows 10/11 in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings and their descriptions for creating device restrictions on Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a configuration profile to control screenshots, password requirements, kiosk settings, apps in the store, Microsoft Edge browser, Microsoft Defender, access to the cloud, start menu, and more in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Administrative templates in Microsoft Intune to create groups of settings for Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a device configuration profile. You can control Office programs, Microsoft Edge, access OneDrive, use remote desktop, enable Auto-Play, set power management settings, use HTTP printing, control user sign-in, and change the event log size.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS device enrollment guide for  Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll macOS devices using device enrollment, automated device enrollment (DEP), and Apple Configurator enrollment options in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to import and analyze group policies</title>
      <description>Import and analyze your group policy objects using the Group Policy analytics tool. See the policies that are supported and aren't supported in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/group-policy-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Universal Print policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to create a Universal Print policy for Windows 10/11 client devices. The policy automatically installs printers on your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-printer-provisioning</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android (AOSP) device management in Intune for corporate-owned userless devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for corporate-owned userless devices built on the Android Open Source Project (AOSP) platform.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-aosp-corporate-owned-userless-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported filter device and app properties &amp; operators in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>When using filters, get more information on the device properties, supported operators, and supported Windows OS SKUs, including examples. Use these features to create rule expressions in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-device-properties</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or configure a device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Select the platform type, configure the settings, and add a scope tag. Learn more about applicability rules, and the policy refresh cycle times.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-create</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure macOS Enterprise SSO app extension with MDMs</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Microsoft Enterprise single sign-on (SSO) app extension plug-in. Add or create an macOS device profile using the SSO app extension in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-macos-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict devices features using policy in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a device configuration profile to restrict features on Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, AOSP, macOS, iOS, iPadOS, and Windows 10/11 client devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Wi-Fi profile for devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the steps to create a Wi-Fi device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Create profiles for Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, Android kiosk, iOS, iPadOS, macOS, Windows 10/11, and Windows Holographic for Business. Use these profiles to create a WiFi connection to use certificates, choose an EAP type, select an authentication method, enable a proxy, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>