<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:54:23 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:54:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage volume-purchased iOS/iPadOS eBooks - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync books you purchased in volume from the iOS store with Intune. You can then manage and track usage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-ebooks-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the prerequisites for installation and use of the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. These include Linux servers, network, and firewall configurations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple volume-purchased apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using a Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policies overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect Intune account to managed Google Play account - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect your Intune account to your Managed Google Play account.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/connect-intune-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App configuration policies for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use app configuration policies on an iOS/iPadOS or Android device in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-protect-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data protection for Windows MAM</title>
      <description>Enable protected MAM access to org data using Windows MAM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/protect-mam-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android with Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft 365 (Office) for iOS and Android to ensure collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-office</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Intune SDK integration into your iOS app</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Intune SDK integration into your iOS app</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase3</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Application Management (MAM) and Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the available features when deciding to use Mobile Application Management (MAM) and/or Android Enterprise personally-owned work profiles for personal or BYOD Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/android-deployment-scenarios-app-protection-work-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Plan the integration</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Plan the integration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-advanced-threat-protection-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review app protection policy logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Get started with MAM</title>
      <description>Get started with Intune before incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase3</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - MAM integration essentials</title>
      <description>Understand MAM integration essentials to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase4</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data storage and processing in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how personal data is stored and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-store-process</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - MSAL prerequisite and setup</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. MSAL prerequisite and setup</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - App participation features</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. App participation features</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase4</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - MSAL Prerequisite</title>
      <description>Understand the MSAL prerequisite to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - App participation features</title>
      <description>Understand App participation features when incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase7</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business</title>
      <description>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-2-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android lets you incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-appendix</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - App Protection CA support (optional)</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. App Protection CA support (optional)</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase6</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Multi-Identity</title>
      <description>Understand Multi-Identity when incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase5</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Multi-Identity</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Multi-Identity</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase5</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense for App Protection Policy</title>
      <description>Step 3. Integrate Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-3-scc</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 6. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business data security</title>
      <description>Step 6. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business corporate data security in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-6-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App protection policy settings for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy (APP) settings for MAM on Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to wipe only corporate data from apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to selectively wipe only corporate data from Intune-managed apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-selective-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Teams for iOS and Android with Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Teams for iOS and Android to ensure team collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-teams</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android with Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data collection in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about personal data collected in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-collect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Appendix</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Appendix</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-appendix</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage device operating system versions with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the methods for managing device operating system versions supported by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/manage-os-versions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure app protection policies for Windows 10/11 - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to configure app protection policies for Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-configure-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign Managed Google Play apps to Android Enterprise devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how to synchronize and assign apps to Android Enterprise devices from the Managed Google Play store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Plan the integration</title>
      <description>Plan the integration to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a custom role in Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a custom role in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data protection framework using app protection policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how app protection policies ensure an organization's data remains safe or contained in a managed app, regardless of whether the device is enrolled.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage transferring data between iOS apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how to use mobile app management policies in Microsoft Intune to manage data transfers between apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/data-transfer-between-apps-manage-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use OEMConfig on Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and use devices running Android Enterprise with OEMConfig. See all the steps, including an overview, see the prerequisites, create the configuration profile in Intune, and see a list of supported OEMConfig apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/android-oem-configuration-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovered apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand details about the detected apps that Intune found on a device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-discovered-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and deploy app protection policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to create and assign Microsoft Intune app protection policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS developer guide - Web-view features</title>
      <description>The Microsoft Intune App SDK for iOS lets you incorporate Intune app protection policies (also known as MAM policies) into your native iOS app. Web-view features</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-ios-phase7</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Outlook for iOS and Android with Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Outlook for iOS and Android to ensure team collaboration experiences are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-outlook</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure your corporate data using Microsoft Edge for Business</title>
      <description>Secure your corporate data in Microsoft Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device restriction settings for Android in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>On Android Enterprise or Android for Work devices owned by your organization, you can restrict settings on the device using Microsoft Intune. Allow copy and paste, notifications, app permissions, data sharing, password length, sign in failures, use fingerprint to unlock, reuse passwords, and enable bluetooth sharing of work contacts. Configure devices as a dedicated device kiosk to run one app, or multiple apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - App configuration</title>
      <description>Understand app configuration features when incorporating Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase6</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration guide to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deployment guide to set up, onboard, or move to Intune. These steps include moving from partner MDM providers, using co-management, moving from on-premises group policy, and moving from Office 365 device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-intune-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Tunnel VPN gateway with Conditional Access policies</title>
      <description>Configure your Azure tenant to support using Conditional Access policies to grant access to the Intune Microsoft Tunnel VPN gateway solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-conditional-access</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platforms and policy types supported by filters in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the supported apps, compliance policies, and device configuration profiles that support filters in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-supported-workloads</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the settings catalog to configure DDM software updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Apple's declarative device management (DDM) settings to install a specific update by an enforced deadline. This feature uses the settings catalog to configure managed software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS and managed macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/managed-software-updates-ios-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to manage software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin guide and checklist for macOS software updates</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updates for macOS devices using Microsoft Intune. Use this article to help manage software updates on your organization-owned devices, including how to create policies, manage updates, and review update status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported Microsoft Intune apps</title>
      <description>This article provides lists of support partner and Microsoft apps that are commonly used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-supported-intune-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for macOS</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned Macs into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Graph API - Reports and properties</title>
      <description>Learn about Intune reports and properties provided via Graph API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-available-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retire or wipe devices using Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Retire or wipe a device on an Android, Android work profile, AOSP, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, or Windows device using Microsoft Intune. Also delete a device from Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/devices-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure policies to manage Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure policies that define how Endpoint Privilege Management functions in your tenant, and behaviors when elevating files to run in administrative context.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Intune policies to configure and manage Windows LAPS</title>
      <description>Create policies to manage the Windows Local Administrator Policy Solution (LAPS) on Windows devices that enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-laps-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Zebra Mobility Extensions on Android devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and use Zebra devices running Android with Zebra Mobility Extensions (MX). See all the steps, including install the Company Portal app, sideload the app, assign device administrator role, create a StageNow profile, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/android-zebra-mx-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 03:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to assist users authenticated by your organization.</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Cloud PKI for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>An overview of the Microsoft Cloud PKI service, available with Microsoft Intune Suite or as an Intune add-on.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Properties catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Properties catalog policy to manage Device Inventory settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Jamf Pro Cloud Connector to integrate Jamf Pro with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Jamf Cloud Connector to integrate Jamf Pro with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-jamf-cloud-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Jamf Mobile Threat Protection integration with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Jamf Mobile Threat Protection solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/jamf-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign MTD apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to add Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) apps, Microsoft Authenticator app, and iOS configuration policy in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-apps-ios-app-configuration-policy-add-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure iOS/iPadOS Enterprise SSO app extension with MDMs</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Microsoft Enterprise single sign-on (SSO) plug-in. Add or create an iOS or iPadOS device configuration profile using the Microsoft Enterprise SSO plug-in app extension in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-ios-ipados-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can use Security Copilot to get information about your Intune data, including devices, apps, policies, and groups managed in Intune. You can also compare policies, get device specific details, and get target info for policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Copilot in Intune features overview</title>
      <description>Microsoft Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Intune data with natural language and take action</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, use Explorer to query your data in natural language and run built-in queries that match your request. Copilot summarizes the results, and provides recommendations and actions based on the query results. You can also create policies that target users and groups in the query results. Use this feature to explore your Intune data, troubleshoot issues, and create custom reports.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-explorer</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Microsoft Surface Management Portal</title>
      <description>You can use Security Copilot to help you manage and monitor Surface devices at scale.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/security-copilot-surface-portal</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copilot in Intune shows device information and errors</title>
      <description>Microsoft Copilot in Intune can help you get information about your devices, compare devices, and get error information. Use this information to help you manage and troubleshoot device issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copilot in Intune FAQ</title>
      <description>Get answers to common questions when using Copilot in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-faq</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot the Enrollment Status Page (ESP) - Intune</title>
      <description>General troubleshooting guide for the Enrollment Status Page (ESP) for Windows Autopilot or OOBE for Microsoft Entra join.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/understand-troubleshoot-esp</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy OMA-URIs to target a CSP through Intune, and a comparison to on-premises - Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the significance of CSPs, Open Mobile Alliance – Uniform Resources (OMA-URIs), and how custom mobile device management (MDM) policies are delivered to a Windows 10-based device with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-configuration/deploy-oma-uris-to-target-csp-via-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot auto-enrolling existing Configuration Manager devices in Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Helps you understand and troubleshoot issues when you set up co-management by taking Path 1 - Auto-enroll existing Configuration Manager-managed devices into Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/comanage-configmgr/troubleshoot-co-management-auto-enrolling</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Windows 10 Intune auto-enrollment error 80180002b - Intune</title>
      <description>Fixes an issue in which Windows 10 Group Policy-based auto-enrollment to Microsoft Intune fails with the error code 0x80180002b in Event Viewer.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/windows10-enroll-error-80180002b</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Intune and Configuration Manager co-management workloads - Intune</title>
      <description>Helps you understand and troubleshoot issues that you may encounter when you configure workloads in an Intune and Configuration Manager co-management environment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/comanage-configmgr/troubleshoot-co-management-workloads</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error 0x87D13BA2 deploying a macOS LOB app in Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Fixes the 0x87D13BA2 error when you deploy a macOS LOB app that contains multiple components in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/app-management/error-0x87d13ba2-deploy-macos-lob-app</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to configure Android enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>This guide describes how to configure Android enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/configure-android-enterprise-devices-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDM enrollment error 0xcaa9001f for co-managed Windows devices - Intune</title>
      <description>Describes an issue in which MDM enrollment fails and generates error 0xcaa9001f for co-managed Windows devices that are Microsoft Entra hybrid joined and managed by using Configuration Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/mdm-enrollment-error-0xcaa9001f</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Microsoft Entra device registration and Windows Autopilot - Intune</title>
      <description>Provides tips for troubleshooting Microsoft Entra device registration and Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-enrollment/azure-ad-device-registration-autopilot</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tips for assigning device password settings to Android Enterprise fully managed devices in Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Describes different behavior when a device restrictions profile that includes password settings is assigned to Android Enterprise fully managed devices before and after enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-configuration/assign-password-setting-android-fully-managed</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Configuration Management bootstrap with modern provisioning - Intune</title>
      <description>Helps you understand and troubleshoot issues that you may encounter when you set up co-management by taking path 2 - Bootstrap the Configuration Manager client with modern provisioning.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/comanage-configmgr/troubleshoot-co-management-bootstrap</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>