<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:05:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration guide to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deployment guide to set up, onboard, or move to Intune. These steps include moving from partner MDM providers, using co-management, moving from on-premises group policy, and moving from Office 365 device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-intune-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is device management? - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about what device management means and how it can help organizations, including Microsoft 365 small &amp; medium business, and enterprise. See a list of features and benefits, including mobile device management (MDM) and mobile application management (MAM), and learn about Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-device-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Windows virtual machines with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the general guidelines for using Windows 10/11 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-10-virtual-machines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune capabilities that can help you protect your devices and data against unauthorized access and other threats.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-protect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune servicing information and details - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the frequency of the Microsoft Intune service updates, the release cadence, and how to check your tenant release version.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-service-servicing-information</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy and personal data in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn what personal data is collected and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-personal-data</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See an overview of the steps to start using Intune. Plan your move and deployment of Intune, determine your licensing needs and any platform requirements, use compliance and Conditional Access, deploy apps, create device configuration profiles, and enroll your devices to be managed. Get more information on mobile application management for BYOD or personal devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/get-started-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View device details with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View your device details, including operating systems, storage space, manufacturer, and model. Get a list of installed apps, check compliance policies, and set up TeamViewer with Microsoft Intune in Azure. Similar to viewing inventory of the devices you manage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-inventory</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add users to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add and managing Microsoft Entra user accounts from within Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/users-add</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Linux device management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Linux device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune manages users and devices, simplifies app management and automated policy deployment, and integrates with mobile threat defense. It connects to Managed Google Play, Apple tokens and certificates, and Teamviewer for remote assistance. Can use MDM or MAM to protect data, configure devices, and simplify access to company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, administrative templates (ADMX), and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrally manage Admin Tasks - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Centrally manage admin tasks in Microsoft Intune. Use the unified Admin tasks view to organize and act on administrative tasks from Device Offboarding, Endpoint Privilege Management, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/admin-tasks</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Mobile Threat Defense connector in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable the connector between your Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) partner and Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-connector-enable</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions for Endpoint Privilege Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A list of frequently asked questions for customers deploying Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-frequently-asked-questions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use OEMConfig on Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage and use devices running Android Enterprise with OEMConfig. See all the steps, including an overview, see the prerequisites, create the configuration profile in Intune, and see a list of supported OEMConfig apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/android-oem-configuration-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) with your Mobile Threat Defense partner to protect access to company resources based on device risk.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mobile-threat-defense</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan and Prepare for Endpoint Privilege Management Deployment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan your Endpoint Privilege Management deploying by understanding requirements, fundamentals, and security recommendations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Corporate Data in Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure your corporate data in Microsoft Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business across all platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set permissions to Managed Home Screen using Android Enterprise OEMConfig - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add the Samsung Knox Service Plugin, Zebra OEMConfig Powered by MX, and Legacy Zebra OEMConfig apps to Intune, and use the app schemas to configure permissions for the Managed Home Screen (MHS) app on Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/oemconfig-managed-home-screen-permissions-android</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud PKI CA Expiration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to renew a certificate authority (CA) in Microsoft Cloud PKI to maintain continuous certificate issuance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/renew-ca</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating elevation rules with Endpoint Privilege Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View guidance on how to create strong file elevation rules with Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-elevation-rules</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Windows Update Packages in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to deploy a Windows update package (.msu file) in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-deploy-update-package</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Scopes in endpoint analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use device scopes in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics with scope tags for custom device reporting and targeted insights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/advanced-analytics/device-scopes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune Management Extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft 365 Apps to Windows Devices Using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to install Microsoft 365 apps on Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-office365</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Win32 Apps in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the most common methods to troubleshoot Win32 app issues with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows App Deployment by Using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Windows app deployment scenarios available with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-windows-10-app-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually Add the Windows Company Portal App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how your workforce can manually add the Windows Company Portal app to their PC from the Microsoft Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Protection for Windows MAM - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable protected MAM access to org data using Windows MAM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/protect-mam-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review App Protection Policy Logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and Assign an App Protection Policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create and assign an app protection policy in Microsoft Intune to protect your organization's data. Get step-by-step guidance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-create-assign-app-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare a Win32 App to Be Uploaded to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to prepare a Win32 app to be uploaded to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-prepare</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win32 App Management in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune. This article provides an overview of the Intune Win32 app delivery and management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add apps to Microsoft Intune so you can assign apps to users and devices. Intune supports a wide range of app types.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign Win32 Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add, assign, and manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-add</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Protection Framework Using App Protection Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how app protection policies ensure an organization's data remains safe or contained in a managed app, regardless of whether the device is enrolled.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovered Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand details about the detected apps that Intune found on a device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-discovered-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Edge for Windows to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Edge for Windows to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-windows-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add PowerShell Scripts to Windows Devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and run PowerShell scripts, assign the script policy to Microsoft Entra groups, and use reports to monitor the scripts. See the steps to delete scripts you add on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune. Read common issues and resolutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/powershell-scripts</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard and Configure Devices with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint via Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune, including connecting the products, onboarding devices, and assigning policies for compliance and risk level assessment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-integrate</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring your own certificate authority with Cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a Microsoft Cloud PKI BYOCA issuing CA in Intune and anchor it to an on-premises or private CA.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/configure-byoca</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune cloud PKI fundamentals - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes fundamentals for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/fundamentals</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Cloud PKI root and issuing CA for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure a root and issuing CA for the Microsoft Cloud PKI service.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/configure-ca</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment models for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the deployment options for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit logs for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get audit logs for Microsoft cloud public key infrastructure (PKI) activity in the admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/audit-logs</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune Suite add-on capabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune Suite unifies a series of mission-critical advanced endpoint management and security capabilities. The capabilities of the suite are integrated with Microsoft 365 and Microsoft Security across endpoint platforms for both cloud and on-premises co-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-add-ons</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Cloud PKI for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>An overview of the Microsoft Cloud PKI service, available with Microsoft Intune Suite or as an Intune add-on.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delete issued PKI certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Delete certificates issued via Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/delete</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor issued PKI certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor reports for certificates issued via Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automatic enrollment in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment of Windows devices that join or register with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/quickstart-setup-auto-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Android, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows devices in Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up or sign in to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to sign up for a Microsoft Intune subscription or sign in to start with your subscription.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/account-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign Up for Microsoft Intune Free Trial Setup Guide - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Sign up for a Microsoft Intune free trial and configure your tenant. Learn the setup process, prerequisites, and how to configure domain names. Start evaluating Intune today.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/free-trial-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1 for deploying or setting up Intune. The starting point is to review supported configurations, sign up for the trial, configure the custom domain name, add users and groups to Intune, assign licenses to users, manage roles, grant admin permissions, and set the MDM authority.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Monitor App Protection Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to monitor app protection policies in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Service Description - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a cloud-based service that helps you manage Windows, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/microsoft-intune-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Configure Slack to Use Intune for EMM and App Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this tutorial you will configure Slack to use Intune for EMM and app configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/tutorial-configure-slack-enterprise-grid</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense for App Protection Policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense signals with Microsoft Edge for Business app protection policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-3-scc</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 4. Create App Configuration Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4. Create app configuration policies for Microsoft Edge for Business across Windows, Android, and iOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-4-acp-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-1-mamca</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 2. Create App Protection Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business across Windows, Android, and iOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-2-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 5. Create Settings Catalog policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 5. Create Settings Catalog policies for Microsoft Edge for Business on Windows and macOS.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-5-settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 6. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business End User Experience for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 6. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business end user experience Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-6-end-user-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 7. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business Data Security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 7. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business corporate data security in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-7-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune-Migration Guide - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Follow this migration guide to move your mobile device management from Microsoft 365 Basic Mobility and Security to Intune. Includes policy mapping and license assignment steps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/migrate-to-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Access requirements policy mapping from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A detailed list of the policy map between Basic Mobility and Security access requirements and Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-map-access-requirements</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configurations policy mapping from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A detailed list of the policy map between Basic Mobility and Security configurations and Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-map-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous policy mapping from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A detailed miscellaneous policy map between Basic Mobility and Security access requirements and Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-map-miscellaneous</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Route logs to Azure Monitor using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Diagnostics Settings to send audit logs and operational logs in Microsoft Intune to Azure Storage account, Event Hubs, or Log Analytics. Choose how long you want to keep the data, and see some estimated costs for different size tenants.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/review-logs-using-azure-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Send Custom Notifications - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send Email Notifications to Noncompliant Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create notification templates and send email alerts to users with noncompliant devices in Microsoft Intune. Configure actions for noncompliance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/quickstart-send-notification</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll a Windows device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll a Windows device into Microsoft Intune. Follow this step-by-step evaluation guide to test device enrollment and verify it in the Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/quickstart-enroll-windows-device</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign an App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add and assign apps to user groups in Microsoft Intune. Ensure your workforce has access to the apps they need.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-add-assign-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a user in Intune and assign a license - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a user in Microsoft Intune and assign an Intune license to this user.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try Microsoft Intune for free - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Evaluate Microsoft Intune with a free trial. Step through common settings, enroll devices, create policies, and learn about cloud-based device management. Start your trial today.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/try-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Password Compliance Policy for Android Enterprise - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a password compliance policy in Microsoft Intune for Android Enterprise devices. Learn to require specific password lengths to meet your organization's security requirements.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/quickstart-set-password-length-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create an Email Device Profile for iOS/iPadOS Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create an email device profile in Microsoft Intune for iOS/iPadOS devices. Configure email settings to help users securely access organization email.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/quickstart-email-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and assign a custom role in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create and assign a custom Intune RBAC role with specific permissions for security operations. Follow this guide to implement least privilege access.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Group to Manage Users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a group in Microsoft Intune and add users to the groups. Use groups to manage user access to company resources and assign policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-group</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center copy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices copy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Wipe - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wipe, or factory reset, devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Intune for Device Compliance - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) solution to enforce device compliance and prevent security breaches.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the prerequisites for installation and use of the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. These include Linux servers, network, and firewall configurations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple Volume-Purchased Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an iOS/iPadOS Line-of-Business App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add an iOS/iPadOS line-of-business (LOB) app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>