<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 17:42:38 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 17:42:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment models for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the deployment options for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-deployment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor your Endpoint Privilege Management policies for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View reports for managed and unmanaged file elevations when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Elevation Settings for Endpoint Privilege Management</title>
      <description>View guidance on how to manage the Endpoint Privilege Management client, including reporting level and default elevation response.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-elevation-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review the type of data that Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management collects</title>
      <description>View details about the type of data Endpoint Privilege Management can collect and store when used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-data-collection</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known Issues for Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure policies that define how Endpoint Privilege Management functions in your tenant, and behaviors when elevating files to run in administrative context.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-known-issues</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrator to standard user</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for using Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrators to standard users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-transition-administrator-to-standard-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for deploying Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions for Endpoint Privilege Management</title>
      <description>A list of frequently asked questions for customers deploying Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-frequently-asked-questions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating elevation rules with Endpoint Privilege Management</title>
      <description>View guidance on how to create strong file elevation rules with Microsoft Intune Endpoint Privilege Management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-elevation-rules</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use EPM support approvals for file elevation requests with Intune</title>
      <description>Manage support approvals for elevation requests when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-support-approved</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To enhance the security of your organization, set your users to run with standard permissions while Endpoint Privilege Management ensures those users can seamlessly run specified files with elevated rights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use reusable groups of settings policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage groups of settings for Intune profiles as a single object and then add that settings group object to multiple profile instances. Later changes you make to the settings groups  automatically apply to each profile that includes the reusable settings group.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/reusable-settings-groups</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan and Prepare for Endpoint Privilege Management Deployment</title>
      <description>Plan your Endpoint Privilege Management deploying by understanding requirements, fundamentals, and security recommendations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center copy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices copy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device restriction settings for Android in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>On Android Enterprise or Android for Work devices owned by your organization, you can restrict settings on the device using Microsoft Intune. Allow copy and paste, notifications, app permissions, data sharing, password length, sign in failures, use fingerprint to unlock, reuse passwords, and enable bluetooth sharing of work contacts. Configure devices as a dedicated device kiosk to run one app, or multiple apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Windows 10, Windows 11, Windows Holographic, and Surface Hub devices in Microsoft Intune. Check for compliance on the minimum and maximum operating system, set password restrictions and length, check for partner anti-virus (AV) solutions, enable encryption on data storage, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure compliance policies with actions for noncompliance in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your compliance policies with one or more actions for noncompliance to protect devices and your organization from unprotected devices. Actions can remotely lock devices, send email or notifications to device users, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/actions-for-noncompliance</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create device compliance policies for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/create-compliance-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for iOS/iPadOS that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create discovery scripts for custom compliance policy in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create scripts for Linux or Windows devices to discover the settings you define as custom compliance settings for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-custom-script</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use app-based Conditional Access policies with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using app-based Conditional Access policies with Microsoft Intune for both enrolled and unenrolled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/app-based-conditional-access-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a JSON file for custom compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create the JSON file that defines custom settings and values for use with device compliance policies in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-custom-json</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View the Android device administrator compliance settings for Microsoft Intune compliance policies</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings that are available for Android device administrator devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android (AOSP) compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Android (AOSP) that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android-aosp</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compliance for Windows Subsystem for Linux</title>
      <description>Evaluate WSL attributes on a host device for compliance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-wsl</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 8.1 compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Windows 8.1 that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows-8-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Enterprise compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the settings you can use when setting compliance for your Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune. Set password rules, choose a minimum or maximum operating system version, restrict specific apps, prevent reusing password, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-android-for-work</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for Linux that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor results of your device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the device compliance dashboard to understand overall device compliance the per policy and per setting device compliance results.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up app-based Conditional Access policies with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Conditional Access policies that work with Intune app protection policies</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/app-based-conditional-access-intune-create</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use custom compliance settings for Linux and Windows devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage custom compliance settings for Linux and Windows devices by using JSON files and discovery scripts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-use-custom-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS device compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the device compliance settings for macOS devices that you can manage with Microsoft Intune compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-policy-create-mac-os</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up device-based Conditional Access policies with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure a device-based Conditional Access policy that uses device status from a Microsoft Intune device compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/create-conditional-access-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenarios for using Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Conditional Access is commonly used with Intune compliance policy for devices and apps</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-intune-common-ways-use</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Jamf Pro Cloud Connector to integrate Jamf Pro with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Jamf Cloud Connector to integrate Jamf Pro with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-jamf-cloud-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to detect and fix support issues</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune compliance policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Combine Conditional Access with Intune compliance policies to define the requirements that users and devices must meet before gaining access your organizations resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Tunnel VPN with iOS/iPad devices that don't enroll with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add support for Mobile Application Management (MAM) for iOS to the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. Tunnel support for MAM expands access to your organizational resources for devices that can't or haven't enrolled with Microsoft Intune. Admins should use this article to create policies that support per-app VPN in line of business (LOB) apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-mam-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune compliance and Microsoft Entra Conditional Access policies with Jamf Pro - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Intune compliance policies and Microsoft Entra Conditional Access to help secure Jamf-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-assign-jamf</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Graph API - Reports and properties</title>
      <description>Learn about Intune reports and properties provided via Graph API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports-export-graph-available-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add PowerShell scripts to Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and run PowerShell scripts, assign the script policy to Microsoft Entra groups, and use reports to monitor the scripts. See the steps to delete scripts you add on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune. Read common issues and resolutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/powershell-scripts</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually configure Jamf Pro integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manually configure Jamf Pro integration with Intune when you can't use the Jamf Cloud Connector.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-integrate-jamf</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of Microsoft Intune device compliance, including tenant-wide compliance policy settings and device compliance policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-compliance-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retire or wipe devices using Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Retire or wipe a device on an Android, Android work profile, AOSP, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, or Windows device using Microsoft Intune. Also delete a device from Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/devices-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for US government deployments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the list of US government endpoint URLs that Intune needs and requires. Allow the ports, IP addresses, and endpoint URLs in your proxy server configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-us-government-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network access control integration with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Network access control (NAC) solutions check enrollment and compliance for devices with Intune. NAC includes certain behaviors and works with Conditional Access. See the steps to get onboarded, and get a list of partner solutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/network-access-control-integrate</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure the Microsoft Managed Home Screen app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-managed-home-screen-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign device profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to assign device configuration profiles and policies to users and devices. Learn how to exclude groups from a profile assignment in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to import and analyze group policies</title>
      <description>Import and analyze your group policy objects using the Group Policy analytics tool. See the policies that are supported and aren't supported in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/group-policy-analytics</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, Windows Information Protection, administrative templates, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate your imported group policy to a policy in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>After you import your Windows group policy objects in Microsoft Intune, use the migrate feature to transfer your GPOs to a Settings Catalog policy. This policy uses your imported GPOs, and can be assigned to users and devices managed by your organizations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/group-policy-analytics-migrate</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide for Windows device management</title>
      <description>Use our platform deployment guide to set up Windows device management in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security, email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4 to deploy device configuration profiles as part of the minimum set of policies for your devices using Microsoft Intune. The starting point is to enable the firewall, install AV, scan for malware, install software updates, create a strong PIN policy, and create email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-configuration-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Store apps to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Store apps to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-microsoft</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To support hybrid and remote workers, convert or migrate your workloads to support cloud-native endpoints. This planning guide focuses on deploying apps and updates with Intune, moving from Group Policy Objects, and using Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-endpoints-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Import custom and third-party partner ADMX templates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>You can add, upload, or import custom and third-party partner ADMX and ADML files in Microsoft Intune. When they're imported, create a device configuration profile and assign the profile to your Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-import-custom</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use derived credentials for mobile devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a third-party partners derived credential as an authentication method for Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/derived-credentials</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune user help</title>
      <description>Enroll your device in Intune to gain secure access to work-related email, apps, and Wi-Fi.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/user-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to set up and use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent for Security Copilot in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/vulnerability-remediation-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure schedules to gradually roll out Windows Updates in Intune</title>
      <description>Configure schedules that manage how and when Windows updates roll out to your managed devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-update-rollout-options</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Administrative templates in Microsoft Intune to create groups of settings for Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a device configuration profile. You can control Office programs, Microsoft Edge, access OneDrive, use remote desktop, enable Auto-Play, set power management settings, use HTTP printing, control user sign-in, and change the event log size.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict USB devices using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to restrict USB devices, including thumb drives, flash drives, USB cameras, and more. Use other settings to allow specific USB devices on Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-restrict-usb</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Universal Print policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to create a Universal Print policy for Windows 10/11 client devices. The policy automatically installs printers on your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-printer-provisioning</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Defender for Endpoint in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/advanced-threat-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common tasks and features in the settings catalog</title>
      <description>Use the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure common features. You can create a Universal Print policy, configure Microsoft Edge and Google Chrome web browsers, and use built in settings instead of plist files for macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-common-features</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Microsoft 365 apps with the settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to update Microsoft 365 apps to the latest version, and choose how frequently Office checks for updates. See the device registry keys that are updated when an Intune policy to Office update is applied.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-update-office</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Microsoft Edge policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create settings using the settings catalog to configure Microsoft Edge on Windows and macOS devices. Using Microsoft Intune, you can configure group policy settings, and deploy these settings to Microsoft Edge users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog-configure-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run remote actions on devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to run remote actions on Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Windows devices. You can reset the password, lock the device, wipe or reset the OS, scan for viruses, and more. Use this feature to remotely manage devices and have help desk run common tasks.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data storage and processing in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how personal data is stored and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-store-process</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remotely administer devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the required roles to use TeamViewer, how to install the TeamViewer connector, and step-by-step guidance to remotely administer devices using Microsoft Intune in the Azure portal</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/teamviewer-support</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune manages users and devices, simplifies app management and automated policy deployment, and integrates with mobile threat defense. It connects to Managed Google Play, Apple tokens and certificates, and Teamviewer for remote assistance. Can use MDM or MAM to protect data, configure devices, and simplify access to company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third-party device compliance partners support in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a third-party device compliance partner as a source of compliance data for devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-compliance-partners</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune contributes to a strong Zero Trust strategy and architecture.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/zero-trust-with-microsoft-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android with Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sync devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Synchronize devices that are registered or managed with Microsoft Intune to get the latest policies and actions. Includes the steps to sync by using the Azure portal, and lists the error codes that can be retried.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure ChromeOS connector for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to connect the Google Admin Console to Microsoft Intune so that you can view and take action on enrolled ChromeOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/chrome-enterprise-connector-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View and correct personal data collected by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to view and correct personal data that's been collected by Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-view-correct</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View device details with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View your device details, including operating systems, storage space, manufacturer, and model. Get a list of installed apps, check compliance policies, and set up TeamViewer with Microsoft Intune in Azure. Similar to viewing inventory of the devices you manage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-inventory</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage devices with endpoint security in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security node to view devices and manage them in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-manage-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find the primary user of a Microsoft Intune device.</title>
      <description>Find the primary user (or User Device Affinity) of an Intune device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/find-primary-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View ChromeOS device information</title>
      <description>View ChromeOS devices and details synced with the Chrome Enterprise connector in the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/chrome-enterprise-device-details</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rename a device with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Rename a device by using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rename</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 02:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO and deploy the configuration to your macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using Microsoft Entra ID with the Secure Enclave, smart card, or password authentication methods. You create a settings catalog policy to configure the settings. This article is a step-by-step guide to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platform SSO scenarios for macOS devices</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure common Platform SSO scenarios for macOS devices. You can enable Kerberos SSO to on-premises Active Directory and cloud-based Microsoft Entra ID, use Touch ID biometric policy with Secure Enclave authentication, and enable SSO on non-Microsoft apps. You can also configure end user experience settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-scenarios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiosk settings for Windows 10/11 in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your Windows 10/11 client devices as single-app and multi-app kiosks, customize the start menu, add apps, show the task bar, and configure a web browser in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kiosk-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>