<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 06:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 06:02:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Known Issues for Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure policies that define how Endpoint Privilege Management functions in your tenant, and behaviors when elevating files to run in administrative context.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-known-issues</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows enrollment attestation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out how the Device attestation status report can help you and learn to use the Attest device action to ensure your devices are secure and reliable.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-attestation</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for iOS/iPadOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt macOS devices with FileVault using Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to configure and manage FileVault disk encryption on macOS devices, including Setup Assistant enforcement and comprehensive recovery key management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View report details for encryption status of devices managed with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to view reports for device encryption status across macOS FileVault and Windows BitLocker encrypted devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encryption-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies with tenant attached Configuration Manager devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use tenant attach to add Configuration Manager devices to Microsoft Intune and then deploy Intune policies to those devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/tenant-attach-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 2. Create App Protection Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business across Windows, Android, and iOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-2-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint detection and response policy. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security endpoint detection and response policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-edr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage antivirus settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies and use reports for devices you manage with endpoint security antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-antivirus-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage firewall settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security firewall policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-firewall-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage account protection settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune endpoint security account protection policies to protect the identity and accounts of users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard and Configure Devices with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint via Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune, including connecting the products, onboarding devices, and assigning policies for compliance and risk level assessment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-integrate</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage attack surface reduction settings with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security attack surface reduction policy settings in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-asr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune endpoint security disk encryption policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy Microsoft Intune endpoint security policy disk encryption policies for BitLocker and FileVault.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-disk-encryption-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security policies and profiles to focus on security configuration of devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automated device enrollment (ADE) for macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll corporate-owned Macs into Microsoft Intune with Apple Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-program-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 4. Create App Configuration Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4. Create app configuration policies for Microsoft Edge for Business across Windows, Android, and iOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-4-acp-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-1-mamca</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense for App Protection Policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense signals with Microsoft Edge for Business app protection policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-3-scc</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 6. Deploy Microsoft Edge security baseline - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 6. Deploy the Microsoft Edge security baseline for rapid Windows security configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-6-security-baseline</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 7. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business End User Experience for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 7. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business end user experience Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-7-end-user-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 5. Create Settings Catalog policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 5. Create Settings Catalog policies for Microsoft Edge for Business on Windows and macOS.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-5-settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 8. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business Data Security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 8. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business corporate data security in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-8-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Corporate Data in Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure your corporate data in Microsoft Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business across all platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of enrollment restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the enrollment restrictions available in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-restrictions-set</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot auto-enrolling existing Configuration Manager devices in Intune - Intune</title>
      <description>Helps you understand and troubleshoot issues when you set up co-management by taking Path 1 - Auto-enroll existing Configuration Manager-managed devices into Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/comanage-configmgr/troubleshoot-co-management-auto-enrolling</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 02:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk enrollment for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a bulk enrollment package for Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-bulk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually Add the Windows 10 Company Portal App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how your workforce can manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app to their PC from the Microsoft Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Apps to Groups in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign an Intune app to groups of users or devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare Apps for Mobile Application Management With Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The information in this article helps you decide when you should use the App wrapping tool and the App SDK to enable your custom line-of-business apps to use the mobile app management policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/apps-prepare-mobile-application-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovered Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand details about the detected apps that Intune found on a device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-discovered-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Transfer Policy Exceptions for Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create exceptions to the Intune App Protection Policy (APP) data transfer policy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-exception</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 12:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS direct enrollment - Apple Configurator-Setup Assistant - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Apple Configurator to enroll corporate-owned iOS/iPadOS devices with Setup Assistant.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-configurator-enroll-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple device enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple device enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-device-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use direct enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy and enroll macOS devices in Microsoft Intune using direct enrollment with Apple Configurator.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-direct-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to Detect and Fix Support Issues - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt Windows devices with BitLocker using Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to manage BitLocker encryption on Windows devices, including silent encryption and Personal Data Encryption.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage devices with endpoint security in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security node to view devices and manage them in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-manage-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings you can manage with Intune Endpoint Protection profiles for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the available settings in Intune endpoint protection profiles for managed Windows devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-protection-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent to Manage Vulnerabilities</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify, prioritize, and remediate security vulnerabilities across your managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/vulnerability-remediation-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Apps and Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how apps and configurations can be removed temporarily, then restored automatically or manually using the Remove apps and configuration device action with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/remove-apps-config</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center copy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices copy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Platform SSO for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Platform SSO and deploy the configuration to your macOS devices. Platform SSO enables single sign-on (SSO) using Microsoft Entra ID with the Secure Enclave, smart card, or password authentication methods. You create a settings catalog policy to configure the settings. This article is a step-by-step guide to configure Platform SSO for macOS devices using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/platform-sso-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Update Policies for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure software update policies for Apple devices using Apple's Declarative Device Management (DDM) model. Improve security, reduce user disruption, and ensure compliance with reliable, automated updates across your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/updates/apple</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with the Device Offboarding Agent</title>
      <description>Learn about the Device Offboarding Agent in Microsoft Intune, its prerequisites, how it works, and how to configure it.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/device-offboarding-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to Assist Users Authenticated by your Organization - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Collect Diagnostics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan for Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the requirements and capabilities of Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to Assist Authenticated Users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-use</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eSIM configuration of a download server - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about configuration of an eSIM Download Server from Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/esim-device-configuration-download-server</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work From Anywhere Report in Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how the Work from Anywhere report in Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics provides insights into remote productivity, device readiness, and user experience.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/analytics/work-from-anywhere</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Remediation Agent Overview and Set Up</title>
      <description>Learn about the Vulnerability Remediation Agent in Microsoft Intune, its prerequisites, how it works, and how to set it up. The agent uses AI to identify and prioritize vulnerability remediation based on Microsoft Defender Vulnerability Management data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/vulnerability-remediation-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Review Agent Overview</title>
      <description>Learn about the Change Review Agent in Microsoft Intune, its prerequisites, and how it works.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/change-review-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable eSIM data connections in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or use eSIM to get internet and data access using different data plans. In Intune, add or import activation codes, and then assign these activation codes using a configuration profile. You can also monitor the eSIM profiles and check the status of the eSIM-enabled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/esim-device-configuration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Actions – Wipe, Lock, Locate, and More - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how to use Microsoft Intune to remotely manage, wipe, lock, restart, and secure Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, Windows, and ChromeOS devices. Learn about available remote actions, prerequisites, and bulk actions for IT admins.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Policy Configuration Agent and set it up</title>
      <description>Learn about the Policy Configuration Agent in Microsoft Intune, its prerequisites, how it works, and how to set it up. The agent is a generative AI feature that helps create Intune policies based on uploaded documents or benchmarks. The Policy Configuration Agent is a feature of Security Copilot in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/policy-configuration-agent</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Follow the steps to deploy Remote Help with Microsoft Intune on Windows, macOS, and Android Enterprise.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot and monitor Remote Help for Microsoft Intune. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the troubleshooting and monitoring information for Remote Help with Microsoft Intune to ensure healthy and successful deployment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-troubleshoot-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows Backup for Organizations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows backup and restore in Intune for employees or students.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-backup-restore</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable autodiscovery of Intune enrollment server - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Simplify enrollment for users by enabling automatic discovery of the Intune enrollment server.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-create-cname</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View enrollment reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor and troubleshoot issues with enrollment restrictions and enrollment status page assignments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/view-enrollment-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot Agents in Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how Microsoft Security Copilot enhances Microsoft Intune through AI-powered security agents. Learn about available agents and explore their capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Change Review Agent</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Change Review Agent in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/change-review-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assignment filter properties and operators reference - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference guide for device and app properties, operators, and rule syntax when creating assignment filters in Microsoft Intune. Includes examples and supported values.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-device-properties</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device platform restrictions - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Restrict personally owned devices, and specific device platforms and OS versions from enrolling in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/create-device-platform-restrictions</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration Policies for Intune App SDK Managed Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure policies for Intune App SDK managed apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-managed-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assignment Filter Performance Tips for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Optimize Microsoft Intune performance with assignment filters. Learn to use virtual groups, reuse groups, and apply filters effectively. Improve policy deployment speed with incremental group changes, and use assignment filters to include and exclude.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-performance-recommendations</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse Collections - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune Data Warehouse collections provide details related to the Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/intune-data-warehouse-collections</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platforms and policy types supported by assignment filters - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn which apps, compliance policies, and device configuration profiles and their platforms support assignment filters in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-supported-workloads</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assignment filter reports &amp; troubleshooting - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use assignment filter reports to troubleshoot policies in Microsoft Intune. View filter evaluation results, resolve conflicts, and understand include vs. exclude modes.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-reports-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create assignment filters in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create assignment filters in Microsoft Intune to target policies based on device properties like OS version or manufacturer. Learn to create, update, and delete filters for managed devices and apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devices - Intune Data Warehouse - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference article for the Devices category of entity collections in the Intune Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/reports-ref-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Wipe - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wipe, or factory reset, devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Device Offboarding Agent</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Device Offboarding Agent in Microsoft Intune to identify and offboard devices that are no longer in use.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/device-offboarding-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Admin Tasks - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the centralized Admin tasks view in Microsoft Intune to manage tasks across capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/admin-tasks</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Multi Admin Approval in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Multi Admin Approval to protect your tenant against the use of compromised administrative accounts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/multi-admin-approval</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune contributes to a strong Zero Trust strategy and architecture.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/zero-trust-with-microsoft-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune to remediate vulnerabilities found by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune Security Tasks to manage threats and vulnerabilities identified by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/atp-manage-vulnerabilities</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the Policy Configuration Agent to create policies</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Policy Configuration Agent in Microsoft Intune to create policies. You can create policies on files you uploaded, natural language prompts, or industry baselines. The Policy Configuration Agent is a feature of Security Copilot in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/policy-configuration-agent-use</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Copilot in Intune features overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Security Copilot in Intune is an AI platform. It can help you create policies, get information about existing policies, and show more details on specific settings, including their impacts on users and devices. You can also use Copilot to troubleshoot device issues and query devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/copilot/copilot-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Security Copilot agents in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/agents/security-copilot-agents-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use EPM support approvals for file elevation requests with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage support approvals for elevation requests when you use Endpoint Privilege Management for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-support-approved</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iVerify Enterprise Mobile Threat Defense with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up iVerify Enterprise Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/iverify-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) with your Mobile Threat Defense partner to protect access to company resources based on device risk.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mobile-threat-defense</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Protection Policies Overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Microsoft Intune app protection policies help protect your company data and prevent data loss.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported Microsoft Intune Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides lists of support partner and Microsoft apps that are commonly used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-supported-intune-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune Management Extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Web Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding web apps (client-server applications) to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/web-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of Intune App SDK - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune App SDK is available for both the iOS and Android platforms, and enables mobile app management features with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>