<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:33:46 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:33:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Configure feature updates policy for Windows 10 Windows 11 devices in Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows feature updates. Configure and deploy policy to maintain the Windows feature version of Windows 10/11 devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-10-feature-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows Backup for Organizations in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows backup and restore in Intune for employees or students.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-backup-restore</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View declarative device management-based software update reports for Apple devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to software updates reports for managed Apple devices based on Apples declarative device management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-reports-apple-declarative-based</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ADMX templates on Windows 10/11 devices in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Administrative templates in Microsoft Intune to create groups of settings for Windows 10/11 client devices. Use these settings in a device configuration profile. You can control Office programs, Microsoft Edge, access OneDrive, use remote desktop, enable Auto-Play, set power management settings, use HTTP printing, control user sign-in, and change the event log size.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Microsoft Edge policy using ADMX template in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create settings using ADMX administrative templates to configure Microsoft Edge on Windows devices. Using Microsoft Intune, you can configure group policy settings, and deploy these settings to Microsoft Edge users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/administrative-templates-configure-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walkthrough-Create a settings catalog policy</title>
      <description>This tutorial or walkthrough steps through creating and comparing an on-premises Administrative Templates (ADMX) Group Policy and Microsoft Intune cloud-based settings catalog policy. It shows similar settings in on-premises and the Intune settings catalog to create and manage policies for Office, Windows, and Microsoft Edge on Windows 10/11 client devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/tutorial-settings-catalog-group-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune enrollment for Android Enterprise dedicated devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure enrollment in Microsoft Intune for Android Enterprise dedicated devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-kiosk-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll personal devices in Intune with Android Enterprise work profile management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Intune for personal devices and bring-your-own-device scenarios using Android Enterprise work profile management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-work-profile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Android Enterprise work profile for corporate owned devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up Android Enterprise work profile for corporate-owned devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-corporate-owned-work-profile-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment for Android Enterprise fully managed devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up enrollment in Intune for devices using the Android Enterprise fully managed device management solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to assist users authenticated by your organization.</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance recommendations when using filters</title>
      <description>When using filters in Microsoft Intune, use Intune virtual groups that don't require Microsoft Entra ID syncing. To improve performance, reuse groups, make incremental group changes, and use filters to include and exclude.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters-performance-recommendations</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags for distributed IT - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use role-based access control (RBAC) and scope tags to filter configuration profiles to specific roles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/scope-tags</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared iOS and iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Shared iOS and iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-shared-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment time grouping - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview and setup of the enrollment time grouping feature in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/enrollment-time-grouping</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add users to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add and managing Microsoft Entra user accounts from within Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/users-add</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set the mobile device management authority - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to set the mobile device management authority in Microsoft Intune and some key considerations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/mdm-authority-set</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1 for deploying or setting up Intune. The starting point is to review supported configurations, sign up for the trial, configure the custom domain name, add users and groups to Intune, assign licenses to users, manage roles, grant admin permissions, and set the MDM authority.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add groups to organize users and devices for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Microsoft Entra groups to organize users and devices for use with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/groups-add</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell scripts for Remediations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>PowerShell script reference for Remediations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/powershell-scripts-remediation</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop single-session with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Windows 10 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the general guidelines for using Windows 10 virtual machines with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/windows-10-virtual-machines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlicensed admins in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to give unlicensed admins permissions to access Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/unlicensed-admins</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a user in Intune</title>
      <description>Create a user in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure a custom domain name - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a custom domain name for your Microsoft Intune subscription</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/custom-domain-name-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remediations to detect and fix support issues</title>
      <description>Learn more about Remediations in Microsoft Intune, including what Remediations are and view any prerequisites and licensing requirements. Also, learn how to deploy built-in and custom remediation scripts, and learn how to monitor your scripts.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remediations</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Delivery Optimization settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure device configuration policy to manage Delivery Optimization settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/delivery-optimization-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Microsoft Intune licenses</title>
      <description>Assign licenses to users so they can enroll in Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/licenses-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operating systems and browsers supported by Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Lists supported device platforms and browsers for Intune device management</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/supported-devices-browsers</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Open Source Project Supported Devices</title>
      <description>Lists Android open source project devices (AOSP) supported devices</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/android-os-project-supported-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidelines for using Azure Virtual Desktop multi-session with Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/azure-virtual-desktop-multi-session</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the Microsoft Intune MDM lifecycle</title>
      <description>Learn how Intune helps you manage devices through their lifecycle - from enrollment, through configuration, to eventual retirement.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/device-lifecycle</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune classic groups in the Azure portal - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn what's new with groups in the Microsoft Intune Azure portal.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/groups-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Licenses available for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune is available with these licenses</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/licenses</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the Microsoft Intune tenant status page - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune tenant status page displays details about your tenant and the status of connectors you've configured, and messages intended for tenants and about the Intune service health.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/tenant-status</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up or sign in to Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to sign up for a Microsoft Intune subscription or sign in to start with your subscription.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/account-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Cloud PKI for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>An overview of the Microsoft Cloud PKI service, available with Microsoft Intune Suite or as an Intune add-on.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to install and configure the unified Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune, which supports SCEP, PKCS, imported PKCS, and certificate revocation.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-install</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune - Azure</title>
      <description>Learn about the unified Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune, which supports SCEP, PKCS, imported PKCS, and certificate revocation.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Types of certificate that are supported by Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Microsoft Intune's support for Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP), Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create trusted certificate profiles in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and deploy trusted certificate profiles to deploy a trusted root certificate to managed devices in Intune. Trusted certificate profiles support use of Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) and Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-trusted-root</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites for the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the software and network prerequisites for use of the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Cloud PKI root and issuing CA for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure a root and issuing CA for the Microsoft Cloud PKI service.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-configure-ca</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment models for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the deployment options for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-deployment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring your own certificate authority with Cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a Microsoft Cloud PKI BYOCA issuing CA in Intune and anchor it to an on-premises or private CA.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-configure-byoca</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune cloud PKI fundamentals - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes fundamentals for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-fundamentals</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Issue DigiCert PKCS certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Install and configure the Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune to issue PKCS certificates from DigiCert PKI Platform to Intune-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-digicert-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor issued PKI certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor reports for certificates issued via Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delete issued PKI certificates with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Delete certificates issued via Microsoft Intune cloud PKI.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View ChromeOS device information</title>
      <description>View ChromeOS devices and details synced with the Chrome Enterprise connector in the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/chrome-enterprise-device-details</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote actions for ChromeOS devices</title>
      <description>Remotely run Microsoft Intune device actions on ChromeOS devices in the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/chrome-enterprise-remote-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use imported PFX certificates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use imported Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificates with Microsoft Intune. Import certificates, configure certificate templates, and create an Imported PKCS Certificate profile.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-imported-pfx-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit logs for Microsoft Intune cloud PKI - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get audit logs for Microsoft cloud public key infrastructure (PKI) activity in the admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-cloud-pki-audit-logs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use a PKCS certificate profile to provision devices with certificates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Public Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS) certificates with Microsoft Intune, work with root certificates and certificate templates, and use device configuration profiles for a PKCS Certificate.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-pfx-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign and encrypt email using S/MIME - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use email digital certificates in Microsoft Intune to sign and encrypt emails on devices. These certificates are called S/MIME and are configured using device configuration profiles. Signing and encryption certificates use PKCS, or private certificates, and use a connector to import certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-s-mime-encryption-sign</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure infrastructure to support SCEP certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To use Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) with Microsoft Intune, configure your on-premises AD domain, create a certification authority, and set up the NDES server to support use of the Certificate Connector.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-scep-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use third-party certification authorities (CA) with SCEP in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In Microsoft Intune, you can add a vendor or third-party certificate authority (CA) to issue certificates to mobile devices using the SCEP protocol. In this overview, a Microsoft Entra application gives Microsoft Intune permissions to validate certificates. Then, use the application ID, authentication key, and tenant ID of the Microsoft Entra application in the setup of your SCEP server to issue certificates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-authority-add-scep-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-supervised-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use SCEP certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and assign Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) certificate profiles with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificates-profile-scep</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Windows devices using Automatic enrollment, Windows Autopilot, group policy, and co-management enrollment options in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retire or wipe devices using Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Retire or wipe a device on an Android, Android work profile, AOSP, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, or Windows device using Microsoft Intune. Also delete a device from Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/devices-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Properties catalog in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure Properties catalog policy to manage Device Inventory settings on Windows devices you manage with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect diagnostics from an Intune managed device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics from an Intune managed device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find lost devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Locate lost or stolen devices by using the locate device feature in Microsoft Intune. Get details on security and privacy information when using the locate device action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-locate</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Windows Driver updates policy for Windows 10 Windows 11 devices in Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using Microsoft Intune policy to manage Windows driver updates on your Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-driver-updates-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disable Activation Lock on Apple devices with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune to disable Activation Lock on Apple devices to access locked devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-activation-lock-disable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the settings catalog to configure DDM software updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to configure Apple's declarative device management (DDM) settings to install a specific update by an enforced deadline. This feature uses the settings catalog to configure managed software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS and managed macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/managed-software-updates-ios-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create device compliance policies for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/create-compliance-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run remote actions on devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to run remote actions on Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Windows devices. You can reset the password, lock the device, wipe or reset the OS, scan for viruses, and more. Use this feature to remotely manage devices and have help desk run common tasks.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View device details with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View your device details, including operating systems, storage space, manufacturer, and model. Get a list of installed apps, check compliance policies, and set up TeamViewer with Microsoft Intune in Azure. Similar to viewing inventory of the devices you manage.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-inventory</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reset device passcodes with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Remove or reset the passcode by using the remove passcode action on devices you manage or monitor with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-passcode-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>ServiceNow integration enables help desk staff, who are licensed to use Remote Help, to use ServiceNow to view incidents and details of the tech issue that an employee is facing from the Troubleshooting pane. This article also describes how to configure ServiceNow integration with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/service-now-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sync devices with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Synchronize devices that are registered or managed with Microsoft Intune to get the latest policies and actions. Includes the steps to sync by using the Azure portal, and lists the error codes that can be retried.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add app configuration policies for managed Android Enterprise devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use app configuration policies in Microsoft Intune to supply settings when users run a Managed Google Play app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-configuration-policies-use-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send custom notifications to users with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom push notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Delivery Optimization settings for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Delivery Optimization settings for Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices that you can deploy using Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/delivery-optimization-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Windows Driver updates policy for Windows 10 Windows 11 devices in Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage policies that install Windows driver updates on your Intune managed Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-driver-updates-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a JSON file for custom compliance settings in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create the JSON file that defines custom settings and values for use with device compliance policies in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/compliance-custom-json</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help on Android to assist users authenticated by your organization.</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app in Android, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activate iOS/iPadOS lost mode with Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Turn on or start lost mode to customize a message that appears on the lock screen of a lost or stolen iOS/iPadOS device by using Microsoft Intune. And, get details on security and privacy information when you're using the lost mode action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-lost-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign a role to an Intune administrator</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign a built-in or custom role to a user in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/assign-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android FOTA Updates</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates on Android devices. A FOTA update can include software and security patches, feature updates, and other changes to the device's firmware.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/fota-updates-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use multiple administrative approvals in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure multi-admin approval to protect your tenant against the use of compromised administrative accounts in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/multi-admin-approval</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Linux devices in Intune using the Intune app. Set an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-linux</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for Android software updates in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for Android devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on corporate owned Android Enterprise devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for software updates on BYOD in Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for BYOD and personally owned devices using Microsoft Intune. See tasks and settings that can manage updates on personal devices on Android and iOS/iPadOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/software-updates-guide-personal-byod</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use bulk device actions in Microsoft Intune device.</title>
      <description>Use bulk remote device actions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/bulk-device-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy and personal data in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn what personal data is collected and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-personal-data</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune operated by 21Vianet in China</title>
      <description>Intune operated by 21Vianet in China.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/china</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit, export or delete personal data collected by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to audit, export, or delete personal data that is collected by Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-audit-export-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>