<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:34:40 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:34:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Assign Apps to Groups in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign an Intune app to groups of users or devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authentication methods for Apple automated device enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Describes the Intune-supported authentication methods you can use with automated device enrollment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/automated-device-enrollment-authentication</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune - Azure - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the unified Certificate Connector for Microsoft Intune, which supports SCEP, PKCS, imported PKCS, and certificate revocation.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/certificate-connector-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Remote Help to Assist Users Authenticated by your Organization - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>With the Remote Help app, provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint security in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage endpoint security in Microsoft Intune. Configure security policies, deploy baselines, and integrate with Defender for Endpoint to protect devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use direct enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy and enroll macOS devices in Microsoft Intune using direct enrollment with Apple Configurator.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-direct-enroll-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS device enrollment guide for  Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll iOS and iPadOS devices using user and device enrollment, automated device enrollment (DEP), and Apple Configurator in Microsoft Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune Suite add-on capabilities - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune Suite unifies a series of mission-critical advanced endpoint management and security capabilities. The capabilities of the suite are integrated with Microsoft 365 and Microsoft Security across endpoint platforms for both cloud and on-premises co-managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-add-ons</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration guide to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deployment guide to set up, onboard, or move to Intune. These steps include moving from partner MDM providers, using co-management, moving from on-premises group policy, and moving from Office 365 device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-intune-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure macOS Enterprise SSO app extension with MDMs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Microsoft Enterprise single sign-on (SSO) app extension plug-in. Add or create an macOS device profile using the SSO app extension in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-macos-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See an overview of the steps to start using Intune. Plan your move and deployment of Intune, determine your licensing needs and any platform requirements, use compliance and Conditional Access, deploy apps, create device configuration profiles, and enroll your devices to be managed. Get more information on mobile application management for BYOD or personal devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/get-started-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add preference file settings to macOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add an xml or plist file that includes key information about your app. Use a preference file device configuration profile to change key information in the property list file, and assign it to your macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/preference-file-settings-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune manages users and devices, simplifies app management and automated policy deployment, and integrates with mobile threat defense. It connects to Managed Google Play, Apple tokens and certificates, and Teamviewer for remote assistance. Can use MDM or MAM to protect data, configure devices, and simplify access to company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/what-is-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data collection in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about personal data collected in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-collect</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign Win32 Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add, assign, and manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-add</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect data and devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune capabilities that can help you protect your devices and data against unauthorized access and other threats.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-protect</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Intune to remediate vulnerabilities found by Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender Vulnerability Management with Intune to create security tasks, track remediation, and reduce vulnerability exposure across managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/atp-manage-vulnerabilities</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Install and configure Microsoft Tunnel Gateway on a Linux server to support Intune managed cloud-based devices in connecting to your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage devices, apps, and security with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud PKI CA Expiration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to renew a certificate authority (CA) in Microsoft Cloud PKI to maintain continuous certificate issuance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/cloud-pki/renew-ca</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Compatibility Reports for Windows Updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use compatibility reports for Windows devices in Intune to identify app and driver risks before deploying feature updates or update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/compatibility-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot and monitor Remote Help for Microsoft Intune. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the troubleshooting and monitoring information for Remote Help with Microsoft Intune to ensure healthy and successful deployment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-troubleshoot-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Reset Protection Emails Not Enforced in Intune for Android - Intune</title>
      <description>Describes an issue in which an Android Enterprise device can be activated by using a Google account that isn't included in the "Factory reset protection emails" setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-configuration/factory-reset-protection-emails-not-enforced</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared iPad devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Shared iPad devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-shared-ipad</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single sign-on (SSO) for iOS/iPadOS and macOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of Microsoft Enterprise SSO plug-in in Microsoft Intune, Jamf Pro, and other MDM solution providers. The Enterprise SSO plug-in is available on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/use-enterprise-sso-plug-in-ios-ipados-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device features and settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Overview of the different Microsoft Intune device profiles. Get info on GPO, features, restrictions, email, wifi, VPN, education, certificates, upgrade Windows 10/11, BitLocker and Microsoft Defender, and custom device configuration settings in the Microsoft Intune admin center. Use these profiles to manage and protect data and devices in your company.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profiles</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared iOS and iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Shared iOS and iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-enrollment-shared-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiosk settings for Windows and Holographic devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure your Windows 10/11 and Windows Holographic for Business devices as single-app and multi-app kiosks, customize the start menu, add apps, show the task bar, and configure a web browser in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/kiosk-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create iOS/iPadOS or macOS device profile with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create an iOS, iPadOS, or macOS device profile. Configure settings for AirPrint, layout of the home screen, app notifications, shared device, single sign-on, and web content filter settings in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-features-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple device feature settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See all the settings to configure iOS, iPadOS, and macOS devices for AirPrint, home screen layout, app notifications, shared devices, single sign-on, and web content filter settings in Microsoft Intune. Use these settings in a device configuration profile to configure iOS, iPadOS, and macOS devices to use these Apple features on your devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-features-apple</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security, email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4 to deploy device configuration profiles as part of the minimum set of policies for your devices using Microsoft Intune. The starting point is to enable the firewall, install AV, scan for malware, install software updates, create a strong PIN policy, and create email, VPN, and Wi-Fi device configuration profiles.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-configuration-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure WiFi settings for Apple devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a Wi-Fi configuration profile on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices using Wi-Fi configuration settings in Microsoft Intune. Configure the connection details, authentication methods, SSIDs, security types, and proxy settings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-settings-apple</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure VPN settings for Apple devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a VPN configuration profile on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices using virtual private network (VPN) configuration settings in Microsoft Intune. Configure the connection details, authentication methods, split tunneling, custom VPN settings with the identifier, key and value pairs, per-app VPN settings that include Safari URLs, and on-demand VPNs with SSIDs or DNS search domains, proxy settings to include a configuration script, IP or FQDN address, and TCP port.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-apple</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create assignment filters in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create assignment filters in Microsoft Intune to target policies based on device properties like OS version or manufacturer. Learn to create, update, and delete filters for managed devices and apps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/filters</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up local admin account creation and password management for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up macOS account configuration with LAPS through automatic device enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-laps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up account driven Apple User Enrollment - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up account driven Apple User Enrollment for personal devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-account-driven-user-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up enrollment for macOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up enrollment for macOS devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/macos-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune to manage software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn the recommended processes to manage macOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment guide to manage iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A guide to managing iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-platform-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Wi-Fi profile for devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the steps to create a Wi-Fi device configuration profile in Microsoft Intune. Create profiles for Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, Android kiosk, iOS, iPadOS, macOS, Windows 10/11, and Windows Holographic for Business. Use these profiles to create a WiFi connection to use certificates, choose an EAP type, select an authentication method, enable a proxy, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Web Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding web apps (client-server applications) to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/web-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict devices features using policy in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add a device configuration profile to restrict features on Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, AOSP, macOS, iOS, iPadOS, and Windows 10/11 client devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple device restriction settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, or create settings on iOS, iPadOS, and macOS devices to restrict features in Microsoft Intune. Create password requirements, control the locked screen, use built-in apps, add restricted or approved apps, handle bluetooth devices, connect to the cloud for backup and storage, enable kiosk mode, add domains, and control how users interact with the Safari web browser.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-restrictions-apple</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple device enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple device enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-device-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add VPN settings to devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>On Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, macOS, and Windows devices, use built-in settings to create virtual private network (VPN) connections in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up per-app VPN for iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See the prerequisites, create a group for the virtual private network (VPN) users, add a SCEP certificate profile, configure a per-app VPN profile, and assign some apps to the VPN profile in Microsoft Intune on iOS/iPadOS devices. Also lists the steps to verify the VPN connection on the device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-setting-configure-per-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up user enrollment with Company Portal for iOS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up the profile based Apple User Enrollment option for personal devices enrolling in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/apple-user-enrollment-with-company-portal</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use custom device settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add or create a profile to use custom settings for Windows 10/11 client, Android device administrator, Android Enterprise, macOS, and iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS bundle IDs for built-in apps in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the bundle IDs for the built-in iOS and iPadOS apps. Use these bundle IDs to explicitly allow apps in device configuration profiles and policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/bundle-ids-built-in-ios-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Wi-Fi settings for Android devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create or add a WiFi device configuration profile for Android Enterprise, Android Kiosk, and AOSP devices. See the different settings, add certificates, choose an EAP type, and select an authentication method in Microsoft Intune. For kiosk devices, also enter the Pre-shared key of your network.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/wi-fi-settings-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use derived credentials for mobile devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use a third-party partners derived credential as an authentication method for Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/derived-credentials</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Email settings for iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the email settings you can configure and add to iOS and iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune, including using Exchange servers, and getting attributes from Microsoft Entra ID. You can also enable SSL, authenticate users with certificates or username/password, and synchronize email on iOS/iPadOS devices using device configuration profiles in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/email-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use VPN settings for Android Enterprise in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See all the settings to create VPN connections on Android Enterprise devices in Microsoft Intune, including COBO, COSU, COPE, and BYOD. Enter the connection name, IP address, or FQDN of the VPN server. Choose how users authenticate and choose Citrix, SonicWall, Check Point Capsule, and Pulse Secure connection types.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-android-enterprise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS supervised device security configurations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review example supervised device security configurations of basic, enhanced, and high security for iOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/ios-ipados-supervised-device-security-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add custom settings to Apple devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Export iOS, iPadOS, and macOS settings from Apple Configurator or Apple Profile Manager tools, and then import these settings into Microsoft Intune. These settings can create, use, and control custom settings and features on iOS, iPadOS, and macOS devices. This custom profile can then be assigned or distributed to iOS, iPadOS, and macOS devices in your organization to create a baseline or standard.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/custom-settings-apple</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS personal device security configurations - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review example personal device security configurations of basic, enhanced, and high security for iOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/ios-ipados-personal-device-security-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with iOS/iPadOS frontline worker devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage frontline worker devices using iOS and iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune. Select the best enrollment option, configure the home screen, and more.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/frontline-worker/frontline-worker-overview-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use VPN settings for Android DA devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See all the settings to create VPN connections on Android device administrator devices in Microsoft Intune. Enter the connection name, IP address, or FQDN of the VPN server. Choose how users authenticate, and choose Citrix, SonicWall, Check Point Capsule, and Pulse Secure connection types.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows VPN settings in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn and read about all the available VPN settings in Microsoft Intune, what they're used for, and what they do. See the traffic rules, Conditional Access, and DNS and proxy settings for Windows 10/11 and Windows Holographic for Business devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/vpn-settings-windows-10</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings insight - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Settings insight provides peer benchmarking information during security baseline configuration, showing when organizations similar to yours use Microsoft's recommended default values.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/settings-insight</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to turn on iOS/iPadOS supervised mode with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/device-supervised-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Apple User Enrollment in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Utilize Apple User Enrollment to enroll and manage user-owned iOS/iPadOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/ios-user-enrollment-supported-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign device profiles in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to assign device configuration profiles and policies to users and devices. Learn how to exclude groups from a profile assignment in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/device-profile-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Update Policies for Apple Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to configure software update policies for Apple devices using Apple's Declarative Device Management (DDM) model. Improve security, reduce user disruption, and ensure compliance with reliable, automated updates across your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get support in the Microsoft Intune admin center - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Get online and telephone support for Microsoft Intune and other device management cloud services from within the Microsoft Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/get-support</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint management services and solutions at Microsoft - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a family of on-premises products and cloud services. It includes Intune, Configuration Manager, co-management, Endpoint Analytics, Windows Autopilot, and the admin center to manage cloud devices and on on-premises.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-manager-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add, Configure, and Protect Apps with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add, configure, and protect apps with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-protect-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Windows Feature Update Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Windows feature update polies and how to manage them in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/feature-update-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help Desk Troubleshooting Dashboard - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Help desk staff use the troubleshooting pane to solve users' technical problems.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/help-desk-operators</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect device hardware info with the properties catalog - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the properties catalog in Microsoft Intune view and collect enhanced device hardware info on Windows devices you manage with Intune. You can collect info like BIOS version, TPM status, disk info, memory details, and network adapter configurations. Use this information to get deeper visibility into your device inventory and troubleshoot issues.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/properties-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare a Win32 App to Be Uploaded to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to prepare a Win32 app to be uploaded to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-prepare</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win32 App Management in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune. This article provides an overview of the Intune Win32 app delivery and management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway server software - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand how Microsoft Tunnel Gateway upgrades to new versions of the tunnel software for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-upgrade</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune built-in roles reference - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Permissions reference for built-in roles for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control-reference</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a custom role in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a custom role in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assign a role to an Intune administrator - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to assign a built-in or custom role to a user in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/assign-role</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable use of Windows diagnostic data by Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows diagnostic data in processor configuration for your tenant to enable its use by Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/data-enable-windows-data</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Windows Update Ring Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Windows Update ring policies for Windows devices, how to create and manage them, and improve update deployment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/update-rings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Windows Feature Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune policies to manage Windows feature updates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/feature-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update Rings Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Reference article that lists all the settings for Windows Update rings.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/update-ring-policy-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Windows quality updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Windows quality updates in Microsoft Intune using quality update policies, expedited updates, and hotpatch to keep devices secure and compliant.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/quality-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Intune policies to manage macOS software updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage system updates for supervised macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Update Management Overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Windows updates with Intune. Control update settings, define rollout strategies, and ensure consistent device security across your organization.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Government Service overview - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about the Intune government service offerings and features. This article is designed to serve as an overview of the Microsoft Intune offering for government community cloud (GCC) High and United States Department of Defense (DoD) environments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-govt-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports for Windows Feature Update Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the reports available for Windows feature update policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/feature-updates-reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android FOTA Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune to manage firmware updates on Android devices. A FOTA update can include software and security patches, feature updates, and other changes to the device's firmware.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/android/fota-updates</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expedite Policies for Windows Quality Updates - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use expedite policies in Microsoft Intune to quickly deploy a specific Windows security update, bypass deferrals, and monitor installation status across devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/expedite-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Rollout Options for Feature Update Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure rollout options in feature update policies to control when Windows feature updates become available to devices and deploy updates gradually.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/rollout-options</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin checklist for iOS/iPadOS software updates in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Guidance and advice for administrators that create and manage software updated for iOS/iPadOS devices using Microsoft Intune. See sample policy for different industry scenarios, including shared devices, kiosk, manufacturing, and information worker.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/apple/software-updates-guide-ios-ipados</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>