<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:04:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment for Windows devices joining or registering with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up automatic enrollment in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Intune automatic enrollment of Windows devices that join or register with your Microsoft Entra ID.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/quickstart-setup-auto-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enroll Android, Android Enterprise, iOS, iPadOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows devices in Intune. Decide which enrollment method to use, and get an overview of the administrator and end user tasks to enroll devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign up or sign in to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to sign up for a Microsoft Intune subscription or sign in to start with your subscription.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/account-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign Up for Microsoft Intune Free Trial Setup Guide - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Sign up for a Microsoft Intune free trial and configure your tenant. Learn the setup process, prerequisites, and how to configure domain names. Start evaluating Intune today.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/free-trial-sign-up</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1 for deploying or setting up Intune. The starting point is to review supported configurations, sign up for the trial, configure the custom domain name, add users and groups to Intune, assign licenses to users, manage roles, grant admin permissions, and set the MDM authority.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-plan-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Monitor App Protection Policies - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes how to monitor app protection policies in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policies-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Service Description - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune is a cloud-based service that helps you manage Windows, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/microsoft-intune-service-description</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial - Configure Slack to Use Intune for EMM and App Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this tutorial you will configure Slack to use Intune for EMM and app configuration.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/tutorial-configure-slack-enterprise-grid</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense for App Protection Policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 3. Integrate Mobile Threat Defense signals with Microsoft Edge for Business app protection policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-3-scc</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 4. Create App Configuration Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 4. Create app configuration policies for Microsoft Edge for Business across Windows, Android, and iOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-4-acp-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 1. Create Microsoft Entra Conditional Access with Microsoft Edge for Business.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-1-mamca</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 2. Create App Protection Policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 2. Create app protection policies for Microsoft Edge for Business across Windows, Android, and iOS platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-2-app</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 5. Create Settings Catalog policies for Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 5. Create Settings Catalog policies for Microsoft Edge for Business on Windows and macOS.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-5-settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 7. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business Data Security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 7. Troubleshoot Microsoft Edge for Business corporate data security in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-7-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Corporate Data in Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Secure your corporate data in Microsoft Intune with Microsoft Edge for Business across all platforms.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step 6. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business End User Experience for Windows - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Step 6. Understand Microsoft Edge for Business end user experience Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/mamedge-6-end-user-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration guide to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deployment guide to set up, onboard, or move to Intune. These steps include moving from partner MDM providers, using co-management, moving from on-premises group policy, and moving from Office 365 device management.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/deployment-guide-intune-setup</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune-Migration Guide - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Follow this migration guide to move your mobile device management from Microsoft 365 Basic Mobility and Security to Intune. Includes policy mapping and license assignment steps.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/migrate-to-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Access requirements policy mapping from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A detailed list of the policy map between Basic Mobility and Security access requirements and Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-map-access-requirements</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configurations policy mapping from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A detailed list of the policy map between Basic Mobility and Security configurations and Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-map-configurations</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous policy mapping from Basic Mobility and Security to Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>A detailed miscellaneous policy map between Basic Mobility and Security access requirements and Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/policy-map-miscellaneous</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Route logs to Azure Monitor using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Diagnostics Settings to send audit logs and operational logs in Microsoft Intune to Azure Storage account, Event Hubs, or Log Analytics. Choose how long you want to keep the data, and see some estimated costs for different size tenants.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/review-logs-using-azure-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with macOS endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Microsoft Intune guide to set up and configure macOS devices from setup to creating policies and enrolling devices. You secure your corporate and organization-owned endpoints that are enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Apple Business Manager or Apple School Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/end-to-end-guides/macos-endpoints-get-started</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Send Custom Notifications - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send Email Notifications to Noncompliant Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create notification templates and send email alerts to users with noncompliant devices in Microsoft Intune. Configure actions for noncompliance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/quickstart-send-notification</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll a Windows device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll a Windows device into Microsoft Intune. Follow this step-by-step evaluation guide to test device enrollment and verify it in the Intune admin center.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/quickstart-enroll-windows-device</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign an App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add and assign apps to user groups in Microsoft Intune. Ensure your workforce has access to the apps they need.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-add-assign-app</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a user in Intune and assign a license - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a user in Microsoft Intune and assign an Intune license to this user.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try Microsoft Intune for free - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Evaluate Microsoft Intune with a free trial. Step through common settings, enroll devices, create policies, and learn about cloud-based device management. Start your trial today.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/try-intune-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and Assign an App Protection Policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create and assign an app protection policy in Microsoft Intune to protect your organization's data. Get step-by-step guidance.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-create-assign-app-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Password Compliance Policy for Android Enterprise - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create a password compliance policy in Microsoft Intune for Android Enterprise devices. Learn to require specific password lengths to meet your organization's security requirements.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/quickstart-set-password-length-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create an Email Device Profile for iOS/iPadOS Devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create an email device profile in Microsoft Intune for iOS/iPadOS devices. Configure email settings to help users securely access organization email.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/quickstart-email-profile</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create and assign a custom role in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create and assign a custom Intune RBAC role with specific permissions for security operations. Follow this guide to implement least privilege access.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-custom-role</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Group to Manage Users - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to create a group in Microsoft Intune and add users to the groups. Use groups to manage user access to company resources and assign policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/quickstart-create-group</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center copy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up a greeting page for users signing in and enrolling Windows devices copy.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Wipe - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wipe, or factory reset, devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 13:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win32 App Management in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune. This article provides an overview of the Intune Win32 app delivery and management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and Assign Win32 Apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add, assign, and manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-add</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Intune for Device Compliance - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) solution to enforce device compliance and prevent security breaches.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-with-intune</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites the Microsoft Tunnel VPN for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the prerequisites for installation and use of the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway. These include Linux servers, network, and firewall configurations.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-prerequisites</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard and Configure Devices with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint via Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune, including connecting the products, onboarding devices, and assigning policies for compliance and risk level assessment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-defender-integrate</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Apple Volume-Purchased Apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to sync apps you bought in volume through Apple Business Manager with Microsoft Intune. Then manage and track these apps on iOS/iPadOS and macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/vpp-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an iOS/iPadOS Line-of-Business App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about how to add an iOS/iPadOS line-of-business (LOB) app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/lob-apps-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add an Enterprise App Catalog App to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add an Enterprise App Catalog app to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-enterprise-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrally manage Admin Tasks - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the centralized Admin tasks view in Microsoft Intune to manage common administrative tasks from across Intune capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/admin-tasks</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Endpoint Analytics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Troubleshoot Microsoft Intune endpoint analytics, including device enrollment issues, startup performance, and data collection problems.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/endpoint-analytics/troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up SentinelOne MTD with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the SentinelOne Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/sentinelone-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use CrowdStrike Falcon for Mobile with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up CrowdStrike Falcon Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/crowdstrike-falcon-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up CrowdStrike Falcon for Mobile integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up CrowdStrike Falcon Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/crowdstrike-falcon-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Mobile Threat Defense compliance policies in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create an Intune device compliance policy that uses your MTD partner threat levels to determine if a mobile device can access company resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-device-compliance-policy-create</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Mobile Threat Defense connector in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable the connector between your Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) partner and Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-connector-enable</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) app protection policy with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) app protection policy with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-app-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign MTD apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to add Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) apps, Microsoft Authenticator app, and iOS configuration policy in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-apps-ios-app-configuration-policy-add-assign</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Mobile Threat Defense apps to unenrolled devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Add Mobile Threat Defense apps to unenrolled devices by device users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-add-apps-unenrolled-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable the Mobile Threat Defense connector for unenrolled devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable the Mobile Threat Defense connector in Microsoft Intune for unenrolled devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mtd-enable-unenrolled-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SentinelOne MTD connector with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up SentinelOne Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/sentinelone-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Sophos Mobile integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Sophos Mobile solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/sophos-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Zimperium MTD integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Zimperium Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zimperium-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Lookout Mobile Endpoint Security with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Lookout Mobile Endpoint Security and Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/lookout-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zimperium MTD connector with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Zimperium Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zimperium-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Trend Micro MTD integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Trend Micro Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/trend-micro-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro Mobile Security and Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Trend Micro Mobile Threat Defense with with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/trend-micro-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Jamf Mobile Security with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Jamf Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/jamf-mtd-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Check Point Harmony integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up CheckPoint Harmony Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/checkpoint-sandblast-mobile-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Jamf Mobile Threat Protection integration with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Jamf Mobile Threat Protection solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/jamf-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Mobile Threat Defense with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Better Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/better-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symantec Endpoint Protection Mobile connector with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Symantec Endpoint Protection Mobile with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/skycure-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up BlackBerry Protect with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the CylancePROTECT (BlackBerry) MTD solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/blackberry-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check Point Harmony Mobile Mobile Threat Defense Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Check Point Harmony Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/checkpoint-sandblast-mobile-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trellix Mobile Security connector with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Trellix Mobile Security with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/trellix-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pradeo Mobile Threat Defense connector and Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Pradeo Mobile Threat Protection with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/pradeo-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Better Mobile integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate the third-party mobile threat defense solution of Better Mobile with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/better-mobile-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Trellix Mobile Security MTD with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Trellix Mobile Security mobile threat defense (MTD) solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/trellix-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Pradeo Mobile Threat Defense to integrate with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Pradeo Mobile Threat Protection solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/pradeo-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Sophos Mobile with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to use the Sophos Mobile solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/sophos-mtd-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lookout Mobile Endpoint with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up Lookout Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) How to set up to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/lookout-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up Symantec Endpoint Protection Mobile integration with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up the Symantec Endpoint Protection Mobile solution with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/skycure-mtd-connector-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Threat Defense with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune Mobile Threat Defense (MTD) with your Mobile Threat Defense partner to protect access to company resources based on device risk.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mobile-threat-defense</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackBerry Protect Mobile MTD and Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>How to set up CylancePROTECT Mobile (BlackBerry) with Microsoft Intune to control mobile device access to your corporate resources</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/blackberry-mobile-threat-defense-connector</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure schedules to gradually roll out Windows Updates in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure schedules that manage how and when Windows updates roll out to your managed devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/rollout-options</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 03:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune Enterprise Application Management - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Enterprise App Management and the Enterprise App Catalog in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-enterprise-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a policy using settings catalog in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use settings catalog in Microsoft Intune to configure thousands of settings for Windows 10/11, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, and Android client devices, including Microsoft Office apps, Microsoft Edge, administrative templates (ADMX), and more. Add these settings in a device configuration profile to secure devices, and control different programs and features. Use Microsoft Copilot to get What If analysis, and learn more about each setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/configuration/settings-catalog</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Windows Driver updates policy for Windows devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about using Microsoft Intune policy to manage Windows driver updates.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/driver-updates-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data storage and processing in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how personal data is stored and processed in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-store-process</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune Management Extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manually Add the Windows Company Portal App - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how your workforce can manually add the Windows 10 Company Portal app to their PC from the Microsoft Store.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/store-apps-company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor App Information and Assignments - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>After you assign an app to users or devices, use this information to help you monitor the app's status.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Edge on iOS and Android With Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune app protection and configuration policies with Microsoft Edge for iOS and Android to ensure corporate websites are always accessed with safeguards in place.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/manage-microsoft-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>File and command reference for Microsoft Tunnel Gateway, a VPN solution for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find file and command-line references for tools you use to install or manage the Microsoft Tunnel Gateway, a VPN server that runs on Linux.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/microsoft-tunnel-reference</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data collection in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about personal data collected in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/privacy-data-collect</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enroll Android Enterprise dedicated, fully managed, or corporate-owned work profile devices in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/android-dedicated-devices-fully-managed-enroll</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS/iPadOS App Protection Policy Settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the iOS/iPadOS app protection policy (APP) settings for iOS/iPadOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune product and capabilities documentation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn more about how Microsoft Intune products and capabilities can help you secure, deploy, and manage users, apps, and endpoint devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning guide to move to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan, design, implement, adopt, and move to Microsoft Intune. Get guidance and advice to determine goals, use-case scenarios and requirements, and create rollout and communication plans, support, testing, and validation plans.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-planning-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Windows Update rings policy in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and manage Intune policy for Windows update rings. You can configure, deploy, and pause update installation with Windows Update client policies using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/device-updates/windows/update-rings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>