<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Learn - in Intune</title>
    <description>The latest updates from Microsoft Learn in Intune</description>
    <link>https://learn.microsoft.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 12:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 12:02:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Using Remote Help on Windows to assist authenticated users. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Remote Help app to provide remote assistance to authenticated users who also run the Remote Help app, and to troubleshoot for frontline workers (FLW).</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/remote-help-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 02:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Reset Protection Emails Not Enforced in Intune for Android - Intune</title>
      <description>Describes an issue in which an Android Enterprise device can be activated by using a Google account that isn't included in the "Factory reset protection emails" setting.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/troubleshoot/mem/intune/device-configuration/factory-reset-protection-emails-not-enforced</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand Microsoft Intune management extension for Windows.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/intune-management-extension</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft 365 Apps to Windows devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to install Microsoft 365 apps on Windows 10/11 devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-office365</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshoot Win32 apps in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the most common methods to troubleshoot Win32 app issues with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-troubleshoot</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows app deployment by using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about Windows 10/11 app deployment scenarios available with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-windows-10-app-deploy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data protection for Windows MAM - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable protected MAM access to org data using Windows MAM.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/protect-mam-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign an app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>In this article, you'll use Microsoft Intune to add and assign an app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/quickstart-add-assign-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review app protection policy logs - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This topic describes how to configure Intune app protection policy (APP) logs.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-log</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Data Warehouse Collections - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>The Intune Data Warehouse collections provide details related to the Data Warehouse API.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/intune-data-warehouse-collections</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Microsoft 365 apps to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Intune to install Microsoft 365 apps on macOS devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add-office365-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Win32 apps on S mode devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enable Win32 apps on S mode devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-s-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph APIs to configure devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of all the Graph API entities with the matching Windows CSP and offset URI on Windows 10 devices and newer used when configuring devices in Microsoft Intune. See the matching API and CSP for shared PCs, endpoint protection, Microsoft Defender for Endpoint, identity protection, Windows 10 Teams, kiosk, and Windows Update client policies.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/graph-apis-used-by-intune-device-configuration-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare a Win32 app to be uploaded to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to prepare a Win32 app to be uploaded to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-prepare</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win32 app management in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune. This article provides an overview of the Intune Win32 app delivery and management capabilities.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add and assign Win32 apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add, assign, and manage Win32 apps with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-add</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Windows update packages in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to deploy a Windows update package (.msu file) in Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-win32-deploy-update-package</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add apps to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to add apps to Microsoft Intune so you can assign apps to users and devices. Intune supports a wide range of app types.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-add</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovered apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand details about the detected apps that Intune found on a device.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-discovered-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is app management in Microsoft Intune? - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about client app management capabilities by platform for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-management</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supported Microsoft Intune apps - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article provides lists of support partner and Microsoft apps that are commonly used with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-supported-intune-apps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Edge to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Edge to macOS devices using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-edge-macos</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Microsoft Edge for Windows to Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about adding Microsoft Edge for Windows to Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/apps-windows-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to configure the Intune Company Portal apps, Company Portal website, and Intune app - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can configure the Intune Company Portal apps, Company Portal website, and Intune app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/company-portal-app</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add PowerShell scripts to Windows devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create and run PowerShell scripts, assign the script policy to Microsoft Entra groups, and use reports to monitor the scripts. See the steps to delete scripts you add on Windows devices in Microsoft Intune. Read common issues and resolutions.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/powershell-scripts</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Intune policies to manage Windows LAPS - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Create policies to manage the Windows Local Administrator Policy Solution (LAPS) on Windows devices that enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-laps-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Microsoft Intune for increased security - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to improve your security posture with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/zero-trust-configure-security</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune App SDK for Android developer integration and testing guide - Plan the integration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Plan the integration to incorporate Intune mobile app management (MAM) into your Android app.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/developer/app-sdk-android-phase1</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows Backup for Organizations in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Enable Windows backup and restore in Intune for employees or students.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/enrollment/windows-backup-restore</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage account protection settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune endpoint security account protection policies to protect the identity and accounts of users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Windows LAPS with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how you can use Microsoft Microsoft Intune and application protection policy to manage the local administrator accounts on Windows devices. Through the Windows LAPS CSP, back up accounts and passwords to Microsoft Entra ID, define password requirements, and protect account passwords through scheduled password rotations and manual rotations at need.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/windows-laps-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Find out what's new in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/whats-new</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In development - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes Microsoft Intune features that are in development.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/in-development</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 22:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Intune to manage Microsoft Defender settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Intune policy to manage Microsoft Defender security settings on devices that aren't enrolled with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/mde-security-integration</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage approved apps for Windows devices with App Control for Business policy and Managed Installers in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use App Control for Business policies and a managed installer to manage which apps are approved to run on Windows devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-app-control-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Collect Diagnostics - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to collect diagnostics with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/collect-diagnostics</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Intune security baselines for Windows devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that have preset and recommended configurations to the Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Find lost devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Locate lost or stolen devices by using the locate device feature in Microsoft Intune. Get details on security and privacy information when using the locate device action.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-locate</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android app protection policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>This article describes the app protection policy settings for Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt macOS FileVault disk encryption with Intune policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to configure FileVault on macOS devices, and use the admin center to manage their recovery keys.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Disable Activation Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use Microsoft Intune to disable Activation Lock on Apple devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-activation-lock-disable</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Microsoft Defender for Endpoint in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune as a Mobile Threat Defense solution.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/advanced-threat-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Reset Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to reset a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-passcode-reset</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Sync - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the device sync remote action in Intune to apply policy, app, and configuration updates to managed devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-sync</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Send Custom Notifications - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Intune to create and send custom notifications to users of iOS/iPadOS and Android devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/custom-notifications</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings for Microsoft Defender Antivirus for Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the settings in the Microsoft Defender Antivirus profile for Windows devices. You can configure these settings as part of Endpoint security Antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and each settings default value.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-defender</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenarios for using Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Conditional Access is commonly used with Intune compliance policy for devices and apps</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/conditional-access-intune-common-ways-use</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View report details for encryption status of devices managed with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the Microsoft Intune admin center to view reports for device encryption status across macOS FileVault and Windows BitLocker encrypted devices that you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encryption-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security firewall settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security firewall policy settings for Windows and macOS in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-firewall-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect devices with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn about the Intune capabilities that can help you protect your devices and data against unauthorized access and other threats.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/device-protect</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Lost Mode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to enable Lost Mode in Microsoft Intune to remotely lock a lost or stolen iOS or iPadOS device and display a custom message and phone number on the lock screen.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-lost-mode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security disk encryption policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View the list of settings that are available in Microsoft Intune endpoint security disk encryption policy settings for BitLocker and FileVault.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-disk-encryption-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Update Cellular Data Plan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to update the cellular data plan for iOS/iPadOS devices that support eSIM with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/update-cellular-data-plan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor security baselines deployed by Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Monitor device and per-setting results of security baselines you deploy with Microsoft Intune, and identify conflicts for devices.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines-monitor</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security Account protection (Preview) policy settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security Account protection policy settings in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antivirus policy settings for Windows Security experience policy for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security Antivirus policy settings for the Windows Security app in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-security-experience-windows-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove User - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a user from a Shared iPad with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Logout current user - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the logout the current user from a Shared iPad with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-logout-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings from Windows security settings for tenant attached devices in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review the settings in the *Windows Security experience* profile for tenant attached devices. To use this Endpoint security Antivirus policy, you must first configure tenant attach for Configuration Manager for Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-windows-security-settings-windows-tenant-attach</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Shutdown - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to shutdown Apple devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-shutdown</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboard and Configure Devices with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint via Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Integrate Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune, including connecting the products, onboarding devices, and assigning policies for compliance and risk level assessment.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/advanced-threat-protection-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encrypt Windows devices with Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use Microsoft Intune policy to manage encryption of Windows devices with either BitLocker or Personal Data Encryption.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/encrypt-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Wipe - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to wipe, or factory reset, devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-wipe</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Quick Scan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand Microsoft Defender quick scan with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-quick-scan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: BitLocker Key Rotation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the BitLocker recovery key with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-bitlocker-keys</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security Attack surface reduction settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Details about the settings in the endpoint security Attack surface reduction policies in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-asr-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint detection and response policy. - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security endpoint detection and response policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-edr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage devices with endpoint security in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security node to view devices and manage them in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-manage-devices</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrator to standard user - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Understand the steps and phases for using Endpoint Privilege Management to transition users from administrators to standard users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-transition-administrator-to-standard-user</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Actions – Wipe, Lock, Locate, and More - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Discover how to use Microsoft Intune to remotely manage, wipe, lock, restart, and secure Android, iOS/iPadOS, macOS, Windows, and ChromeOS devices. Learn about available remote actions, prerequisites, and bulk actions for IT admins.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Run Remediation - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand remediations with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-run-remediation</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Apps and Configuration - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how apps and configurations can be removed temporarily, then restored automatically or manually using the Remove apps and configuration device action with Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/remove-apps-config</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune reports - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Intune provides specific report types with focused views that contain consistent and timely data.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/reports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Remote Action: Rotate FileVault Recovery Key - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the FileVault recovery key with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-filevault</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage antivirus settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies and use reports for devices you manage with endpoint security antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-antivirus-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings list for the Microsoft Edge security baseline in Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>View a list of the settings in the Microsoft Intune security baseline for Microsoft Edge browser. This list includes the default values for settings as found in the default configuration of the baseline.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baseline-settings-edge</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remove Passcode - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to remove a passcode with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remove-passcode</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage firewall settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security firewall policy in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-firewall-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Delete - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to delete devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-delete</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: New Remote Assistance Session - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the the new remote assistance session action in Intune to offer support to your users.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remote-assist</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Retire - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to retire device using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-retire</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial-Get started with cloud-native Windows endpoints</title>
      <description>Set up secure cloud-native Windows endpoints that are Microsoft Entra joined, enrolled in Intune, and then deploy at scale with Windows Autopilot.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/solutions/cloud-native-endpoints/cloud-native-windows-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Antivirus policy settings from Microsoft Defender Antivirus for tenant attached devices - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>See a list of the settings in the Microsoft Defender Antivirus profile for Windows devices managed by Configuration Manager. You can configure these settings as part of Endpoint security Antivirus policy in Microsoft Intune after you configure tenant attach for Configuration Manager.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows-tenant-attach</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Rotate local admin password - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to rotate the local admin password on Windows and macOS devices with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rotate-local-admin-password</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Play Lost Mode Sound - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Play lost device sound remote action in Microsoft Intune to trigger an audible alert on a lost, stolen, or misplaced device—helping users locate it quickly and securely.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-play-lost-mode-sound</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Pause Config Refresh - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to temporarily pause policy enforcement on Windows 11 devices using Intune's Pause Config Refresh remote action to support troubleshooting and manual changes.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/pause-config-refresh</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune endpoint security Endpoint detection and response settings - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Endpoint security Endpoint detection and response policy settings for deprecated profiles in Microsoft Intune</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-edr-profile-settings</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure security baseline policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Deploy security baselines that establish a default and recommended security postures on Windows devices you manage with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/security-baselines-configure</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Remote Lock - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Use the remote lock action in Microsoft Intune to lock a managed device that has a passcode or PIN.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-remote-lock</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Rename Device - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to use the Rename device remote action in Microsoft Intune to update the device name shown in the admin center. Useful for standardizing naming conventions, managing shared devices, and improving inventory clarity.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-rename</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about using Endpoint Privilege Management with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>To enhance the security of your organization, set your users to run with standard permissions while Endpoint Privilege Management ensures those users can seamlessly run specified files with elevated rights.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/epm-overview</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use reusable groups of settings policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Manage groups of settings for Intune profiles as a single object and then add that settings group object to multiple profile instances. Later changes you make to the settings groups  automatically apply to each profile that includes the reusable settings group.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/reusable-settings-groups</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Remote Action: Deprovision - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to deprovision a chromeOS device with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-deprovision</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Device Action: Full Scan - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how to initiate on demand Microsoft Defender full scan with Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/remote-actions/device-full-scan</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network endpoints for Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Review endpoints for Intune. This page lists IP addresses and port settings needed for proxy settings in your Intune deployments.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/intune-endpoints</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role-based access control (RBAC) with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Learn how RBAC lets you control who can perform actions and make changes in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/fundamentals/role-based-access-control</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage attack surface reduction settings with Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy policies for devices you manage with endpoint security attack surface reduction policy settings in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-asr-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Intune endpoint security disk encryption policy - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Configure and deploy Microsoft Intune endpoint security policy disk encryption policies for BitLocker and FileVault.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-disk-encryption-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune - Microsoft Intune</title>
      <description>Security Administrators can use the Endpoint Security policies and profiles to focus on security configuration of devices in Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/intune/intune-service/protect/endpoint-security-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>